US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
own	null	O	VB
in	null	O	IN
return	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
inject	null	O	VBG
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
30	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
own	null	O	VB
in	null	O	IN
return	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
inject	null	O	VBG
on	null	O	IN
top	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
20	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
provide	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
30.1	null	MONEY	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
government	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
9.5	null	MONEY	CD
Arabia	null	O	NNP
carry	null	O	VBD
passenger	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
3.6	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
100.28	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
12.93	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
debt	null	O	NN
over	null	O	IN
concern	null	O	VBN
pledge	null	O	VBD
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
30	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
star	null	O	NN
dream	null	O	VBD
dream	null	O	NN
hit	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
viewing	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
100	null	NUMBER	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
audition	null	O	NNS
hit	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
viewing	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
100	null	NUMBER	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
Talent	null	O	NNP
watch	null	O	VBD
total	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
19.2	null	NUMBER	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
worth	null	O	JJ
close	null	O	VBD
on	null	O	IN
volume	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
share	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
3.53	null	NUMBER	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
2.45	null	NUMBER	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
1.70	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
billion	null	MONEY	CD
dollar	null	O	NNS
worth	null	O	JJ
close	null	O	VBD
on	null	O	IN
volume	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
share	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
3.53	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
billion	null	MONEY	CD
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
2.45	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
billion	null	MONEY	CD
1.70	null	MONEY	CD
swedish	null	MISC	JJ
government	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
krona	null	O	NNS
creditor	null	O	NN
owe	null	O	VBZ
krona	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
9.7	null	MONEY	CD
swedish	null	MISC	JJ
government	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
krona	null	O	NNS
creditor	null	O	NN
owe	null	O	VBZ
krona	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
1.3	null	MONEY	CD
swedish	null	MISC	JJ
government	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
krona	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
347	null	NUMBER	CD
Zimbabwe	null	LOCATION	NNP
need	null	O	VBZ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
718	null	MONEY	CD
Zimbabwe	null	LOCATION	NNP
need	null	O	VBZ
say	null	O	VBD
need	null	O	VBZ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
718	null	MONEY	CD
Zimbabwe	null	LOCATION	NNP
HARARE	null	LOCATION	NNP
need	null	O	VBZ
say	null	O	VBD
need	null	O	VBZ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
718	null	MONEY	CD
Zimbabwe	null	LOCATION	NNP
HARARE	null	LOCATION	NNP
need	null	O	VBZ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
718	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Nations	null	ORGANIZATION	NNPS
say	null	O	VBD
need	null	O	VBZ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
718	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Nations	null	ORGANIZATION	NNPS
say	null	O	VBD
need	null	O	VBZ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
718	null	MONEY	CD
Zimbabwe	null	LOCATION	NNP
assist	null	O	VB
appeal	null	O	VBD
for	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
550	null	MONEY	CD
Iraq	null	LOCATION	NNP
have	null	O	VBN
shortfall	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
10	null	MONEY	CD
Iraq	null	LOCATION	NNP
oil	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
incompetence	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
due	null	O	JJ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
10	null	MONEY	CD
Iraq	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
field	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
tag	null	O	NN
than	null	O	IN
less	null	O	JJR
production	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
500	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
offer	null	O	VB
as	null	O	IN
part	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
bailout	null	O	NN
worth	null	O	JJ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
59	null	MONEY	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
subsidiary	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
loan	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
form	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
be	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
1.3	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
take	null	O	VB
pump	null	O	NN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
30	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
history	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
proceedings	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
one	null	NUMBER	CD
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
of	null	O	IN
debt	null	O	NNS
asset	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
82.3	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
history	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
proceedings	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
one	null	NUMBER	CD
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
172.8	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
give	null	O	VB
provide	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
9.5	null	MONEY	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
government	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
9.5	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
own	null	O	VB
in	null	O	IN
return	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
inject	null	O	VBG
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
30	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
own	null	O	VB
in	null	O	IN
return	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
inject	null	O	VBG
on	null	O	IN
top	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
20	null	MONEY	CD
japanese	null	MISC	JJ
automaker	null	O	NN
sell	null	O	VBD
sell	null	O	VBZ
vehicle	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
9.369	null	NUMBER	CD
japanese	null	MISC	JJ
automaker	null	O	NN
sell	null	O	VBD
million	null	NUMBER	CD
9.366	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
loan	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
receive	null	O	VBZ
bring	null	O	VBG
to	null	O	TO
billion	null	MONEY	CD
19.4	null	MONEY	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
retaliate	null	O	VBN
by	null	O	IN
place	null	O	VBG
tariff	null	O	NNS
represent	null	O	VBG
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
2.4	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
product	null	O	NNS
on	null	O	IN
place	null	O	VBG
tariff	null	O	NNS
represent	null	O	VBG
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
2.4	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
in	null	O	IN
product	null	O	NNS
on	null	O	IN
place	null	O	VBG
tariff	null	O	NNS
represent	null	O	VBG
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
2.4	null	MONEY	CD
Azerbaijan	null	LOCATION	NNP
country	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
8.7	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
27.1	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
3.49	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
star	null	O	NN
dream	null	O	VBD
dream	null	O	NN
hit	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
viewing	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
100	null	NUMBER	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
audition	null	O	NNS
hit	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
viewing	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
100	null	NUMBER	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
Talent	null	O	NNP
watch	null	O	VBD
total	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
19.2	null	NUMBER	CD
Kuwaiti	null	MISC	NNP
size	null	O	NN
demand	null	O	VBD
provide	null	O	VBZ
size	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
follow	null	O	VBG
over	null	O	IN
figure	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
barrel	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
100	null	MONEY	CD
KUWAIT	null	LOCATION	NNP
CITY	null	LOCATION	NNP
size	null	O	NN
demand	null	O	VBD
provide	null	O	VBZ
size	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
follow	null	O	VBG
over	null	O	IN
figure	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
barrel	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
100	null	MONEY	CD
kuwaiti	null	LOCATION	JJ
lawmaker	null	O	NN
CITY	null	LOCATION	NNP
size	null	O	NN
demand	null	O	VBD
provide	null	O	VBZ
size	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
follow	null	O	VBG
over	null	O	IN
figure	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
barrel	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
100	null	MONEY	CD
Kuwait	null	LOCATION	NNP
reserve	null	O	NNS
stand	null	O	VBD
at	null	O	IN
barrel	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
48	null	MONEY	CD
Kuwaiti	null	LOCATION	NNP
reserve	null	O	NNS
barrel	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
100	null	NUMBER	CD
Kuwait	null	LOCATION	NNP
reserve	null	O	NNS
amount	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
barrel	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
24.2	null	NUMBER	CD
Kuwait	null	LOCATION	NNP
barrel	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
100	null	NUMBER	CD
Arabia	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
those	null	O	DT
after	null	O	IN
form	null	O	VBP
barrel	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
100	null	NUMBER	CD
Iran	null	LOCATION	NNP
Arabia	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
those	null	O	DT
after	null	O	IN
form	null	O	VBP
barrel	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
100	null	NUMBER	CD
Iraq	null	LOCATION	NNP
Arabia	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
those	null	O	DT
after	null	O	IN
form	null	O	VBP
barrel	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
100	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
Emirates	null	LOCATION	NNPS
Arabia	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
those	null	O	DT
after	null	O	IN
form	null	O	VBP
barrel	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
100	null	NUMBER	CD
Kuwait	null	LOCATION	NNP
pump	null	O	VBG
around	null	O	RP
barrel	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.2	null	NUMBER	CD
Russian	null	MISC	NNP
bank	null	O	NNS
need	null	O	VBP
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
40	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
official	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
30	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
official	null	O	NNS
pledge	null	O	VBD
on	null	O	IN
top	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
20	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
give	null	O	VB
provide	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
9.5	null	MONEY	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
government	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
9.5	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
history	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
case	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
one	null	NUMBER	CD
in	null	O	IN
list	null	O	VBD
asset	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
82.3	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
history	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
case	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
one	null	NUMBER	CD
in	null	O	IN
list	null	O	VBD
asset	null	O	NNS
debt	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
172.8	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
official	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
30	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
official	null	O	NNS
pledge	null	O	VBD
on	null	O	IN
top	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
20	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
give	null	O	VB
provide	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
9.5	null	MONEY	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
government	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
9.5	null	MONEY	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
audition	null	O	NNS
hit	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
viewing	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
100	null	NUMBER	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
Talent	null	O	NNP
watch	null	O	VBD
total	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
19.2	null	NUMBER	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
boost	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
move	null	O	NN
worth	null	O	NN
billion	null	MONEY	CD
85	null	MONEY	CD
german	null	MISC	JJ
french	null	MISC	JJ
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
boost	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
move	null	O	NN
worth	null	O	NN
billion	null	MONEY	CD
85	null	MONEY	CD
spanish	null	LOCATION	JJ
french	null	MISC	JJ
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
boost	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
move	null	O	NN
worth	null	O	NN
billion	null	MONEY	CD
85	null	MONEY	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
leader	null	O	NNS
express	null	O	VBN
concern	null	O	NNS
over	null	O	IN
safety	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
800	null	MONEY	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
800	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
bond	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
safety	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
800	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
deficit	null	O	NN
amid	null	O	IN
express	null	O	VBN
concern	null	O	NNS
over	null	O	IN
safety	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
800	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
investment	null	O	NN
reach	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
50	null	MONEY	CD
American	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Express	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
commence	null	O	VBN
offering	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
500	null	MONEY	CD
American	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Express	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
commence	null	O	VBN
as	null	O	IN
part	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
plan	null	O	NN
raise	null	O	VB
repay	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
investment	null	O	NN
billion	null	MONEY	CD
3.4	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
repay	null	O	VB
raise	null	O	VB
plan	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
part	null	O	NN
as	null	O	IN
commence	null	O	VBN
offering	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
500	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
repay	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
investment	null	O	NN
billion	null	MONEY	CD
3.4	null	MONEY	CD
Belarus	null	LOCATION	NNP
refuse	null	O	VBN
tranche	null	O	NN
dollar	null	MONEY	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
500	null	MONEY	CD
russian	null	LOCATION	JJ
loan	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
tranche	null	O	NN
dollar	null	MONEY	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
500	null	MONEY	CD
russian	null	MISC	JJ
ruble	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
in	null	O	IN
receive	null	O	VBG
on	null	O	IN
insist	null	O	VBN
refuse	null	O	VBN
tranche	null	O	NN
dollar	null	MONEY	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
500	null	MONEY	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
leader	null	O	NNS
express	null	O	VBN
concern	null	O	NNS
over	null	O	IN
safety	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
800	null	MONEY	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
800	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
bond	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
safety	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
800	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
deficit	null	O	NN
amid	null	O	IN
express	null	O	VBN
concern	null	O	NNS
over	null	O	IN
safety	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
800	null	MONEY	CD
Taiwan	null	LOCATION	NNP
PVI	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
acquire	null	O	VBZ
ink	null	ORGANIZATION	NN
announce	null	O	VBD
buy	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
215	null	MONEY	CD
Taiwan	null	LOCATION	NNP
International	null	O	NNP
announce	null	O	VBD
buy	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
215	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
buy	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
215	null	MONEY	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
dalit	null	MISC	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
160	null	NUMBER	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
boost	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
move	null	O	NN
worth	null	O	NN
billion	null	MONEY	CD
85	null	MONEY	CD
german	null	MISC	JJ
french	null	MISC	JJ
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
boost	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
move	null	O	NN
worth	null	O	NN
billion	null	MONEY	CD
85	null	MONEY	CD
spanish	null	LOCATION	JJ
french	null	MISC	JJ
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
boost	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
move	null	O	NN
worth	null	O	NN
billion	null	MONEY	CD
85	null	MONEY	CD
Poland	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
Jews	null	MISC	NNPS
of	null	O	IN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
die	null	O	VBD
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
1.1	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
firm	null	O	NN
stay	null	O	VBZ
of	null	O	IN
part	null	O	NN
ensure	null	O	VB
offer	null	O	VBN
worth	null	O	JJ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
60	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
50	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
46	null	NUMBER	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
be	null	O	VB
job	null	O	NNS
700,000	null	NUMBER	CD
canadian	null	ORGANIZATION	JJ
Union	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
be	null	O	VB
job	null	O	NNS
700,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
operation	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
maintain	null	O	VB
spend	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
2.4	null	MONEY	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
operation	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
maintain	null	O	VB
spend	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
900	null	MONEY	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
subsidiary	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
loan	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
form	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
be	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
1.3	null	MONEY	CD
North	null	LOCATION	NNP
America	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
manufacture	null	O	VB
car	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
3.0	null	NUMBER	CD
America	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
manufacture	null	O	VB
car	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
3.0	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
to	null	O	TO
offer	null	O	VB
as	null	O	IN
part	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
bailout	null	O	NN
worth	null	O	JJ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
60	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
firm	null	O	NN
production	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
portion	null	O	NN
keep	null	O	VB
offer	null	O	VB
as	null	O	IN
part	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
bailout	null	O	NN
worth	null	O	JJ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
60	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
court	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
file	null	O	VBN
emerge	null	O	VBZ
receive	null	O	VB
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
400	null	MONEY	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
subsidiary	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
loan	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
form	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
be	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
1.3	null	MONEY	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
operation	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
maintain	null	O	VB
spend	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
2.4	null	MONEY	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
operation	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
maintain	null	O	VB
spend	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
900	null	MONEY	CD
North	null	LOCATION	NNP
America	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
manufacture	null	O	VB
car	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
3.0	null	NUMBER	CD
America	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
manufacture	null	O	VB
car	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
3.0	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
provide	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
30.1	null	MONEY	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
government	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
9.5	null	MONEY	CD
indian	null	MISC	JJ
side	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
seek	null	O	VBG
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
200	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
court	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
file	null	O	VBN
emerge	null	O	VBZ
receive	null	O	VB
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
400	null	MONEY	CD
Canada	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
loan	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
form	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
be	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
1.3	null	MONEY	CD
Kuwaiti	null	MISC	NNP
official	null	O	NNS
say	null	O	VBD
owe	null	O	VBZ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
25.5	null	MONEY	CD
Iraq	null	LOCATION	NNP
owe	null	O	VBZ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
25.5	null	MONEY	CD
iraqi	null	LOCATION	JJ
Hussein	null	PERSON	NNP
of	null	O	IN
regime	null	O	NN
under	null	O	IN
occupation	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
reparation	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
owe	null	O	VBZ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
25.5	null	MONEY	CD
Kuwait	null	LOCATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBZ
owe	null	O	VBZ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
16	null	MONEY	CD
Iran	null	LOCATION	NNP
with	null	O	IN
war	null	O	NN
during	null	O	IN
loan	null	O	NNS
from	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
16	null	MONEY	CD
Kuwait	null	LOCATION	NNP
figure	null	O	NNS
on	null	O	IN
base	null	O	VBN
receive	null	O	VBN
claim	null	O	NNS
worth	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
368	null	MONEY	CD
Kuwait	null	LOCATION	NNP
figure	null	O	NNS
on	null	O	IN
base	null	O	VBN
receive	null	O	VBN
approve	null	O	VBN
payment	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
52	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
Corp.	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
for	null	O	IN
bid	null	O	NN
offer	null	O	VBD
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
1.8	null	MONEY	CD
Somalia	null	LOCATION	NNP
have	null	O	VBN
country	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
10	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
level	null	O	NNS
plummet	null	O	VBP
from	null	O	IN
600,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
437.5	null	NUMBER	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
302	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
million	null	NUMBER	CD
dollar	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
437.5	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
million	null	NUMBER	CD
302	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
sale	null	O	NNS
reach	null	O	VBP
vehicle	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
10	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
obtain	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
company	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
exchange	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
provide	null	O	VBG
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
50	null	MONEY	CD
Brazil	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
director	null	O	NN
Gilliam	null	PERSON	NNP
gather	null	O	VBD
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
32	null	MONEY	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
Paradis	null	PERSON	NNP
star	null	O	VBG
film	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
financing	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
gather	null	O	VBD
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
32	null	MONEY	CD
Spanish	null	MISC	NNP
Palma	null	PERSON	NNP
Paradis	null	PERSON	NNP
star	null	O	VBG
film	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
financing	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
gather	null	O	VBD
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
32	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
history	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
case	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
one	null	NUMBER	CD
in	null	O	IN
list	null	O	VBD
asset	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
82.3	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
history	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
case	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
one	null	NUMBER	CD
in	null	O	IN
list	null	O	VBD
asset	null	O	NN
debt	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
172.8	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
official	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
30	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
official	null	O	NNS
pledge	null	O	VBD
on	null	O	IN
top	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
20	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
give	null	O	VB
provide	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
9.5	null	MONEY	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
government	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
9.5	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
history	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
case	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
one	null	NUMBER	CD
in	null	O	IN
list	null	O	VBD
asset	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
82.3	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
history	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
case	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
one	null	NUMBER	CD
in	null	O	IN
list	null	O	VBD
asset	null	O	NN
debt	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
172.8	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
official	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
30	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
official	null	O	NNS
pledge	null	O	VBD
on	null	O	IN
top	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
20	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
give	null	O	VB
provide	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
9.5	null	MONEY	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
government	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
9.5	null	MONEY	CD
Zimbabwe	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Zimbabwe-aid-UN	null	PERSON	NNP
by	null	O	IN
GMT	null	MISC	NNP
need	null	O	VBZ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
718	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Nations	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBZ
need	null	O	VBZ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
718	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
obtain	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
company	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
exchange	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
provide	null	O	VBG
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
50	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
level	null	O	NNS
plummet	null	O	VBP
from	null	O	IN
600,000	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
meltdown	null	O	NN
from	null	O	IN
result	null	O	VBG
turmoil	null	O	NN
follow	null	O	VBG
take	null	O	VBD
pump	null	O	VBN
company	null	O	NNS
hold	null	O	VBZ
after	null	O	IN
inject	null	O	VBG
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
170	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
giant	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
provide	null	O	VBN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
20	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
giant	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
provide	null	O	VBN
promise	null	O	VBD
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
30	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
giant	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
provide	null	O	VBN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
12.5	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
history	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
case	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
one	null	NUMBER	CD
in	null	O	IN
list	null	O	VBD
asset	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
82.3	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
history	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
case	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
one	null	NUMBER	CD
in	null	O	IN
list	null	O	VBD
asset	null	O	NN
debt	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
172.8	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
official	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
30	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
official	null	O	NNS
pledge	null	O	VBD
on	null	O	IN
top	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
20	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
give	null	O	VB
provide	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
9.5	null	MONEY	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
government	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
9.5	null	MONEY	CD
Georgia	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
slowdown	null	O	NN
follow	null	O	VBG
in	null	O	IN
despite	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
4.5	null	MONEY	CD
Zimbabwe	null	LOCATION	NNP
need	null	O	VBZ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
718	null	MONEY	CD
Zimbabwe	null	LOCATION	NNP
need	null	O	VBZ
say	null	O	VBD
need	null	O	VBZ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
718	null	MONEY	CD
Zimbabwe	null	LOCATION	NNP
HARARE	null	LOCATION	NNP
need	null	O	VBZ
say	null	O	VBD
need	null	O	VBZ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
718	null	MONEY	CD
Zimbabwe	null	LOCATION	NNP
HARARE	null	LOCATION	NNP
need	null	O	VBZ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
718	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Nations	null	ORGANIZATION	NNPS
say	null	O	VBD
need	null	O	VBZ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
718	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Nations	null	ORGANIZATION	NNPS
say	null	O	VBD
need	null	O	VBZ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
718	null	MONEY	CD
Zimbabwe	null	LOCATION	NNP
assist	null	O	VB
appeal	null	O	VBD
for	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
550	null	MONEY	CD
Zimbabwe	null	LOCATION	NNP
have	null	O	VBZ
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
1.3	null	NUMBER	CD
Zimbabwe	null	LOCATION	NNP
have	null	O	VBZ
with	null	O	IN
orphan	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
1.5	null	NUMBER	CD
Egypt	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
supporter	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
40	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	MONEY	NN
billion	null	MONEY	CD
15.5	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
billion	null	MONEY	CD
12.2	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
Treasury	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
loan	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
keep	null	O	VB
manage	null	O	VBN
rack	null	O	VBD
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
88	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
Treasury	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
loan	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
keep	null	O	VB
with	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
19.4	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
from	null	O	IN
see	null	O	VBN
bring	null	O	VBD
hit	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
100	null	NUMBER	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
from	null	O	IN
see	null	O	VBN
bring	null	O	VBD
hit	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
100	null	NUMBER	CD
Japan	null	LOCATION	NNP
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
from	null	O	IN
see	null	O	VBN
bring	null	O	VBD
hit	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
100	null	NUMBER	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
from	null	O	IN
see	null	O	VBN
bring	null	O	VBD
hit	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
100	null	NUMBER	CD
Arabia	null	LOCATION	NNP
barrel	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
115	null	MONEY	CD
Iran	null	LOCATION	NNP
Arabia	null	LOCATION	NNP
barrel	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
115	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	MONEY	NN
billion	null	MONEY	CD
15.5	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
billion	null	MONEY	CD
12.2	null	MONEY	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Na	null	PERSON	NNP
6.2	null	NUMBER	CD
Scott	null	PERSON	NNP
Na	null	PERSON	NNP
6.2	null	NUMBER	CD
Egypt	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
supporter	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
40	null	NUMBER	CD
Israel	null	LOCATION	NNP
enter	null	O	VB
land	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
1.5	null	NUMBER	CD
Arabia	null	LOCATION	NNP
barrel	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
115	null	MONEY	CD
Iran	null	LOCATION	NNP
Arabia	null	LOCATION	NNP
barrel	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
115	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
Treasury	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
loan	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
keep	null	O	VB
with	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
19.4	null	MONEY	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
faith	null	O	NN
follow	null	O	VBP
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
24	null	NUMBER	CD
Kuwait	null	LOCATION	NNP
pump	null	O	NNS
barrel	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.2	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
earnings	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
12.7	null	MONEY	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
embrace	null	O	VBD
Moore	null	PERSON	NNP
include	null	O	VBG
bring	null	O	VBD
have	null	O	VBN
hit	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
100	null	NUMBER	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
watch	null	O	VBD
total	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
19.2	null	NUMBER	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
budget	null	O	VBN
over	null	O	IN
ruble	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
10	null	MONEY	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
budget	null	O	VBN
over	null	O	IN
ruble	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
320	null	MONEY	CD
Scott	null	PERSON	NNP
Steinberg	null	PERSON	NNP
website	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
reader	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
40	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
invest	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
30	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
invest	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
on	null	O	IN
top	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
20	null	MONEY	CD
israeli	null	MISC	JJ
community	null	O	NN
comprise	null	O	VBZ
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
1.2	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
embrace	null	O	VBD
Moore	null	PERSON	NNP
include	null	O	VBG
bring	null	O	VBD
have	null	O	VBN
hit	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
100	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
discuss	null	O	VB
sale	null	O	NNS
include	null	O	VBG
request	null	O	NN
buy	null	O	VB
worth	null	O	JJ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
15.2	null	MONEY	CD
Israel	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
sale	null	O	NNS
include	null	O	VBG
request	null	O	NN
buy	null	O	VB
worth	null	O	JJ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
15.2	null	MONEY	CD
Egypt	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
supporter	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
40	null	NUMBER	CD
Israel	null	LOCATION	NNP
control	null	O	NN
over	null	O	IN
Bank	null	LOCATION	NNP
be	null	O	VBZ
to	null	O	TO
Palestinians	null	MISC	NNPS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.4	null	NUMBER	CD
japanese	null	MISC	JJ
automaker	null	O	NN
sell	null	O	VBD
sell	null	O	VBZ
vehicle	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
9.369	null	NUMBER	CD
japanese	null	MISC	JJ
automaker	null	O	NN
sell	null	O	VBD
million	null	NUMBER	CD
9.366	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
loan	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
receive	null	O	VBZ
bring	null	O	VBG
to	null	O	TO
billion	null	MONEY	CD
19.4	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
ship	null	O	VBG
represent	null	O	VBG
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
of	null	O	IN
car	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
3.1	null	NUMBER	CD
Kuwait	null	LOCATION	NNP
pump	null	O	NNS
barrel	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.2	null	NUMBER	CD
Niger	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Delta	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
unrest	null	O	NN
reduce	null	O	VBN
output	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
barrel	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
1.76	null	NUMBER	CD
Niger	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Delta	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
unrest	null	O	NN
reduce	null	O	VBN
compare	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
barrel	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.6	null	NUMBER	CD
Nigeria	null	LOCATION	NNP
output	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
barrel	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
1.76	null	NUMBER	CD
Nigeria	null	LOCATION	NNP
output	null	O	NN
reduce	null	O	VBN
compare	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
barrel	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.6	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
embrace	null	O	VBD
Moore	null	PERSON	NNP
include	null	O	VBG
bring	null	O	VBD
have	null	O	VBN
hit	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
100	null	NUMBER	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
of	null	O	IN
rights	null	O	NNS
erode	null	O	VBN
islamise	null	MISC	VBN
country	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	NUMBER	CD
indian	null	MISC	JJ
minority	null	O	NNS
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
of	null	O	IN
rights	null	O	NNS
erode	null	O	VBN
islamise	null	MISC	VBN
country	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	NUMBER	CD
Niger	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Delta	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
violence	null	O	NN
reduce	null	O	VBN
output	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
barrel	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
1.76	null	NUMBER	CD
Niger	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Delta	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
violence	null	O	NN
reduce	null	O	VBN
compare	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
barrel	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.6	null	NUMBER	CD
Nigeria	null	LOCATION	NNP
output	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
barrel	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
1.76	null	NUMBER	CD
Nigeria	null	LOCATION	NNP
output	null	O	NN
reduce	null	O	VBN
compare	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
barrel	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.6	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
from	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
33.3	null	MONEY	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
from	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
33.3	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
history	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
case	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
one	null	NUMBER	CD
in	null	O	IN
list	null	O	VBD
asset	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
82.3	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
history	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
case	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
one	null	NUMBER	CD
in	null	O	IN
list	null	O	VBD
asset	null	O	NNS
debt	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
172.8	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
discuss	null	O	VB
sale	null	O	NNS
include	null	O	VBG
request	null	O	NN
buy	null	O	VB
worth	null	O	JJ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
15.2	null	MONEY	CD
Israel	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
sale	null	O	NNS
include	null	O	VBG
request	null	O	NN
buy	null	O	VB
worth	null	O	JJ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
15.2	null	MONEY	CD
israeli	null	MISC	JJ
official	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
expect	null	O	VBN
discuss	null	O	VB
sale	null	O	NNS
include	null	O	VBG
request	null	O	NN
buy	null	O	VB
worth	null	O	JJ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
15.2	null	MONEY	CD
Taiwan	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
201.85	null	NUMBER	CD
Taiwan	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
6.23	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
201.85	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
6.23	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
sector	null	O	NN
lose	null	O	VBN
job	null	O	NNS
532,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Malaysia	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Airlines	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
order	null	O	VBN
pay	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
9.8	null	MONEY	CD
german	null	MISC	JJ
firm	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
contract	null	O	NN
break	null	O	VBG
after	null	O	IN
pay	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
9.8	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
dream	null	O	VBD
dream	null	O	NN
hit	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
viewing	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
100	null	NUMBER	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
audition	null	O	NNS
hit	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
viewing	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
100	null	NUMBER	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
Talent	null	O	NNP
watch	null	O	VBD
total	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
19.2	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
population	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
Muslims	null	MISC	NNPS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
1.4	null	NUMBER	CD
Taiwan	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
201.85	null	NUMBER	CD
Taiwan	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
6.23	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
201.85	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
6.23	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
101.86	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
13.06	null	NUMBER	CD
danish	null	MISC	JJ
krone	null	O	NN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
10	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
agency	null	O	NNS
through	null	O	IN
channel	null	O	VBN
worth	null	O	JJ
krone	null	O	NN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
10	null	NUMBER	CD
danish	null	MISC	JJ
organization	null	O	NNS
agency	null	O	NNS
through	null	O	IN
channel	null	O	VBN
worth	null	O	JJ
krone	null	O	NN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
10	null	NUMBER	CD
danish	null	MISC	JJ
government	null	O	NN
release	null	O	VBN
krone	null	O	NN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
24	null	NUMBER	CD
danish	null	MISC	JJ
government	null	O	NN
release	null	O	VBN
bring	null	O	VBG
to	null	O	TO
krone	null	O	NN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
34	null	NUMBER	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
for	null	O	IN
krone	null	O	NN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
24	null	NUMBER	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
for	null	O	IN
krone	null	O	NN
release	null	O	VBN
bring	null	O	VBG
to	null	O	TO
krone	null	O	NN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
34	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
4.6	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
3.7	null	NUMBER	CD
Iraq	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
rest	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
most	null	O	JJS
in	null	O	IN
hold	null	O	VBN
elect	null	O	VB
voter	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.5	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
130.3	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
million	null	NUMBER	CD
84.4	null	NUMBER	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
try	null	O	VBG
give	null	O	VBZ
purchase	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
800	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
asset	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
purchase	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
800	null	MONEY	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
fund	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
raise	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
2.2	null	MONEY	CD
japanese	null	MISC	JJ
bank	null	O	NN
expect	null	O	VBN
raise	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
2.2	null	MONEY	CD
China	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Corp.	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
fund	null	O	NN
dollar	null	MONEY	NN
billion	null	MONEY	CD
200	null	MONEY	CD
japanese	null	MISC	JJ
Group	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
CIC	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
be	null	O	VB
among	null	O	IN
buyer	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
2.2	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
capital	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
receive	null	O	VBN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
10	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
sector	null	O	NN
lose	null	O	VBN
job	null	O	NNS
532,000	null	NUMBER	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
boost	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
move	null	O	NN
worth	null	O	NN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
85	null	MONEY	CD
german	null	MISC	JJ
french	null	MISC	JJ
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
boost	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
move	null	O	NN
worth	null	O	NN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
85	null	MONEY	CD
spanish	null	MISC	JJ
french	null	MISC	JJ
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
boost	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
move	null	O	NN
worth	null	O	NN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
85	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
from	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
33.3	null	MONEY	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
from	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
33.3	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
history	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
case	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
one	null	NUMBER	CD
in	null	O	IN
list	null	O	VBD
asset	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
82.3	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
history	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
case	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
one	null	NUMBER	CD
in	null	O	IN
list	null	O	VBD
asset	null	O	NNS
debt	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
172.8	null	NUMBER	CD
chinese	null	LOCATION	JJ
media	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
event	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
mention	null	O	NN
monitor	null	O	VBG
reach	null	O	VB
to	null	O	TO
world	null	O	NN
Muslims	null	MISC	NNPS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
1.5	null	NUMBER	CD
chinese	null	LOCATION	JJ
media	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
event	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
mention	null	O	NN
monitor	null	O	VBG
reach	null	O	VB
to	null	O	TO
world	null	O	NN
Muslims	null	MISC	NNPS
in	null	O	IN
speech	null	O	NN
expect	null	O	VBN
begin	null	O	VB
on	null	O	IN
charge	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
attempt	null	O	VBG
topple	null	O	VB
ISLAMABAD	null	LOCATION	NNP
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
visit	null	O	VBG
be	null	O	VBZ
visit	null	O	VB
assess	null	O	VB
of	null	O	IN
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.5	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
Obama	null	PERSON	NNP
reach	null	O	VB
to	null	O	TO
world	null	O	NN
Muslims	null	MISC	NNPS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
1.5	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
Obama	null	PERSON	NNP
reach	null	O	VB
to	null	O	TO
world	null	O	NN
Muslims	null	MISC	NNPS
in	null	O	IN
speech	null	O	NN
expect	null	O	VBN
begin	null	O	VB
on	null	O	IN
charge	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
attempt	null	O	VBG
topple	null	O	VB
ISLAMABAD	null	LOCATION	NNP
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
visit	null	O	VBG
be	null	O	VBZ
visit	null	O	VB
assess	null	O	VB
of	null	O	IN
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.5	null	NUMBER	CD
France	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
plane	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
passenger	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
body	null	O	NNS
for	null	O	IN
continue	null	O	VBZ
Mukoko	null	PERSON	NNP
expect	null	O	VBN
speech	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
Muslims	null	MISC	NNPS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
1.5	null	NUMBER	CD
France	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
plane	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
passenger	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
body	null	O	NNS
for	null	O	IN
continue	null	O	VBZ
Mukoko	null	PERSON	NNP
begin	null	O	VB
on	null	O	IN
charge	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
attempt	null	O	VBG
topple	null	O	VB
ISLAMABAD	null	LOCATION	NNP
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
visit	null	O	VBG
be	null	O	VBZ
visit	null	O	VB
assess	null	O	VB
of	null	O	IN
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.5	null	NUMBER	CD
Zimbabwean	null	MISC	NNP
ISLAMABAD	null	LOCATION	NNP
topple	null	O	VB
attempt	null	O	VBG
of	null	O	IN
charge	null	O	NNS
on	null	O	IN
begin	null	O	VB
expect	null	O	VBN
speech	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
Muslims	null	MISC	NNPS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
1.5	null	NUMBER	CD
Zimbabwean	null	MISC	NNP
ISLAMABAD	null	LOCATION	NNP
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
visit	null	O	VBG
be	null	O	VBZ
visit	null	O	VB
assess	null	O	VB
of	null	O	IN
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.5	null	NUMBER	CD
ZIMBABWE	null	LOCATION	NNP
ISLAMABAD	null	LOCATION	NNP
topple	null	O	VB
attempt	null	O	VBG
of	null	O	IN
charge	null	O	NNS
on	null	O	IN
begin	null	O	VB
expect	null	O	VBN
speech	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
Muslims	null	MISC	NNPS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
1.5	null	NUMBER	CD
ZIMBABWE	null	LOCATION	NNP
ISLAMABAD	null	LOCATION	NNP
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
visit	null	O	VBG
be	null	O	VBZ
visit	null	O	VB
assess	null	O	VB
of	null	O	IN
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.5	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
ISLAMABAD	null	LOCATION	NNP
topple	null	O	VB
attempt	null	O	VBG
of	null	O	IN
charge	null	O	NNS
on	null	O	IN
begin	null	O	VB
expect	null	O	VBN
speech	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
Muslims	null	MISC	NNPS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
1.5	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
visit	null	O	VBG
be	null	O	VBZ
visit	null	O	VB
assess	null	O	VB
of	null	O	IN
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.5	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
envoy	null	O	NN
be	null	O	VBZ
visit	null	O	VBG
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
ISLAMABAD	null	LOCATION	NNP
topple	null	O	VB
attempt	null	O	VBG
of	null	O	IN
charge	null	O	NNS
on	null	O	IN
begin	null	O	VB
expect	null	O	VBN
speech	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
Muslims	null	MISC	NNPS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
1.5	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
envoy	null	O	NN
visit	null	O	VB
assess	null	O	VB
of	null	O	IN
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.5	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
LONDON	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
offensive	null	O	NN
by	null	O	IN
displace	null	O	VBN
people	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
assess	null	O	VB
visit	null	O	VB
be	null	O	VBZ
visit	null	O	VBG
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
ISLAMABAD	null	LOCATION	NNP
topple	null	O	VB
attempt	null	O	VBG
of	null	O	IN
charge	null	O	NNS
on	null	O	IN
begin	null	O	VB
expect	null	O	VBN
speech	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
Muslims	null	MISC	NNPS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
1.5	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
LONDON	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
offensive	null	O	NN
by	null	O	IN
displace	null	O	VBN
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.5	null	NUMBER	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
vote	null	O	VBZ
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
ISLAMABAD	null	LOCATION	NNP
topple	null	O	VB
attempt	null	O	VBG
of	null	O	IN
charge	null	O	NNS
on	null	O	IN
begin	null	O	VB
expect	null	O	VBN
speech	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
Muslims	null	MISC	NNPS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
1.5	null	NUMBER	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
vote	null	O	VBZ
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
visit	null	O	VBG
be	null	O	VBZ
visit	null	O	VB
assess	null	O	VB
of	null	O	IN
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.5	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
authority	null	O	NNS
ISLAMABAD	null	LOCATION	NNP
topple	null	O	VB
attempt	null	O	VBG
of	null	O	IN
charge	null	O	NNS
on	null	O	IN
begin	null	O	VB
expect	null	O	VBN
speech	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
Muslims	null	MISC	NNPS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
1.5	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
authority	null	O	NNS
ISLAMABAD	null	LOCATION	NNP
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
visit	null	O	VBG
be	null	O	VBZ
visit	null	O	VB
assess	null	O	VB
of	null	O	IN
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.5	null	NUMBER	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
boost	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
move	null	O	NN
buy	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
85	null	MONEY	CD
german	null	MISC	JJ
french	null	MISC	JJ
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
boost	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
move	null	O	NN
buy	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
85	null	MONEY	CD
spanish	null	LOCATION	JJ
french	null	MISC	JJ
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
boost	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
move	null	O	NN
buy	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
85	null	MONEY	CD
Japan	null	LOCATION	NNP
truckmaker	null	O	NN
Motors	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
fail	null	O	VB
collect	null	O	VB
yen	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
1.65	null	MONEY	CD
Japan	null	LOCATION	NNP
Enshu	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
fail	null	O	VB
collect	null	O	VB
yen	null	MONEY	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
314	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
firm	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
extend	null	O	VBN
account	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
collect	null	O	VB
yen	null	MONEY	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
314	null	MONEY	CD
Greenland	null	LOCATION	NNP
island	null	O	NN
cover	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
surface	null	O	NN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.1	null	NUMBER	CD
south	null	MISC	JJ
troops	null	O	NNS
600,000	null	NUMBER	CD
south	null	MISC	JJ
troops	null	O	NNS
confront	null	O	VBG
threat	null	O	NN
from	null	O	IN
military	null	O	NN
1.1	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
troops	null	O	NNS
by	null	O	IN
back	null	O	VBN
troops	null	O	NNS
600,000	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
troops	null	O	NNS
by	null	O	IN
back	null	O	VBN
troops	null	O	NNS
confront	null	O	VBG
threat	null	O	NN
from	null	O	IN
military	null	O	NN
1.1	null	NUMBER	CD
North	null	O	NNP
military	null	O	NN
from	null	O	IN
threat	null	O	NN
confront	null	O	VBG
troops	null	O	NNS
600,000	null	NUMBER	CD
North	null	O	NNP
military	null	O	NN
1.1	null	NUMBER	CD
Arabia	null	LOCATION	NNP
into	null	O	IN
fly	null	O	VBD
give	null	O	VB
much	null	O	JJ
speech	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
Muslims	null	MISC	NNPS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
1.5	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
report	null	O	VBD
tumble	null	O	VBN
barrel	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
5.4	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
tumble	null	O	VBN
barrel	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
5.4	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	O	NNP
sale	null	O	NNS
compare	null	O	VBN
performance	null	O	NN
rate	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
9.91	null	NUMBER	CD
Bolivia	null	LOCATION	NNP
improve	null	O	VBG
with	null	O	IN
Iran	null	LOCATION	NNP
send	null	O	VBD
ratify	null	O	VB
agreement	null	O	NN
dollar	null	MONEY	NN
billion	null	MONEY	CD
1.2	null	MONEY	CD
Iran	null	LOCATION	NNP
send	null	O	VBD
ratify	null	O	VB
agreement	null	O	NN
dollar	null	MONEY	NN
billion	null	MONEY	CD
1.2	null	MONEY	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
inject	null	O	VB
China	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
receive	null	O	VB
worth	null	O	JJ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
63	null	MONEY	CD
Macau	null	LOCATION	NNP
Beijing	null	LOCATION	NNP
into	null	O	IN
inject	null	O	VB
China	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
receive	null	O	VB
worth	null	O	JJ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
63	null	MONEY	CD
China	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
receive	null	O	VB
worth	null	O	JJ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
63	null	MONEY	CD
Macau	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
receive	null	O	VB
worth	null	O	JJ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
63	null	MONEY	CD
Macau	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
value	null	O	NN
stand	null	O	VBD
at	null	O	IN
yuan	null	MONEY	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
91.2	null	MONEY	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
hold	null	O	VBZ
value	null	O	NN
stand	null	O	VBD
at	null	O	IN
yuan	null	MONEY	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
91.2	null	MONEY	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
carrier	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
stand	null	O	VBD
at	null	O	IN
yuan	null	MONEY	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
91.2	null	MONEY	CD
Macau	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
into	null	O	IN
pump	null	O	VB
yuan	null	MONEY	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
431.2	null	MONEY	CD
Macau	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
government	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
issue	null	O	VBG
by	null	O	IN
pump	null	O	VB
yuan	null	MONEY	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
431.2	null	MONEY	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
wait	null	O	VBG
reach	null	O	VBD
yuan	null	MONEY	NN
billion	null	MONEY	CD
9.3	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
provide	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
30.1	null	MONEY	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
government	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
9.5	null	MONEY	CD
Malaysia	null	LOCATION	NNP
partner	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
trade	null	O	NN
worth	null	O	JJ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
billion	null	MONEY	CD
1.95	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
billion	null	MONEY	CD
1.95	null	MONEY	CD
Rwanda	null	LOCATION	NNP
genocide	null	O	NN
during	null	O	IN
kill	null	O	VBD
people	null	O	NNS
800,000	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
101.86	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
13.06	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
sector	null	O	NN
shed	null	O	VBD
job	null	O	NNS
532,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Egypt	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
travel	null	O	VB
deliver	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
reconciliation	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
Muslims	null	MISC	NNPS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
1.5	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
sector	null	O	NN
shed	null	O	VBD
job	null	O	NNS
532,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Somalia	null	LOCATION	NNP
have	null	O	VBN
country	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
10	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
claim	null	O	VBZ
die	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
operation	null	O	NNS
which	null	O	WDT
displace	null	O	VBN
to	null	O	TO
civilian	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.4	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
visit	null	O	VBG
say	null	O	VBD
seek	null	O	VBG
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
200	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
give	null	O	VBG
amount	null	O	NN
bring	null	O	VB
to	null	O	TO
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
300	null	MONEY	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
crisis	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
give	null	O	VBG
amount	null	O	NN
bring	null	O	VB
to	null	O	TO
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
300	null	MONEY	CD
Taiwan	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
231.19	null	NUMBER	CD
Taiwan	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
billion	null	MONEY	CD
7.26	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
231.19	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
billion	null	MONEY	CD
7.26	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
treasury	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
holder	null	O	NN
make	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
800	null	MONEY	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
try	null	O	VBG
give	null	O	VBZ
purchase	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
800	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
asset	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
purchase	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
800	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
soil	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
move	null	O	VB
use	null	O	NN
stop	null	O	VB
vote	null	O	VBD
run	null	O	VBD
into	null	O	IN
buzzsaw	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
opposition	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
Congress	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
block	null	O	VBD
use	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
130.3	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
million	null	NUMBER	CD
84.4	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
announce	null	O	VBN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
110	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Congress	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
through	null	O	IN
work	null	O	VBG
package	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
top	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
announce	null	O	VBN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
110	null	MONEY	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
root	null	O	NN
help	null	O	VB
work	null	O	VBG
package	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
top	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
announce	null	O	VBN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
110	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
priority	null	O	NN
extremism	null	O	NN
root	null	O	NN
help	null	O	VB
work	null	O	VBG
package	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
top	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
announce	null	O	VBN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
110	null	MONEY	CD
India	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
of	null	ORGANIZATION	IN
Trust	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
tell	null	O	VBD
live	null	O	VBG
family	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
6.4	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
provide	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
30.1	null	MONEY	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
government	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
9.5	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
visit	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
Coverage	null	O	NNP
who	null	O	WP
assess	null	O	VB
of	null	O	IN
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.4	null	NUMBER	CD
german	null	MISC	JJ
voter	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
62	null	NUMBER	CD
Germany	null	LOCATION	NNP
state	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
20	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
examine	null	O	VB
meet	null	O	VB
some	null	O	DT
of	null	O	IN
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.4	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
send	null	O	VBG
examine	null	O	VB
meet	null	O	VB
some	null	O	DT
of	null	O	IN
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.4	null	NUMBER	CD
Egypt	null	LOCATION	NNP
one	null	NUMBER	CD
receive	null	O	VBZ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
1.5	null	MONEY	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
try	null	O	VBG
give	null	O	VBZ
purchase	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
800	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
asset	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
purchase	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
800	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
from	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
33.3	null	MONEY	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
from	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
33.3	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
history	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
case	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
one	null	NUMBER	CD
in	null	O	IN
list	null	O	VBD
asset	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
82.3	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
history	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
case	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
one	null	NUMBER	CD
in	null	O	IN
list	null	O	VBD
asset	null	O	NNS
debt	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
172.8	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
base	null	O	NN
cross	null	O	VBZ
Delhi	null	LOCATION	NNP
million	null	NUMBER	CD
400	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
base	null	O	NN
cross	null	O	VBZ
cross	null	O	VBD
mark	null	O	NN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
400	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
base	null	O	NN
cross	null	O	VBZ
cross	null	O	VBD
show	null	O	VBD
put	null	O	VBG
on	null	O	IN
track	null	O	NN
reach	null	O	VB
goal	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
customer	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
500	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
subscriber	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
number	null	O	NN
cross	null	O	VBD
cross	null	O	VBZ
Delhi	null	LOCATION	NNP
million	null	NUMBER	CD
400	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
subscriber	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
number	null	O	NN
cross	null	O	VBD
mark	null	O	NN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
400	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
subscriber	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
number	null	O	NN
cross	null	O	VBD
show	null	O	VBD
put	null	O	VBG
on	null	O	IN
track	null	O	NN
reach	null	O	VB
goal	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
customer	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
500	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
of	null	ORGANIZATION	IN
Regulatory	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
on	null	O	IN
post	null	O	VBD
figure	null	O	NNS
website	null	O	NN
add	null	O	VBN
subscriber	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
11.90	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
of	null	ORGANIZATION	IN
Regulatory	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
on	null	O	IN
post	null	O	VBD
figure	null	O	NNS
website	null	O	NN
add	null	O	VBN
compare	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
15.64	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
base	null	O	NN
take	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
million	null	NUMBER	CD
403.66	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
market	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBP
reach	null	O	VBN
target	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
user	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
500	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
have	null	O	VBZ
people	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
1.2	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
lose	null	O	VBZ
hectare	null	O	NNS
equivalent	null	O	JJ
to	null	O	TO
size	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
capital	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
20	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
plant	null	O	VBN
tree	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
537	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Programme	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
accord	null	O	VBG
plant	null	O	VBN
tree	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
537	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Treasury	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
pump	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
30	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
receive	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
8.8	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
from	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
33.3	null	MONEY	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
from	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
33.3	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
history	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
case	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
one	null	NUMBER	CD
in	null	O	IN
list	null	O	VBD
asset	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
82.3	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
history	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
case	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
one	null	NUMBER	CD
in	null	O	IN
list	null	O	VBD
asset	null	O	NNS
debt	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
172.8	null	NUMBER	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
reside	null	O	VBG
Ecuadorans	null	MISC	NNPS
of	null	O	IN
number	null	O	NN
large	null	O	JJ
at	null	O	IN
around	null	O	IN
800,000	null	NUMBER	CD
russian	null	MISC	JJ
bank	null	O	NNS
need	null	O	VBP
capital	null	O	NN
dlr	null	O	NNS
bln	null	O	NN
40	null	NUMBER	CD
russian	null	MISC	JJ
bank	null	O	NNS
need	null	O	VBP
say	null	O	VBD
agency	null	O	NN
MOSCOW	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
need	null	O	VBP
total	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
40	null	MONEY	CD
russian	null	LOCATION	JJ
bank	null	O	NNS
need	null	O	VBP
June	null	DATE	NNP
MOSCOW	null	LOCATION	NNP
agency	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
need	null	O	VBP
capital	null	O	NN
dlr	null	O	NNS
bln	null	O	NN
40	null	NUMBER	CD
russian	null	LOCATION	JJ
bank	null	O	NNS
need	null	O	VBP
total	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
40	null	MONEY	CD
russian	null	LOCATION	JJ
bank	null	O	NNS
for	null	O	IN
sum	null	O	NN
amount	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
23.6	null	MONEY	CD
russian	null	LOCATION	JJ
bank	null	O	NNS
for	null	O	IN
sum	null	O	NN
amount	null	O	VBD
amount	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
15.6	null	MONEY	CD
russian	null	MISC	JJ
bank	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
need	null	O	NNS
meet	null	O	VBN
that	null	O	IN
sector	null	O	NN
by	null	O	IN
require	null	O	VBN
recapitalisation	null	O	NN
dollar	null	MONEY	NN
billion	null	MONEY	CD
40	null	MONEY	CD
dutch	null	MISC	JJ
mp	null	O	NNS
elect	null	O	VB
voter	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
13	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
envoy	null	O	NN
due	null	O	JJ
on	null	O	IN
Wednesday	null	DATE	NNP
assess	null	O	VB
situation	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.4	null	NUMBER	CD
Afghanistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
envoy	null	O	NN
due	null	O	JJ
on	null	O	IN
Wednesday	null	DATE	NNP
assess	null	O	VB
situation	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.4	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
Afghanistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
envoy	null	O	NN
due	null	O	JJ
on	null	O	IN
Wednesday	null	DATE	NNP
assess	null	O	VB
situation	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.4	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
due	null	O	JJ
on	null	O	IN
Wednesday	null	DATE	NNP
assess	null	O	VB
situation	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.4	null	NUMBER	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
worth	null	O	JJ
lose	null	O	VBD
on	null	O	IN
volume	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
share	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
3.87	null	NUMBER	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
2.68	null	NUMBER	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
billion	null	MONEY	CD
1.86	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
worth	null	O	JJ
lose	null	O	VBD
on	null	O	IN
volume	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
share	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
3.87	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
2.68	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
billion	null	MONEY	CD
1.86	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
market	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
rule	null	O	VBZ
Google	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
merge	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
47.5	null	MONEY	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
boost	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
move	null	O	NN
worth	null	O	NN
billion	null	MONEY	CD
85	null	MONEY	CD
german	null	MISC	JJ
french	null	MISC	JJ
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
boost	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
move	null	O	NN
worth	null	O	NN
billion	null	MONEY	CD
85	null	MONEY	CD
spanish	null	LOCATION	JJ
french	null	MISC	JJ
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
boost	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
move	null	O	NN
worth	null	O	NN
billion	null	MONEY	CD
85	null	MONEY	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
researcher	null	O	NNS
by	null	O	IN
study	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
accord	null	O	VBG
blind	null	O	JJ
million	null	NUMBER	CD
include	null	O	VBG
eyesight	null	O	NN
from	null	O	IN
suffer	null	O	VBP
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
158	null	NUMBER	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
researcher	null	O	NNS
by	null	O	IN
study	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
accord	null	O	VBG
blind	null	O	JJ
million	null	NUMBER	CD
8.7	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Africa	null	LOCATION	NNP
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
researcher	null	O	NNS
by	null	O	IN
study	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
accord	null	O	VBG
blind	null	O	JJ
million	null	NUMBER	CD
include	null	O	VBG
eyesight	null	O	NN
from	null	O	IN
suffer	null	O	VBP
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
158	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Africa	null	LOCATION	NNP
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
researcher	null	O	NNS
by	null	O	IN
study	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
accord	null	O	VBG
blind	null	O	JJ
million	null	NUMBER	CD
8.7	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
researcher	null	O	NNS
by	null	O	IN
study	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
accord	null	O	VBG
blind	null	O	JJ
million	null	NUMBER	CD
include	null	O	VBG
eyesight	null	O	NN
from	null	O	IN
suffer	null	O	VBP
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
158	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
researcher	null	O	NNS
by	null	O	IN
study	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
accord	null	O	VBG
blind	null	O	JJ
million	null	NUMBER	CD
8.7	null	NUMBER	CD
Israel	null	LOCATION	NNP
maintain	null	O	VBN
blockade	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
Gaza	null	LOCATION	NNP
home	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
1.5	null	NUMBER	CD
egyptian	null	LOCATION	JJ
resort	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
conference	null	O	NN
at	null	O	IN
pledge	null	O	VBD
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
4.5	null	MONEY	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
home	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
1.2	null	NUMBER	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
nation	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
46	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	O	NNP
sale	null	O	NNS
be	null	O	VBD
at	null	O	IN
vehicle	null	O	NNS
925,824	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
history	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
case	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
one	null	NUMBER	CD
in	null	O	IN
list	null	O	VBD
asset	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
82.3	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
history	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
case	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
one	null	NUMBER	CD
in	null	O	IN
list	null	O	VBD
asset	null	O	NNS
debt	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
172.8	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
official	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
30	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
official	null	O	NNS
pledge	null	O	VBD
on	null	O	IN
top	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
20	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
give	null	O	VB
provide	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
9.5	null	MONEY	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
government	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
9.5	null	MONEY	CD
Japan	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
that	null	O	DT
behind	null	O	IN
lag	null	O	VBN
relationship	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
ASEAN	null	LOCATION	NNP
market	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
600	null	NUMBER	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
Japan	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
that	null	O	DT
behind	null	O	IN
lag	null	O	VBN
relationship	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
ASEAN	null	LOCATION	NNP
market	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
600	null	NUMBER	CD
rwandan	null	MISC	JJ
genocide	null	O	NN
claim	null	O	VBD
life	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
Tutsis	null	MISC	NNPS
800,000	null	NUMBER	CD
south	null	MISC	JJ
soldier	null	O	NNS
600,000	null	NUMBER	CD
south	null	MISC	JJ
soldier	null	O	NNS
confront	null	O	VBG
from	null	O	IN
military	null	O	NN
1.1	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
troops	null	O	NNS
by	null	O	IN
back	null	O	VBN
soldier	null	O	NNS
600,000	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
troops	null	O	NNS
by	null	O	IN
back	null	O	VBN
soldier	null	O	NNS
confront	null	O	VBG
from	null	O	IN
military	null	O	NN
1.1	null	NUMBER	CD
North	null	O	NNP
military	null	O	NN
from	null	O	IN
confront	null	O	VBG
soldier	null	O	NNS
600,000	null	NUMBER	CD
North	null	O	NNP
military	null	O	NN
1.1	null	NUMBER	CD
Greenland	null	LOCATION	NNP
island	null	O	NN
cover	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
surface	null	O	NN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.1	null	NUMBER	CD
Greenland	null	LOCATION	NNP
receive	null	O	VBZ
subsidy	null	O	NNS
krone	null	MONEY	NN
billion	null	MONEY	CD
3.4	null	MONEY	CD
Greenland	null	LOCATION	NNP
receive	null	O	VBZ
subsidy	null	O	NNS
krone	null	MONEY	NN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
645	null	MONEY	CD
Denmark	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
subsidy	null	O	NNS
krone	null	MONEY	NN
billion	null	MONEY	CD
3.4	null	MONEY	CD
Denmark	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
subsidy	null	O	NNS
krone	null	MONEY	NN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
645	null	MONEY	CD
Greenland	null	LOCATION	NNP
island	null	O	NN
cover	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
surface	null	O	NN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.1	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
Survey	null	O	NNP
estimate	null	O	VBD
barrel	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
31.4	null	NUMBER	CD
Greenland	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
part	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
barrel	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
31.4	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Department	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
announce	null	O	VBD
leap	null	O	VBD
barrel	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.9	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Department	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
announce	null	O	VBD
leap	null	O	VBD
reach	null	O	VB
barrel	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
366	null	NUMBER	CD
American	null	MISC	NNP
inventory	null	O	NNS
leap	null	O	VBD
barrel	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.9	null	NUMBER	CD
American	null	MISC	NNP
inventory	null	O	NNS
reach	null	O	VB
barrel	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
366	null	NUMBER	CD
japanese	null	MISC	JJ
automaker	null	O	NN
sell	null	O	VBD
sell	null	O	VBZ
vehicle	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
9.369	null	NUMBER	CD
japanese	null	MISC	JJ
automaker	null	O	NN
sell	null	O	VBD
million	null	NUMBER	CD
9.366	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
loan	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
receive	null	O	VBZ
bring	null	O	VBG
to	null	O	TO
billion	null	MONEY	CD
19.4	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Congress	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
through	null	O	IN
work	null	O	VBG
package	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
top	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
announce	null	O	VBN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
110	null	MONEY	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
root	null	O	NN
help	null	O	VB
work	null	O	VBG
package	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
top	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
announce	null	O	VBN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
110	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
priority	null	O	NN
extremism	null	O	NN
root	null	O	NN
help	null	O	VB
work	null	O	VBG
package	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
top	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
announce	null	O	VBN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
110	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
54.78	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
7.02	null	NUMBER	CD
Taiwan	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
231.19	null	NUMBER	CD
Taiwan	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
billion	null	MONEY	CD
7.26	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
231.19	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
billion	null	MONEY	CD
7.26	null	MONEY	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
Boyle	null	PERSON	NNP
star	null	O	NN
view	null	O	VBN
time	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
100	null	NUMBER	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
sale	null	O	NNS
grow	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
unit	null	O	NNS
670,000	null	NUMBER	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
with	null	O	IN
turn	null	O	VBN
press	null	O	VBG
on	null	O	IN
safety	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
800	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
press	null	O	VBG
on	null	O	IN
safety	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
800	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
debt	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
invest	null	O	VBN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
800	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
report	null	O	VBD
tumble	null	O	VBN
barrel	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
5.4	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
tumble	null	O	VBN
barrel	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
5.4	null	NUMBER	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
be	null	O	VBP
in	null	O	IN
ASEAN	null	LOCATION	NNP
have	null	O	VBZ
product	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
trillion	null	MONEY	CD
1.3	null	MONEY	CD
Japan	null	LOCATION	NNP
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
be	null	O	VBP
in	null	O	IN
ASEAN	null	LOCATION	NNP
have	null	O	VBZ
product	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
trillion	null	MONEY	CD
1.3	null	MONEY	CD
Ukraine	null	LOCATION	NNP
need	null	O	VBZ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
500	null	MONEY	CD
Kuwait	null	LOCATION	NNP
receive	null	O	VBN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
13	null	MONEY	CD
Kuwait	null	LOCATION	NNP
receive	null	O	VBN
unpaid	null	O	JJ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
25.5	null	MONEY	CD
Iraq	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
receive	null	O	VBN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
13	null	MONEY	CD
Iraq	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
receive	null	O	VBN
unpaid	null	O	JJ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
25.5	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Treasury	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
obtain	null	O	VBN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
30	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
provide	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
30.1	null	MONEY	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
government	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
9.5	null	MONEY	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
as	null	O	IN
economy	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
energy	null	O	NN
produce	null	O	VBG
in	null	O	IN
invest	null	O	VBN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
36	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
lead	null	O	VBN
put	null	O	VBG
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
67	null	MONEY	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
lead	null	O	VBN
put	null	O	VBG
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
67	null	MONEY	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
buy	null	O	VBZ
say	null	O	VBD
pay	null	O	VBN
dollar	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
437.5	null	NUMBER	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
buy	null	O	VBZ
say	null	O	VBD
pay	null	O	VBN
dollar	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
302	null	NUMBER	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
firm	null	O	JJ
International	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
pay	null	O	VBN
dollar	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
437.5	null	NUMBER	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
firm	null	O	JJ
International	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
pay	null	O	VBN
dollar	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
302	null	NUMBER	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
437.5	null	NUMBER	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
302	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
million	null	NUMBER	CD
dollar	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
437.5	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
million	null	NUMBER	CD
302	null	NUMBER	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
vehicle	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
one	null	NUMBER	CD
Temasek	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
have	null	O	VBZ
portfolio	null	O	NN
worth	null	O	JJ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
185	null	MONEY	CD
Poland	null	LOCATION	NNP
have	null	O	VBZ
country	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
38	null	NUMBER	CD
Greenland	null	LOCATION	NNP
island	null	O	NN
cover	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
surface	null	O	NN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.1	null	NUMBER	CD
Egypt	null	LOCATION	NNP
one	null	NUMBER	CD
receive	null	O	VBZ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
1.5	null	MONEY	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
media	null	O	NNS
to	null	O	TO
accord	null	O	VBG
charge	null	O	VBN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
20	null	MONEY	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
media	null	O	NNS
to	null	O	TO
accord	null	O	VBG
charge	null	O	VBN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
15	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
bln	null	O	NN
30.1	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
bln	null	O	NN
get	null	O	VB
official	null	O	NNS
bln	null	O	NN
9.5	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
bln	null	O	NN
get	null	O	VB
official	null	O	NNS
receive	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
30.1	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
bln	null	O	NN
get	null	O	VB
official	null	O	NNS
receive	null	O	VB
from	null	O	IN
government	null	O	NN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
9.5	null	MONEY	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
bln	null	O	NN
official	null	O	NNS
get	null	O	VB
bln	null	O	NN
30.1	null	NUMBER	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
bln	null	O	NN
9.5	null	NUMBER	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
bln	null	O	NN
official	null	O	NNS
receive	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
30.1	null	MONEY	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
bln	null	O	NN
official	null	O	NNS
receive	null	O	VB
from	null	O	IN
government	null	O	NN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
9.5	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
official	null	O	NNS
get	null	O	VB
bln	null	O	NN
30.1	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
official	null	O	NNS
bln	null	O	NN
9.5	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
official	null	O	NNS
receive	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
30.1	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
official	null	O	NNS
receive	null	O	VB
from	null	O	IN
government	null	O	NN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
9.5	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
from	null	O	IN
receive	null	O	VB
official	null	O	NNS
get	null	O	VB
bln	null	O	NN
30.1	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
from	null	O	IN
receive	null	O	VB
official	null	O	NNS
bln	null	O	NN
9.5	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
from	null	O	IN
receive	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
30.1	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
9.5	null	MONEY	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
government	null	O	NN
from	null	O	IN
receive	null	O	VB
official	null	O	NNS
get	null	O	VB
bln	null	O	NN
30.1	null	NUMBER	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
government	null	O	NN
from	null	O	IN
receive	null	O	VB
official	null	O	NNS
bln	null	O	NN
9.5	null	NUMBER	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
government	null	O	NN
from	null	O	IN
receive	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
30.1	null	MONEY	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
9.5	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
official	null	O	NNS
say	null	O	VBD
protection	null	O	NN
under	null	O	IN
restructure	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
receive	null	O	VB
official	null	O	NNS
get	null	O	VB
bln	null	O	NN
30.1	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
official	null	O	NNS
say	null	O	VBD
protection	null	O	NN
under	null	O	IN
restructure	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
receive	null	O	VB
official	null	O	NNS
bln	null	O	NN
9.5	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
official	null	O	NNS
say	null	O	VBD
protection	null	O	NN
under	null	O	IN
restructure	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
receive	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
30.1	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
official	null	O	NNS
say	null	O	VBD
protection	null	O	NN
under	null	O	IN
restructure	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
receive	null	O	VB
from	null	O	IN
government	null	O	NN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
9.5	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
examine	null	O	VB
meet	null	O	VB
some	null	O	DT
of	null	O	IN
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.4	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
send	null	O	VBG
examine	null	O	VB
meet	null	O	VB
some	null	O	DT
of	null	O	IN
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.4	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
announce	null	O	VBN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
110	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Congress	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
through	null	O	IN
work	null	O	VBG
package	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
top	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
announce	null	O	VBN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
110	null	MONEY	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
root	null	O	NN
help	null	O	VB
work	null	O	VBG
package	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
top	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
announce	null	O	VBN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
110	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
priority	null	O	NN
extremism	null	O	NN
root	null	O	NN
help	null	O	VB
work	null	O	VBG
package	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
top	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
announce	null	O	VBN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
110	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
take	null	O	VBD
in	null	O	IN
exchange	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
provide	null	O	VBG
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
50	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
job	null	O	NNS
cut	null	O	VB
close	null	O	VB
plan	null	O	NNS
include	null	O	VBZ
restructuring	null	O	NN
finance	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
provide	null	O	VBG
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
50	null	MONEY	CD
Venezuela	null	LOCATION	NNP
prove	null	O	VBN
reserve	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
barrel	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
99	null	NUMBER	CD
Cambodia	null	LOCATION	NNP
deny	null	O	VBZ
reject	null	O	VBD
statement	null	O	NN
cost	null	O	VBZ
to	null	O	TO
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
500	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
diplomat	null	O	NN
Penh	null	LOCATION	NNP
reject	null	O	VBD
statement	null	O	NN
cost	null	O	VBZ
to	null	O	TO
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
500	null	MONEY	CD
Cambodia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Tuesday	null	DATE	NNP
Penh	null	LOCATION	NNP
reject	null	O	VBD
statement	null	O	NN
cost	null	O	VBZ
to	null	O	TO
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
500	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
diplomat	null	O	NN
statement	null	O	NN
cost	null	O	VBZ
to	null	O	TO
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
500	null	MONEY	CD
Cambodia	null	LOCATION	NNP
cabinet	null	O	NN
issue	null	O	VBD
say	null	O	VBG
regrettable	null	O	JJ
figure	null	O	NN
dollar	null	MONEY	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
500	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
report	null	O	VBD
tumble	null	O	VBN
barrel	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
5.4	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
tumble	null	O	VBN
barrel	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
5.4	null	NUMBER	CD
Kuwait	null	LOCATION	NNP
receive	null	O	VBN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
13	null	MONEY	CD
Kuwait	null	LOCATION	NNP
receive	null	O	VBN
unpaid	null	O	JJ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
25.5	null	MONEY	CD
Iraq	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
receive	null	O	VBN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
13	null	MONEY	CD
Iraq	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
receive	null	O	VBN
unpaid	null	O	JJ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
25.5	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
from	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
33.3	null	MONEY	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
from	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
33.3	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
history	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
case	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
one	null	NUMBER	CD
in	null	O	IN
list	null	O	VBD
asset	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
82.3	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
history	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
case	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
one	null	NUMBER	CD
in	null	O	IN
list	null	O	VBD
asset	null	O	NNS
debt	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
172.8	null	NUMBER	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
worth	null	O	JJ
lose	null	O	VBD
on	null	O	IN
volume	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
share	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
3.87	null	NUMBER	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
2.68	null	NUMBER	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
billion	null	MONEY	CD
1.86	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
worth	null	O	JJ
lose	null	O	VBD
on	null	O	IN
volume	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
share	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
3.87	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
2.68	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
billion	null	MONEY	CD
1.86	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
earnings	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
12.7	null	MONEY	CD
Greenland	null	LOCATION	NNP
island	null	O	NN
cover	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
surface	null	O	NN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.1	null	NUMBER	CD
Greenland	null	LOCATION	NNP
receive	null	O	VBZ
subsidy	null	O	NNS
krone	null	MONEY	NN
billion	null	MONEY	CD
3.4	null	MONEY	CD
Greenland	null	LOCATION	NNP
receive	null	O	VBZ
subsidy	null	O	NNS
krone	null	MONEY	NN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
645	null	MONEY	CD
Denmark	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
subsidy	null	O	NNS
krone	null	MONEY	NN
billion	null	MONEY	CD
3.4	null	MONEY	CD
Denmark	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
subsidy	null	O	NNS
krone	null	MONEY	NN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
645	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
examine	null	O	VB
meet	null	O	VB
some	null	O	DT
of	null	O	IN
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.4	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
send	null	O	VBG
examine	null	O	VB
meet	null	O	VB
some	null	O	DT
of	null	O	IN
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.4	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.3	null	NUMBER	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
appearance	null	O	NN
course	null	O	NN
at	null	O	IN
play	null	O	VB
pay	null	O	VBN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.3	null	NUMBER	CD
south	null	MISC	JJ
troops	null	O	NNS
600,000	null	NUMBER	CD
south	null	MISC	JJ
troops	null	O	NNS
confront	null	O	VBG
threat	null	O	NN
from	null	O	IN
military	null	O	NN
1.1	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
troops	null	O	NNS
by	null	O	IN
back	null	O	VBN
troops	null	O	NNS
600,000	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
troops	null	O	NNS
by	null	O	IN
back	null	O	VBN
troops	null	O	NNS
confront	null	O	VBG
threat	null	O	NN
from	null	O	IN
military	null	O	NN
1.1	null	NUMBER	CD
North	null	O	NNP
military	null	O	NN
from	null	O	IN
threat	null	O	NN
confront	null	O	VBG
troops	null	O	NNS
600,000	null	NUMBER	CD
North	null	O	NNP
military	null	O	NN
1.1	null	NUMBER	CD
Poland	null	LOCATION	NNP
announce	null	O	VBD
sale	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
total	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
zloty	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
364	null	MONEY	CD
Poland	null	LOCATION	NNP
announce	null	O	VBD
sale	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
total	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
zloty	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
115	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Trust	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
sale	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
total	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
zloty	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
364	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Trust	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
sale	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
total	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
zloty	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
115	null	MONEY	CD
Greenland	null	LOCATION	NNP
receive	null	O	VBZ
subsidy	null	O	NNS
krone	null	MONEY	NN
billion	null	MONEY	CD
3.4	null	MONEY	CD
Greenland	null	LOCATION	NNP
receive	null	O	VBZ
subsidy	null	O	NNS
krone	null	MONEY	NN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
645	null	MONEY	CD
Denmark	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
subsidy	null	O	NNS
krone	null	MONEY	NN
billion	null	MONEY	CD
3.4	null	MONEY	CD
Denmark	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
subsidy	null	O	NNS
krone	null	MONEY	NN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
645	null	MONEY	CD
Greenland	null	LOCATION	NNP
island	null	O	NN
cover	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
surface	null	O	NN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.1	null	NUMBER	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
boost	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
move	null	O	NN
buy	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
85	null	MONEY	CD
german	null	MISC	JJ
french	null	MISC	JJ
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
boost	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
move	null	O	NN
buy	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
85	null	MONEY	CD
spanish	null	LOCATION	JJ
french	null	MISC	JJ
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
boost	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
move	null	O	NN
buy	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
85	null	MONEY	CD
Somalia	null	LOCATION	NNP
have	null	O	VBN
country	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
10	null	NUMBER	CD
Ukraine	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
krona	null	MONEY	NNS
lose	null	O	VBD
suffer	null	O	VBD
loss	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
krona	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
2.4	null	NUMBER	CD
Ukraine	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
krona	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
6.8	null	MONEY	CD
Ukraine	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
4.2	null	NUMBER	CD
Ukraine	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
1.4	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
discuss	null	O	VB
sale	null	O	NNS
include	null	O	VBG
request	null	O	NN
buy	null	O	VB
worth	null	O	JJ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
15.2	null	MONEY	CD
Israel	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
sale	null	O	NNS
include	null	O	VBG
request	null	O	NN
buy	null	O	VB
worth	null	O	JJ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
15.2	null	MONEY	CD
israeli	null	MISC	JJ
official	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
expect	null	O	VBN
discuss	null	O	VB
sale	null	O	NNS
include	null	O	VBG
request	null	O	NN
buy	null	O	VB
worth	null	O	JJ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
15.2	null	MONEY	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
NOL	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBZ
plan	null	O	VBG
issue	null	O	NN
mln	null	O	NN
993	null	NUMBER	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
Lines	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
announce	null	O	VBD
issue	null	O	NN
mln	null	O	NN
993	null	NUMBER	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
Lines	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
announce	null	O	VBD
issue	null	O	NN
mln	null	O	NN
993	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
raise	null	O	VB
plan	null	O	NNS
announce	null	O	VBD
issue	null	O	NN
mln	null	O	NN
993	null	NUMBER	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
1.43	null	NUMBER	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
million	null	NUMBER	CD
993	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
1.43	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
million	null	NUMBER	CD
993	null	NUMBER	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
at	null	O	IN
issue	null	O	VBN
share	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
1.1	null	NUMBER	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
leader	null	O	NNS
reassure	null	O	VB
safe	null	O	JJ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
800	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
asset	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
800	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
deficit	null	O	NN
despite	null	O	IN
safe	null	O	JJ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
800	null	MONEY	CD
China	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Daily	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
be	null	O	VBZ
reassure	null	O	VB
safe	null	O	JJ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
800	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
visit	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
Coverage	null	O	NNP
who	null	O	WP
assess	null	O	VB
of	null	O	IN
people	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.4	null	NUMBER	CD
Latvia	null	LOCATION	NNP
warn	null	O	VBD
nation	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.3	null	NUMBER	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
try	null	O	VBG
give	null	O	VBZ
purchase	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
800	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
asset	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
800	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
market	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
rule	null	O	VBZ
Google	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
merge	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
47.5	null	MONEY	CD
Croatia	null	LOCATION	NNP
visit	null	O	VBD
people	null	O	NNS
834,984	null	NUMBER	CD
Croatia	null	LOCATION	NNP
register	null	O	VBD
stay	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.3	null	NUMBER	CD
Somalia	null	LOCATION	NNP
have	null	O	VBN
country	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
10	null	NUMBER	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
double	null	O	VBN
announce	null	O	VBD
spend	null	O	VB
yuan	null	MONEY	NN
billion	null	MONEY	CD
480	null	MONEY	CD
Macau	null	LOCATION	NNP
Macau	null	LOCATION	NNP
on	null	O	IN
fact	null	O	NNS
list	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
fact	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
Macau	null	LOCATION	NNP
open	null	O	VBD
region	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
population	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
546,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Macau	null	LOCATION	NNP
on	null	O	IN
fact	null	O	NNS
list	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
fact	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
Macau	null	LOCATION	NNP
open	null	O	VBD
region	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
population	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
546,000	null	NUMBER	CD
chinese	null	LOCATION	JJ
territory	null	O	NN
about	null	O	IN
fact	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
Macau	null	LOCATION	NNP
open	null	O	VBD
region	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
population	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
546,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Macau	null	LOCATION	NNP
open	null	O	VBD
region	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
population	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
546,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Macau	null	LOCATION	NNP
region	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
population	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
546,000	null	NUMBER	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
region	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
population	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
546,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Arabia	null	LOCATION	NNP
into	null	O	IN
fly	null	O	VBD
give	null	O	VB
much	null	O	JJ
speech	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
Muslims	null	MISC	NNPS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
1.5	null	NUMBER	CD
Thailand	null	LOCATION	NNP
Court	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
rule	null	O	VBD
legal	null	O	JJ
plan	null	O	NN
approve	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
11.8	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
support	null	O	VB
military	null	O	NN
against	null	O	IN
threat	null	O	NN
from	null	O	IN
force	null	O	NNS
1.1	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
station	null	O	NNS
support	null	O	VB
military	null	O	NN
against	null	O	IN
threat	null	O	NN
from	null	O	IN
force	null	O	NNS
1.1	null	NUMBER	CD
North	null	O	NNP
force	null	O	NNS
1.1	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
Obama	null	PERSON	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
want	null	O	VBZ
with	null	O	IN
world	null	O	NN
Muslims	null	MISC	NNPS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
1.5	null	NUMBER	CD
Yemen	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
population	null	O	NN
estimate	null	O	VBN
at	null	O	IN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
24	null	NUMBER	CD
north	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
live	null	O	VBP
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
of	null	O	IN
population	null	O	NN
estimate	null	O	VBN
at	null	O	IN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
24	null	NUMBER	CD
north	null	O	NN
have	null	O	VBZ
option	null	O	NN
live	null	O	VBP
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
of	null	O	IN
population	null	O	NN
estimate	null	O	VBN
at	null	O	IN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
24	null	NUMBER	CD
south	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
be	null	O	VBP
fact	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
refer	null	O	VBG
say	null	O	VBD
option	null	O	NN
live	null	O	VBP
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
of	null	O	IN
population	null	O	NN
estimate	null	O	VBN
at	null	O	IN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
24	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
90.63	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
11.62	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
Department	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
announce	null	O	VBD
leap	null	O	VBD
barrel	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.9	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
Department	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
announce	null	O	VBD
leap	null	O	VBD
reach	null	O	VB
barrel	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
366	null	NUMBER	CD
American	null	MISC	NNP
inventory	null	O	NNS
leap	null	O	VBD
barrel	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.9	null	NUMBER	CD
American	null	MISC	NNP
inventory	null	O	NNS
reach	null	O	VB
barrel	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
366	null	NUMBER	CD
Iran	null	LOCATION	NNP
sign	null	O	NN
Iran	null	LOCATION	NNP
5	null	NUMBER	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
sign	null	O	NN
Iran	null	LOCATION	NNP
5	null	NUMBER	CD
Iran	null	LOCATION	NNP
5	null	NUMBER	CD
China	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Corporation	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
develop	null	O	VB
with	null	O	IN
sign	null	O	VBD
sign	null	O	NN
Iran	null	LOCATION	NNP
5	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	O	NNP
field	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
develop	null	O	VB
with	null	O	IN
sign	null	O	VBD
sign	null	O	NN
Iran	null	LOCATION	NNP
5	null	NUMBER	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
population	null	O	NN
hit	null	O	VBZ
MADRID	null	LOCATION	NNP
million	null	NUMBER	CD
5.6	null	NUMBER	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
population	null	O	NN
hit	null	O	VBZ
rise	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
million	null	NUMBER	CD
5.6	null	NUMBER	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
live	null	O	VBG
June	null	DATE	NNP
rise	null	O	VBD
hit	null	O	VBZ
MADRID	null	LOCATION	NNP
million	null	NUMBER	CD
5.6	null	NUMBER	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
live	null	O	VBG
June	null	DATE	NNP
rise	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
million	null	NUMBER	CD
5.6	null	NUMBER	CD
Romania	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
come	null	O	VBG
with	null	O	IN
hit	null	O	VBZ
MADRID	null	LOCATION	NNP
million	null	NUMBER	CD
5.6	null	NUMBER	CD
Romania	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
come	null	O	VBG
with	null	O	IN
hit	null	O	VBZ
rise	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
million	null	NUMBER	CD
5.6	null	NUMBER	CD
Morocco	null	LOCATION	NNP
Romania	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
come	null	O	VBG
with	null	O	IN
hit	null	O	VBZ
MADRID	null	LOCATION	NNP
million	null	NUMBER	CD
5.6	null	NUMBER	CD
Morocco	null	LOCATION	NNP
Romania	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
come	null	O	VBG
with	null	O	IN
hit	null	O	VBZ
rise	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
million	null	NUMBER	CD
5.6	null	NUMBER	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
Romania	null	LOCATION	NNP
