Germany	null	LOCATION	NNP
have	null	O	VBZ
with	null	O	IN
area	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
km	null	O	NN
357,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Chinese	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Reserve	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
hectare	null	O	NNS
43,300	null	NUMBER	CD
Greenland	null	LOCATION	NNP
island	null	O	NN
cover	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
surface	null	O	NN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.1	null	NUMBER	CD
Greenland	null	LOCATION	NNP
island	null	O	NN
cover	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
surface	null	O	NN
mile	null	O	NN
840,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
lose	null	O	VBZ
hectare	null	O	NNS
600,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
lose	null	O	VBZ
hectare	null	O	NNS
acre	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
1.5	null	NUMBER	CD
Greenland	null	LOCATION	NNP
island	null	O	NN
cover	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
surface	null	O	NN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.1	null	NUMBER	CD
Greenland	null	LOCATION	NNP
island	null	O	NN
cover	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
surface	null	O	NN
mile	null	O	NN
840,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Greenland	null	LOCATION	NNP
island	null	O	NN
cover	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
surface	null	O	NN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.1	null	NUMBER	CD
Greenland	null	LOCATION	NNP
island	null	O	NN
cover	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
surface	null	O	NN
mile	null	O	NN
840,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Namibia	null	LOCATION	NNP
start	null	O	VBD
aim	null	O	VBG
acquire	null	O	VB
hectare	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
15	null	MONEY	CD
Namibia	null	LOCATION	NNP
start	null	O	VBD
aim	null	O	VBG
acquire	null	O	VB
hectare	null	MONEY	NNS
acre	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
37	null	NUMBER	CD
Greenland	null	LOCATION	NNP
island	null	O	NN
cover	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
surface	null	O	NN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.1	null	NUMBER	CD
Greenland	null	LOCATION	NNP
island	null	O	NN
cover	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
surface	null	O	NN
mile	null	O	NN
840,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Greenland	null	LOCATION	NNP
island	null	O	NN
cover	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
surface	null	O	NN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.1	null	NUMBER	CD
Greenland	null	LOCATION	NNP
island	null	O	NN
cover	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
surface	null	O	NN
mile	null	O	NN
840,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Greenland	null	LOCATION	NNP
island	null	O	NN
cover	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
surface	null	O	NN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.1	null	NUMBER	CD
Greenland	null	LOCATION	NNP
island	null	O	NN
cover	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
surface	null	O	NN
mile	null	O	NN
840,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Macau	null	LOCATION	NNP
sit	null	O	VBZ
Covering	null	O	NNP
kilometre	null	O	NNS
29	null	NUMBER	CD
Macau	null	LOCATION	NNP
sit	null	O	VBZ
Covering	null	O	NNP
kilometre	null	O	NNS
mile	null	O	NNS
11	null	NUMBER	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
bank	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
sit	null	O	VBZ
Covering	null	O	NNP
kilometre	null	O	NNS
29	null	NUMBER	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
bank	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
sit	null	O	VBZ
Covering	null	O	NNP
kilometre	null	O	NNS
mile	null	O	NNS
11	null	NUMBER	CD
Indonesia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Borneo	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
forest	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
hectare	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
3.3	null	NUMBER	CD
Indonesia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Borneo	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
forest	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
hectare	null	O	NNS
acre	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
8.25	null	NUMBER	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
produce	null	O	VB
manage	null	O	VBD
relaunch	null	O	VB
use	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
hectar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
20	null	MONEY	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBZ
occupy	null	O	VBZ
kilometre	null	O	NNS
38,000	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBZ
occupy	null	O	VBZ
kilometre	null	O	NNS
mile	null	O	NNS
14,700	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBZ
occupy	null	O	VBZ
claim	null	O	VBZ
whole	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
state	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
Pradesh	null	LOCATION	NNP
kilometre	null	O	NNS
90,000	null	NUMBER	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
occupy	null	O	VBZ
kilometre	null	O	NNS
38,000	null	NUMBER	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
occupy	null	O	VBZ
kilometre	null	O	NNS
mile	null	O	NNS
14,700	null	NUMBER	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
occupy	null	O	VBZ
claim	null	O	VBZ
whole	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
state	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
Pradesh	null	LOCATION	NNP
kilometre	null	O	NNS
90,000	null	NUMBER	CD
indian	null	MISC	JJ
state	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
whole	null	O	NN
claim	null	O	VBZ
occupy	null	O	VBZ
kilometre	null	O	NNS
38,000	null	NUMBER	CD
indian	null	MISC	JJ
state	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
whole	null	O	NN
claim	null	O	VBZ
occupy	null	O	VBZ
kilometre	null	O	NNS
mile	null	O	NNS
14,700	null	NUMBER	CD
indian	null	MISC	JJ
state	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
Pradesh	null	LOCATION	NNP
kilometre	null	O	NNS
90,000	null	NUMBER	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
overseas	null	O	JJ
to	null	O	TO
thanks	null	O	NNS
have	null	O	VBZ
zone	null	O	NN
kilometre	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
25	null	NUMBER	CD
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
fact	null	O	NNS
about	null	O	IN
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
go	null	O	VBZ
to	null	O	TO
poll	null	O	NNS
at	null	O	IN
kilometre	null	O	NNS
10,452	null	NUMBER	CD
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
fact	null	O	NNS
about	null	O	IN
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
go	null	O	VBZ
to	null	O	TO
poll	null	O	NNS
at	null	O	IN
kilometre	null	O	NNS
one	null	NUMBER	CD
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
mile	null	O	NNS
4,036	null	NUMBER	CD
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
go	null	O	VBZ
to	null	O	TO
poll	null	O	NNS
at	null	O	IN
kilometre	null	O	NNS
10,452	null	NUMBER	CD
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
go	null	O	VBZ
to	null	O	TO
poll	null	O	NNS
at	null	O	IN
kilometre	null	O	NNS
one	null	NUMBER	CD
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
mile	null	O	NNS
4,036	null	NUMBER	CD
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
one	null	NUMBER	CD
kilometre	null	O	NNS
10,452	null	NUMBER	CD
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
mile	null	O	NNS
4,036	null	NUMBER	CD
Cyprus	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
island	null	O	NN
than	null	O	IN
larger	null	O	JJR
to	null	O	TO
poll	null	O	NNS
at	null	O	IN
kilometre	null	O	NNS
10,452	null	NUMBER	CD
Cyprus	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
island	null	O	NN
than	null	O	IN
larger	null	O	JJR
to	null	O	TO
poll	null	O	NNS
at	null	O	IN
kilometre	null	O	NNS
one	null	NUMBER	CD
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
mile	null	O	NNS
4,036	null	NUMBER	CD
Philippines	null	LOCATION	NNPS
in	null	O	IN
affect	null	O	VBN
hectare	null	O	NNS
400,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Philippines	null	LOCATION	NNPS
in	null	O	IN
affect	null	O	VBN
hectare	null	O	NNS
acre	null	O	NNS
988,386	null	NUMBER	CD
Philippines	null	LOCATION	NNPS
in	null	O	IN
affect	null	O	VBN
flood	null	O	NN
hectare	null	O	NNS
370,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Vietnam	null	LOCATION	NNP
for	null	O	IN
product	null	O	NN
plant	null	O	VBN
about	null	O	IN
hectare	null	O	NNS
70,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Vietnam	null	LOCATION	NNP
for	null	O	IN
product	null	O	NN
plant	null	O	VBN
about	null	O	IN
hectare	null	O	NNS
acre	null	O	NNS
173,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Vietnam	null	LOCATION	NNP
for	null	O	IN
product	null	O	NN
bring	null	O	VBG
to	null	O	TO
hectare	null	O	NNS
650,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Indonesia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Borneo	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
forest	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
hectare	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
3.3	null	NUMBER	CD
Indonesia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Borneo	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
forest	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
hectare	null	O	NNS
acre	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
8.25	null	NUMBER	CD
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
fact	null	O	NNS
hold	null	O	VBZ
on	null	O	IN
June	null	DATE	NNP
one	null	NUMBER	CD
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
mile	null	O	NNS
at	null	O	IN
kilometre	null	O	NNS
10,452	null	NUMBER	CD
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
fact	null	O	NNS
hold	null	O	VBZ
on	null	O	IN
June	null	DATE	NNP
one	null	NUMBER	CD
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
mile	null	O	NNS
4,036	null	NUMBER	CD
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
about	null	O	IN
fact	null	O	NNS
hold	null	O	VBZ
on	null	O	IN
June	null	DATE	NNP
one	null	NUMBER	CD
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
mile	null	O	NNS
at	null	O	IN
kilometre	null	O	NNS
10,452	null	NUMBER	CD
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
about	null	O	IN
fact	null	O	NNS
hold	null	O	VBZ
on	null	O	IN
June	null	DATE	NNP
one	null	NUMBER	CD
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
mile	null	O	NNS
4,036	null	NUMBER	CD
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
mile	null	O	NNS
at	null	O	IN
kilometre	null	O	NNS
10,452	null	NUMBER	CD
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
mile	null	O	NNS
4,036	null	NUMBER	CD
Cyprus	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
island	null	O	NN
than	null	O	IN
larger	null	O	JJR
on	null	O	IN
June	null	DATE	NNP
one	null	NUMBER	CD
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
mile	null	O	NNS
at	null	O	IN
kilometre	null	O	NNS
10,452	null	NUMBER	CD
Cyprus	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
island	null	O	NN
than	null	O	IN
larger	null	O	JJR
on	null	O	IN
June	null	DATE	NNP
one	null	NUMBER	CD
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
mile	null	O	NNS
4,036	null	NUMBER	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
begin	null	O	VB
cultivation	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
hectare	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
20	null	MONEY	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
begin	null	O	VB
cultivation	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
hectare	null	MONEY	NNS
acre	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
49.5	null	NUMBER	CD
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
hold	null	O	VBG
at	null	O	IN
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
kilometre	null	O	NNS
10,452	null	NUMBER	CD
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
hold	null	O	VBG
at	null	O	IN
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
kilometre	null	O	NNS
mile	null	O	NNS
4,036	null	NUMBER	CD
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
about	null	O	IN
fact	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
hold	null	O	VBG
at	null	O	IN
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
kilometre	null	O	NNS
10,452	null	NUMBER	CD
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
about	null	O	IN
fact	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
hold	null	O	VBG
at	null	O	IN
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
kilometre	null	O	NNS
mile	null	O	NNS
4,036	null	NUMBER	CD
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
kilometre	null	O	NNS
10,452	null	NUMBER	CD
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
kilometre	null	O	NNS
mile	null	O	NNS
4,036	null	NUMBER	CD
Cyprus	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
island	null	O	NN
than	null	O	IN
larger	null	O	JJR
one	null	NUMBER	CD
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
hold	null	O	VBG
at	null	O	IN
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
kilometre	null	O	NNS
10,452	null	NUMBER	CD
Cyprus	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
island	null	O	NN
than	null	O	IN
larger	null	O	JJR
one	null	NUMBER	CD
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
hold	null	O	VBG
at	null	O	IN
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
kilometre	null	O	NNS
mile	null	O	NNS
4,036	null	NUMBER	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
quarter	null	DURATION	NNS
land	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
hectare	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
24	null	MONEY	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
quarter	null	DURATION	NNS
land	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
hectare	null	MONEY	NNS
acre	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
59.3	null	NUMBER	CD
Russian	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Institute	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
head	null	O	NN
Rylko	null	PERSON	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
lose	null	O	VBN
hectare	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
24	null	MONEY	CD
Russian	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Institute	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
head	null	O	NN
Rylko	null	PERSON	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
lose	null	O	VBN
hectare	null	MONEY	NNS
acre	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
59.3	null	NUMBER	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
prepare	null	O	VBG
cultivation	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
hectare	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
20	null	NUMBER	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
begin	null	O	VB
cultivation	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
hectare	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
20	null	MONEY	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
begin	null	O	VB
cultivation	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
hectare	null	MONEY	NNS
acre	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
49.5	null	NUMBER	CD
Iran	null	LOCATION	NNP
time	null	O	NNS
with	null	O	IN
area	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
kilometre	null	O	NNS
1,648,195	null	NUMBER	CD
Iran	null	LOCATION	NNP
time	null	O	NNS
with	null	O	IN
area	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
kilometre	null	O	NNS
mile	null	O	NNS
659,278	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
state	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
size	null	O	NN
time	null	O	NNS
with	null	O	IN
area	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
kilometre	null	O	NNS
1,648,195	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
state	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
size	null	O	NN
time	null	O	NNS
with	null	O	IN
area	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
kilometre	null	O	NNS
mile	null	O	NNS
659,278	null	NUMBER	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
as	null	O	IN
big	null	O	JJ
time	null	O	NNS
time	null	O	NNS
with	null	O	IN
area	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
kilometre	null	O	NNS
1,648,195	null	NUMBER	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
as	null	O	IN
big	null	O	JJ
time	null	O	NNS
time	null	O	NNS
with	null	O	IN
area	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
kilometre	null	O	NNS
mile	null	O	NNS
659,278	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
firm	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
consider	null	O	VBN
Block	null	O	NNP
located	null	O	JJ
cover	null	O	VBZ
kilometer	null	O	NNS
8,100	null	NUMBER	CD
Iran	null	LOCATION	NNP
time	null	O	NNS
with	null	O	IN
area	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
kilometre	null	O	NNS
1,648,195	null	NUMBER	CD
Iran	null	LOCATION	NNP
time	null	O	NNS
with	null	O	IN
area	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
kilometre	null	O	NNS
mile	null	O	NNS
659,278	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
state	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
size	null	O	NN
time	null	O	NNS
with	null	O	IN
area	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
kilometre	null	O	NNS
1,648,195	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
state	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
size	null	O	NN
time	null	O	NNS
with	null	O	IN
area	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
kilometre	null	O	NNS
mile	null	O	NNS
659,278	null	NUMBER	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
as	null	O	IN
big	null	O	JJ
time	null	O	NNS
time	null	O	NNS
with	null	O	IN
area	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
kilometre	null	O	NNS
1,648,195	null	NUMBER	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
as	null	O	IN
big	null	O	JJ
time	null	O	NNS
time	null	O	NNS
with	null	O	IN
area	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
kilometre	null	O	NNS
mile	null	O	NNS
659,278	null	NUMBER	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
have	null	O	VBZ
hectare	null	O	NNS
3,300	null	NUMBER	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
have	null	O	VBZ
hectare	null	O	NNS
acre	null	O	NNS
8,154	null	NUMBER	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
family	null	O	NNS
share	null	O	NN
hectare	null	O	NNS
850	null	NUMBER	CD
brazilian	null	MISC	JJ
rainforest	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
swath	null	O	NNS
cut	null	O	VBN
at	null	O	IN
rate	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
hectare	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
1.8	null	NUMBER	CD
brazilian	null	MISC	JJ
rainforest	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
swath	null	O	NNS
cut	null	O	VBN
at	null	O	IN
rate	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
hectare	null	O	NNS
acre	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
4.4	null	NUMBER	CD
Kuwait	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
size	null	O	NN
hectare	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
1.8	null	NUMBER	CD
Kuwait	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
size	null	O	NN
hectare	null	O	NNS
acre	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
4.4	null	NUMBER	CD
Iran	null	LOCATION	NNP
time	null	O	NNS
with	null	O	IN
area	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
kilometre	null	O	NNS
1,648,195	null	NUMBER	CD
Iran	null	LOCATION	NNP
time	null	O	NNS
with	null	O	IN
area	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
kilometre	null	O	NNS
mile	null	O	NNS
659,278	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
state	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
size	null	O	NN
time	null	O	NNS
with	null	O	IN
area	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
kilometre	null	O	NNS
1,648,195	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
state	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
size	null	O	NN
time	null	O	NNS
with	null	O	IN
area	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
kilometre	null	O	NNS
mile	null	O	NNS
659,278	null	NUMBER	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
as	null	O	IN
big	null	O	JJ
time	null	O	NNS
time	null	O	NNS
with	null	O	IN
area	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
kilometre	null	O	NNS
1,648,195	null	NUMBER	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
as	null	O	IN
big	null	O	JJ
time	null	O	NNS
time	null	O	NNS
with	null	O	IN
area	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
kilometre	null	O	NNS
mile	null	O	NNS
659,278	null	NUMBER	CD
turkish	null	MISC	JJ
bomb	null	O	NNS
burn	null	O	VBP
burn	null	O	VBN
tract	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
forest	null	O	NN
more	null	O	JJR
than	null	O	IN
hectare	null	O	NNS
125	null	NUMBER	CD
turkish	null	MISC	JJ
bomb	null	O	NNS
burn	null	O	VBP
burn	null	O	VBN
tract	null	O	NNS
acre	null	O	NNS
300	null	NUMBER	CD
iraqi	null	LOCATION	JJ
forest	null	O	NN
more	null	O	JJR
than	null	O	IN
hectare	null	O	NNS
125	null	NUMBER	CD
iraqi	null	LOCATION	JJ
forest	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
tract	null	O	NNS
acre	null	O	NNS
300	null	NUMBER	CD
Iraq	null	LOCATION	NNP
Arbil	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
more	null	O	JJR
than	null	O	IN
hectare	null	O	NNS
125	null	NUMBER	CD
Iraq	null	LOCATION	NNP
Arbil	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
more	null	O	JJR
forest	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
tract	null	O	NNS
acre	null	O	NNS
300	null	NUMBER	CD
Iraq	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
forest	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
tract	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
forest	null	O	NN
more	null	O	JJR
than	null	O	IN
hectare	null	O	NNS
125	null	NUMBER	CD
Iraq	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
forest	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
tract	null	O	NNS
acre	null	O	NNS
300	null	NUMBER	CD
turkish	null	MISC	JJ
bombardment	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
burn	null	O	VBN
tract	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
forest	null	O	NN
more	null	O	JJR
than	null	O	IN
hectare	null	O	NNS
125	null	NUMBER	CD
turkish	null	MISC	JJ
bombardment	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
burn	null	O	VBN
tract	null	O	NNS
acre	null	O	NNS
300	null	NUMBER	CD
iraqi	null	ORGANIZATION	JJ
Kurdistan	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
official	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
burn	null	O	VBP
burn	null	O	VBN
tract	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
forest	null	O	NN
more	null	O	JJR
than	null	O	IN
hectare	null	O	NNS
125	null	NUMBER	CD
iraqi	null	ORGANIZATION	JJ
Kurdistan	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
official	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
burn	null	O	VBP
burn	null	O	VBN
tract	null	O	NNS
acre	null	O	NNS
300	null	NUMBER	CD
turkish	null	MISC	JJ
bombardment	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
result	null	O	NN
as	null	O	IN
burn	null	O	VBN
dhonam	null	O	NN
hectare	null	O	NNS
125	null	NUMBER	CD
turkish	null	MISC	JJ
bombardment	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
result	null	O	NN
as	null	O	IN
burn	null	O	VBN
dhonam	null	O	NN
hectare	null	O	NNS
kilometre	null	O	NNS
1.25	null	NUMBER	CD
Iran	null	LOCATION	NNP
time	null	O	NNS
with	null	O	IN
area	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
kilometre	null	O	NNS
1,648,195	null	NUMBER	CD
Iran	null	LOCATION	NNP
time	null	O	NNS
with	null	O	IN
area	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
kilometre	null	O	NNS
mile	null	O	NNS
659,278	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
state	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
size	null	O	NN
time	null	O	NNS
with	null	O	IN
area	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
kilometre	null	O	NNS
1,648,195	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
state	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
size	null	O	NN
time	null	O	NNS
with	null	O	IN
area	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
kilometre	null	O	NNS
mile	null	O	NNS
659,278	null	NUMBER	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
as	null	O	IN
big	null	O	JJ
time	null	O	NNS
time	null	O	NNS
with	null	O	IN
area	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
kilometre	null	O	NNS
1,648,195	null	NUMBER	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
as	null	O	IN
big	null	O	JJ
time	null	O	NNS
time	null	O	NNS
with	null	O	IN
area	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
kilometre	null	O	NNS
mile	null	O	NNS
659,278	null	NUMBER	CD
Uganda	null	LOCATION	NNP
ministry	null	O	NN
at	null	O	IN
Unit	null	O	NNP
to	null	O	TO
accord	null	O	VBG
cover	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
hectare	null	O	NNS
217	null	NUMBER	CD
Uganda	null	LOCATION	NNP
ministry	null	O	NN
at	null	O	IN
Unit	null	O	NNP
to	null	O	TO
accord	null	O	VBG
cover	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
hectare	null	O	NNS
acre	null	O	NNS
536	null	NUMBER	CD
Cyprus	null	LOCATION	NNP
launch	null	O	VBD
for	null	O	IN
block	null	O	NNS
cover	null	O	VBG
kilometre	null	O	NNS
51,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Cyprus	null	LOCATION	NNP
launch	null	O	VBD
for	null	O	IN
block	null	O	NNS
cover	null	O	VBG
kilometre	null	O	NNS
mile	null	O	NNS
20,400	null	NUMBER	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
LVMH	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
hand	null	O	VBG
after	null	O	IN
retire	null	O	VBD
Kenzo	null	PERSON	NNP
move	null	O	VBG
to	null	O	TO
flat	null	O	JJ
square	null	O	NN
200	null	NUMBER	CD
Argentina	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
share	null	O	VBP
hectare	null	O	NNS
850	null	NUMBER	CD
dutch	null	MISC	JJ
Hermitage	null	MISC	NNP
house	null	O	VBN
await	null	O	VBG
at	null	O	IN
metre	null	O	NNS
10,000	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBZ
occupy	null	O	VBZ
kilometre	null	O	NNS
38,000	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBZ
occupy	null	O	VBZ
kilometre	null	O	NNS
mile	null	O	NNS
14,700	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBZ
occupy	null	O	VBZ
claim	null	O	VBZ
whole	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
state	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
Pradesh	null	LOCATION	NNP
kilometre	null	O	NNS
90,000	null	NUMBER	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
occupy	null	O	VBZ
kilometre	null	O	NNS
38,000	null	NUMBER	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
occupy	null	O	VBZ
kilometre	null	O	NNS
mile	null	O	NNS
14,700	null	NUMBER	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
occupy	null	O	VBZ
claim	null	O	VBZ
whole	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
state	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
Pradesh	null	LOCATION	NNP
kilometre	null	O	NNS
90,000	null	NUMBER	CD
indian	null	MISC	JJ
state	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
whole	null	O	NN
claim	null	O	VBZ
occupy	null	O	VBZ
kilometre	null	O	NNS
38,000	null	NUMBER	CD
indian	null	MISC	JJ
state	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
whole	null	O	NN
claim	null	O	VBZ
occupy	null	O	VBZ
kilometre	null	O	NNS
mile	null	O	NNS
14,700	null	NUMBER	CD
indian	null	MISC	JJ
state	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
Pradesh	null	LOCATION	NNP
kilometre	null	O	NNS
90,000	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBZ
occupy	null	O	VBZ
kilometre	null	O	NNS
38,000	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBZ
occupy	null	O	VBZ
kilometre	null	O	NNS
mile	null	O	NNS
14,700	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBZ
occupy	null	O	VBZ
claim	null	O	VBZ
whole	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
state	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
Pradesh	null	LOCATION	NNP
kilometre	null	O	NNS
90,000	null	NUMBER	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
occupy	null	O	VBZ
kilometre	null	O	NNS
38,000	null	NUMBER	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
occupy	null	O	VBZ
kilometre	null	O	NNS
mile	null	O	NNS
14,700	null	NUMBER	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
occupy	null	O	VBZ
claim	null	O	VBZ
whole	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
state	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
Pradesh	null	LOCATION	NNP
kilometre	null	O	NNS
90,000	null	NUMBER	CD
indian	null	MISC	JJ
state	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
whole	null	O	NN
claim	null	O	VBZ
occupy	null	O	VBZ
kilometre	null	O	NNS
38,000	null	NUMBER	CD
indian	null	MISC	JJ
state	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
whole	null	O	NN
claim	null	O	VBZ
occupy	null	O	VBZ
kilometre	null	O	NNS
mile	null	O	NNS
14,700	null	NUMBER	CD
indian	null	MISC	JJ
state	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
Pradesh	null	LOCATION	NNP
kilometre	null	O	NNS
90,000	null	NUMBER	CD
