U.S.	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
Pound	null	MONEY	NNP
15	null	DATE	CD
U.S.	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NN
Pound	null	MONEY	NNP
15	null	DATE	CD
japanese	null	MONEY	JJ
yen	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	O	NN
Pound	null	MONEY	NNP
15	null	DATE	CD
U.S.	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	O	NN
Pound	null	MONEY	NNP
15	null	DATE	CD
North	null	LOCATION	NNP
future	null	O	NNS
rate	null	O	NN
5,190.24	null	NUMBER	CD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
ftse	null	O	VBP
dollar	null	O	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	O	NN
Pound	null	MONEY	NNP
15	null	DATE	CD
U.S.	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
rate	null	O	NN
5,190.24	null	NUMBER	CD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
ftse	null	O	VBP
dollar	null	O	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	O	NN
Pound	null	MONEY	NNP
15	null	DATE	CD
U.S.	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
rate	null	O	NN
5,190.24	null	NUMBER	CD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
ftse	null	O	VBP
dollar	null	O	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	O	NN
Pound	null	MONEY	NNP
15	null	DATE	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
rate	null	O	NN
5,190.24	null	NUMBER	CD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
ftse	null	O	VBP
dollar	null	O	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	O	NN
Pound	null	MONEY	NNP
15	null	DATE	CD
Ireland	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
17	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	ORGANIZATION	NNPS
AUS	null	O	NNP
17	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
17	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
17	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
17	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
17	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
17	null	NUMBER	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
estimate	null	O	VBN
at	null	O	IN
equivalent	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
tonne	null	O	NNS
5,000	null	NUMBER	CD
15,000	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
bomb	null	O	NN
destroy	null	O	VBD
in	null	O	IN
August	null	DATE	NNP
be	null	O	VBD
around	null	O	IN
kilotonne	null	O	NNS
12.5	null	NUMBER	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
estimate	null	O	VBN
at	null	O	IN
kilotonne	null	O	NNS
10	null	NUMBER	CD
20	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
17	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNPS
AUS	null	O	NNP
17	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
17	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
17	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
17	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
17	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
17	null	NUMBER	CD
Kazakhstan	null	LOCATION	NNP
mine	null	O	VBD
tonne	null	O	NNS
8,500	null	NUMBER	CD
Kazakhstan	null	LOCATION	NNP
mine	null	O	VBD
plan	null	O	VBZ
extract	null	O	VB
tonne	null	O	NNS
11,900	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
17	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
17	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNPS
AUS	null	O	NNP
17	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNPS
AUS	null	O	NNP
17	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
17	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
17	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
17	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
17	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
17	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
17	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
17	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
17	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	O	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
17	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	O	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
17	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
17	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
17	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
17	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
17	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
17	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
17	null	NUMBER	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
back	null	O	RB
persuade	null	O	VBN
leave	null	O	VB
with	null	O	IN
lure	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
contract	null	O	NN
worth	null	O	JJ
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
6.5	null	MONEY	CD
Yemen	null	LOCATION	NNP
export	null	O	VB
tonne	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
6.7	null	NUMBER	CD
Sweden	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
192	null	NUMBER	CD
Sweden	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
87	null	NUMBER	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
to	null	O	TO
192	null	NUMBER	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
to	null	O	TO
87	null	NUMBER	CD
Sweden	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
192	null	NUMBER	CD
Sweden	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
87	null	NUMBER	CD
Monaco	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
192	null	NUMBER	CD
Monaco	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
87	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
192	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
87	null	NUMBER	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
to	null	O	TO
192	null	NUMBER	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
to	null	O	TO
87	null	NUMBER	CD
Kazakhstan	null	LOCATION	NNP
mine	null	O	VBD
tonne	null	O	NNS
8,500	null	NUMBER	CD
Kazakhstan	null	LOCATION	NNP
mine	null	O	VBD
plan	null	O	VBZ
extract	null	O	VB
tonne	null	O	NNS
11,900	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
23	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
23	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
23	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
23	null	NUMBER	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
import	null	O	VBN
tonne	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
57	null	NUMBER	CD
Kazakhstan	null	LOCATION	NNP
mine	null	O	VBD
tonne	null	O	NNS
8,500	null	NUMBER	CD
Kazakhstan	null	LOCATION	NNP
mine	null	O	VBD
plan	null	O	VBZ
extract	null	O	VB
tonne	null	O	NNS
11,900	null	NUMBER	CD
swedish	null	MISC	JJ
technique	null	O	NN
consist	null	O	VBZ
of	null	O	IN
store	null	O	VBG
tonne	null	O	NNS
canister	null	O	NNS
weigh	null	O	VBP
tonne	null	O	NNS
25	null	NUMBER	CD
Cambodia	null	LOCATION	NNP
burn	null	O	NNS
tonne	null	O	NNS
Penh	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
2	null	DATE	CD
cambodian	null	LOCATION	JJ
authority	null	O	NNS
Penh	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
2	null	DATE	CD
spanish	null	MISC	JJ
beti	null	ORGANIZATION	NN
to	null	O	TO
move	null	O	VBD
player	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
21.5	null	MONEY	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
Barry	null	PERSON	NNP
sign	null	O	VBD
from	null	O	IN
rival	null	O	VBZ
for	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
12	null	MONEY	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
League	null	MISC	NNP
rival	null	O	VBZ
for	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
12	null	MONEY	CD
Azerbaijan	null	LOCATION	NNP
extract	null	O	NN
tonne	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
45	null	MONEY	CD
Azerbaijan	null	LOCATION	NNP
produce	null	O	VBD
tonne	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
44.5	null	MONEY	CD
Afghanistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
buy	null	O	VB
tonne	null	O	NNS
200,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Afghanistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
buy	null	O	VB
compare	null	O	VBN
to	null	O	TO
tonne	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.1	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
cost	null	O	VBG
weigh	null	O	VBG
less	null	O	JJR
than	null	O	IN
kilogram	null	O	NN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
2.2	null	MONEY	CD
Ireland	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
23	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
23	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
23	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
23	null	NUMBER	CD
spanish	null	MISC	JJ
queen	null	O	NN
take	null	O	VBZ
give	null	O	VBD
fly	null	O	VBD
for	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
13	null	MONEY	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
Sofia	null	LOCATION	NNP
give	null	O	VBD
fly	null	O	VBD
for	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
13	null	MONEY	CD
Azerbaijan	null	LOCATION	NNP
extract	null	O	NN
tonne	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
45	null	MONEY	CD
Azerbaijan	null	LOCATION	NNP
produce	null	O	VBD
tonne	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
44.5	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
cost	null	O	VB
weigh	null	O	VBP
less	null	O	JJR
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
2.2	null	MONEY	CD
british	null	LOCATION	JJ
loan	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
8.2	null	MONEY	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
member	null	O	NN
accuse	null	O	VBN
of	null	O	IN
pay	null	O	VBG
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
500,000	null	MONEY	CD
Israel	null	LOCATION	NNP
exceed	null	O	VBP
emission	null	O	NNS
tonne	null	O	NNS
11.8	null	NUMBER	CD
Israel	null	LOCATION	NNP
exceed	null	O	VBP
average	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
tonne	null	O	NNS
10.05	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
Thailand	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
board	null	O	NN
try	null	O	VBG
catch	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
gram	null	O	NNS
680	null	NUMBER	CD
Thailand	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
board	null	O	NN
try	null	O	VBG
catch	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
gram	null	O	NNS
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
1.5	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
from	null	O	IN
receive	null	O	VBN
AIG	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
be	null	O	VBZ
in	null	O	IN
position	null	O	NN
renew	null	O	VB
partnership	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
start	null	O	VBD
worth	null	O	JJ
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
19	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
start	null	O	VBD
worth	null	O	JJ
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
19	null	MONEY	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
champion	null	O	NNS
to	null	O	TO
worth	null	O	JJ
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
19	null	MONEY	CD
Azerbaijani	null	MISC	NNP
Aliyev	null	PERSON	NNP
tell	null	O	VBD
stable	null	O	JJ
at	null	O	IN
tonne	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
45	null	MONEY	CD
british	null	LOCATION	JJ
minister	null	O	NN
create	null	O	VB
to	null	O	TO
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
150	null	MONEY	CD
albanian	null	MISC	JJ
state	null	O	NN
by	null	O	IN
hide	null	O	VBN
steal	null	O	VBN
far	null	O	RB
from	null	O	IN
legend	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
find	null	O	VBG
out	null	O	IN
of	null	O	IN
misery	null	O	NN
cache	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
kilogram	null	O	NNS
370	null	NUMBER	CD
albanian	null	MISC	JJ
state	null	O	NN
by	null	O	IN
hide	null	O	VBN
steal	null	O	VBN
far	null	O	RB
from	null	O	IN
legend	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
find	null	O	VBG
out	null	O	IN
of	null	O	IN
misery	null	O	NN
cache	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
kilogram	null	O	NNS
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
815	null	MONEY	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
state	null	O	NN
own	null	O	VBZ
end	null	O	VB
own	null	O	VBG
snub	null	O	VBP
worth	null	O	JJ
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
4.0	null	MONEY	CD
british	null	LOCATION	JJ
minister	null	O	NN
create	null	O	VB
to	null	O	TO
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
150	null	MONEY	CD
Laos	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
heroin	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
trafficking	null	O	NN
gram	null	O	NNS
680	null	NUMBER	CD
Laos	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
heroin	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
trafficking	null	O	NN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
1.5	null	MONEY	CD
Thailand	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
board	null	O	NN
try	null	O	VBG
catch	null	O	VBN
trafficking	null	O	NN
gram	null	O	NNS
680	null	NUMBER	CD
Thailand	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
board	null	O	NN
try	null	O	VBG
catch	null	O	VBN
trafficking	null	O	NN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
1.5	null	MONEY	CD
Laos	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
find	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
gram	null	O	NNS
500	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
Barclays	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
sell	null	O	VBN
worth	null	O	JJ
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
1.25	null	MONEY	CD
Thailand	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
board	null	O	NN
try	null	O	VBG
catch	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
gram	null	O	NNS
680	null	NUMBER	CD
Thailand	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
board	null	O	NN
try	null	O	VBG
catch	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
gram	null	O	NNS
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
1.5	null	MONEY	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
bank	null	O	NN
pump	null	O	VB
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
50	null	MONEY	CD
british	null	LOCATION	JJ
minister	null	O	NN
Darling	null	PERSON	NNP
create	null	O	VB
to	null	O	TO
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
150	null	MONEY	CD
moroccan	null	MISC	JJ
custom	null	O	NNS
seize	null	O	VBP
seize	null	O	VBD
tonne	null	O	NNS
19.5	null	NUMBER	CD
moroccan	null	MISC	JJ
custom	null	O	NNS
seize	null	O	VBP
seize	null	O	VBD
tonne	null	O	NNS
19.5	null	NUMBER	CD
moroccan	null	LOCATION	JJ
officer	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
tonne	null	O	NNS
19.5	null	NUMBER	CD
moroccan	null	LOCATION	JJ
officer	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
tonne	null	O	NNS
seize	null	O	VBD
tonne	null	O	NNS
19.5	null	NUMBER	CD
Thailand	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
board	null	O	NN
try	null	O	VBG
catch	null	O	VBN
find	null	O	VBN
guilty	null	O	JJ
of	null	O	IN
trafficking	null	O	NN
gram	null	O	NNS
680	null	NUMBER	CD
Thailand	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
board	null	O	NN
try	null	O	VBG
catch	null	O	VBN
find	null	O	VBN
guilty	null	O	JJ
of	null	O	IN
trafficking	null	O	NN
gram	null	O	NNS
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
1.5	null	MONEY	CD
Thailand	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
board	null	O	NN
try	null	O	VBG
catch	null	O	VBN
August	null	DATE	NNP
of	null	O	IN
gram	null	O	NNS
680	null	NUMBER	CD
Thailand	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
board	null	O	NN
try	null	O	VBG
catch	null	O	VBN
August	null	DATE	NNP
of	null	O	IN
gram	null	O	NNS
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
1.5	null	MONEY	CD
Laos	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
face	null	O	VBZ
anyone	null	O	NN
find	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
gram	null	O	NNS
500	null	NUMBER	CD
Thailand	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
board	null	O	NN
try	null	O	VBG
catch	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
gram	null	O	NNS
680	null	NUMBER	CD
Thailand	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
board	null	O	NN
try	null	O	VBG
catch	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
gram	null	O	NNS
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
1.5	null	MONEY	CD
Laos	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
find	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
gram	null	O	NNS
500	null	NUMBER	CD
Thailand	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
board	null	O	NN
try	null	O	VBG
catch	null	O	VBN
August	null	DATE	NNP
of	null	O	IN
gram	null	O	NNS
680	null	NUMBER	CD
Thailand	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
board	null	O	NN
try	null	O	VBG
catch	null	O	VBN
August	null	DATE	NNP
of	null	O	IN
gram	null	O	NNS
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
1.5	null	MONEY	CD
Laos	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
face	null	O	VBZ
anyone	null	O	NN
find	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
gram	null	O	NNS
500	null	NUMBER	CD
Israel	null	LOCATION	NNP
exceed	null	O	VBP
emission	null	O	NNS
tonne	null	O	NNS
11.8	null	NUMBER	CD
Israel	null	LOCATION	NNP
exceed	null	O	VBP
average	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
tonne	null	O	NNS
10.05	null	NUMBER	CD
Thailand	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
board	null	O	NN
try	null	O	VBG
catch	null	O	VBN
find	null	O	VBN
guilty	null	O	JJ
of	null	O	IN
trafficking	null	O	NN
gram	null	O	NNS
680	null	NUMBER	CD
Thailand	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
board	null	O	NN
try	null	O	VBG
catch	null	O	VBN
find	null	O	VBN
guilty	null	O	JJ
of	null	O	IN
trafficking	null	O	NN
gram	null	O	NNS
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
1.5	null	MONEY	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
welcome	null	O	VBD
say	null	O	VBD
add	null	O	VBG
intend	null	O	VBN
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
have	null	O	VBD
output	null	O	NN
amount	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
tonne	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
108.4	null	NUMBER	CD
russian	null	LOCATION	JJ
leader	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
add	null	O	VBG
intend	null	O	VBN
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
have	null	O	VBD
output	null	O	NN
amount	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
tonne	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
108.4	null	NUMBER	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
have	null	O	VBD
output	null	O	NN
amount	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
tonne	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
108.4	null	NUMBER	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
produce	null	O	VB
to	null	O	TO
tonne	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
136	null	MONEY	CD
swedish	null	MISC	JJ
technique	null	O	NN
consist	null	O	VBZ
of	null	O	IN
store	null	O	VBG
tonne	null	O	NNS
canister	null	O	NNS
weigh	null	O	VBP
tonne	null	O	NNS
25	null	NUMBER	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
bank	null	O	NN
pump	null	O	VB
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
50	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
GDP	null	O	NNP
inflation	null	O	NN
troops	null	O	NNS
56,000	null	NUMBER	CD
british	null	LOCATION	JJ
home	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
cost	null	O	NN
stand	null	O	VBD
at	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
158,565	null	MONEY	CD
Vietnam	null	LOCATION	NNP
export	null	O	VBN
ton	null	O	NNS
175,000	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
cent	null	O	NNS
to	null	O	TO
fall	null	O	VBD
from	null	O	IN
cent	null	MONEY	NNS
136.90	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
cent	null	O	NNS
to	null	O	TO
retreat	null	O	VBD
from	null	O	IN
cent	null	MONEY	NNS
15.68	null	MONEY	CD
Iran	null	LOCATION	NNP
defy	null	O	VBG
amass	null	O	VBN
kilogram	null	O	NNS
1,339	null	NUMBER	CD
China	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Television	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
focus	null	O	VBD
on	null	O	IN
mine	null	O	NN
work	null	O	VBG
crash	null	O	VBD
tonne	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
3.5	null	NUMBER	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
Kent	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
96	null	NUMBER	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
Kent	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
69	null	NUMBER	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
Kent	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
225	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
Kent	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
96	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
Kent	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
69	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
Kent	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
225	null	NUMBER	CD
danish	null	O	JJ
Kent	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
96	null	NUMBER	CD
danish	null	O	JJ
Kent	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
69	null	NUMBER	CD
danish	null	O	JJ
Kent	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
225	null	NUMBER	CD
icelandic	null	MISC	JJ
government	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
pay	null	O	VB
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
2.3	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
report	null	O	NN
digest	null	O	VBD
sink	null	O	VBD
euro	null	O	NN
LONDON	null	LOCATION	NNP
8	null	DATE	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
for	null	O	IN
downgrade	null	O	NN
report	null	O	NN
digest	null	O	VBD
sink	null	O	VBD
euro	null	O	NN
LONDON	null	LOCATION	NNP
8	null	DATE	CD
british	null	LOCATION	JJ
turmoil	null	O	NN
throw	null	O	VBD
digest	null	O	VBD
sink	null	O	VBD
euro	null	O	NN
LONDON	null	LOCATION	NNP
8	null	DATE	CD
French	null	MISC	NNP
Residence	null	O	NNP
of	null	O	IN
Factfile	null	O	NNP
Weight	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
161	null	NUMBER	CD
French	null	MISC	NNP
Residence	null	O	NNP
of	null	O	IN
Factfile	null	O	NNP
Weight	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
kg	null	O	NN
73	null	NUMBER	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
Kuznetsova	null	PERSON	NNP
on	null	O	IN
factfile	null	O	NN
Residence	null	O	NNP
of	null	O	IN
Factfile	null	O	NNP
Weight	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
161	null	NUMBER	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
Kuznetsova	null	PERSON	NNP
on	null	O	IN
factfile	null	O	NN
Residence	null	O	NNP
of	null	O	IN
Factfile	null	O	NNP
Weight	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
kg	null	O	NN
73	null	NUMBER	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
Kuznetsova	null	PERSON	NNP
on	null	O	IN
factfile	null	O	NN
Residence	null	O	NNP
of	null	O	IN
Factfile	null	O	NNP
Weight	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
161	null	NUMBER	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
Kuznetsova	null	PERSON	NNP
on	null	O	IN
factfile	null	O	NN
Residence	null	O	NNP
of	null	O	IN
Factfile	null	O	NNP
Weight	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
kg	null	O	NN
73	null	NUMBER	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Residence	null	O	NNP
of	null	O	IN
Factfile	null	O	NNP
Weight	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
161	null	NUMBER	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Residence	null	O	NNP
of	null	O	IN
Factfile	null	O	NNP
Weight	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
kg	null	O	NN
73	null	NUMBER	CD
Monaco	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Height	null	O	NNP
Carlo	null	PERSON	NNP
Factfile	null	O	NNP
Weight	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
161	null	NUMBER	CD
Monaco	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Height	null	O	NNP
Carlo	null	PERSON	NNP
Factfile	null	O	NNP
Weight	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
kg	null	O	NN
73	null	NUMBER	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
result	null	O	NN
Plays	null	O	NNP
Weight	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
161	null	NUMBER	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
result	null	O	NN
Plays	null	O	NNP
Weight	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
kg	null	O	NN
73	null	NUMBER	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
Open	null	MISC	NNP
at	null	O	IN
win	null	O	VBD
Federer	null	PERSON	NNP
on	null	O	IN
factfile	null	O	NN
June	null	DATE	NNP
PARIS	null	LOCATION	NNP
Residence	null	O	NNP
Federer	null	PERSON	NNP
Weight	null	O	NNP
tennis	null	O	NN
lb	null	O	NNS
187	null	NUMBER	CD
Switzerland	null	LOCATION	NNP
Residence	null	O	NNP
Federer	null	PERSON	NNP
Weight	null	O	NNP
tennis	null	O	NN
lb	null	O	NNS
187	null	NUMBER	CD
Switzerland	null	LOCATION	NNP
Height	null	O	NNP
Bottmingen	null	PERSON	NNP
Federer	null	PERSON	NNP
Weight	null	O	NNP
tennis	null	O	NN
lb	null	O	NNS
187	null	NUMBER	CD
australian	null	MISC	JJ
tennis	null	O	NN
lb	null	O	NNS
187	null	NUMBER	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
australian	null	MISC	JJ
tennis	null	O	NN
lb	null	O	NNS
187	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
french	null	MISC	JJ
australian	null	MISC	JJ
tennis	null	O	NN
lb	null	O	NNS
187	null	NUMBER	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
result	null	O	NN
tennis	null	O	NN
lb	null	O	NNS
187	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
reduce	null	O	VB
emission	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
tonne	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
50	null	MONEY	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
export	null	O	VBD
tonne	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
20	null	NUMBER	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
export	null	O	VBD
out	null	O	IN
of	null	O	IN
total	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
tonne	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
108.4	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
Institute	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
at	null	O	IN
bear	null	O	VBN
weigh	null	O	VBD
kilogram	null	O	NNS
43	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
Institute	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
at	null	O	IN
bear	null	O	VBN
weigh	null	O	VBD
kilogram	null	O	NNS
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
95	null	MONEY	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
15	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
15	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
15	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
15	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
15	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
15	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
15	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
15	null	NUMBER	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
national	null	O	NNS
pay	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
21,000	null	MONEY	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
into	null	O	IN
smuggle	null	O	VBN
pay	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
21,000	null	MONEY	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
head	null	O	VBG
carry	null	O	VBG
tonne	null	O	NNS
144,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Sudan	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
head	null	O	VBG
carry	null	O	VBG
tonne	null	O	NNS
144,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Libya	null	LOCATION	NNP
supply	null	O	VBZ
tonne	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.5	null	NUMBER	CD
Switzerland	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
crude	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
tonne	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.5	null	NUMBER	CD
Switzerland	null	LOCATION	NNP
association	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
crude	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
tonne	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.5	null	NUMBER	CD
libyan	null	MISC	JJ
delivery	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
halt	null	O	NN
affect	null	O	VB
say	null	O	VBD
crude	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
tonne	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.5	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
use	null	O	VBG
police	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
catch	null	O	VBD
three	null	NUMBER	CD
of	null	O	IN
suspect	null	O	NNS
mix	null	O	VBG
make	null	O	VB
of	null	O	IN
kilogramme	null	O	NNS
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
900	null	MONEY	CD
German	null	MISC	NNP
intelligence	null	O	NN
police	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
catch	null	O	VBD
three	null	NUMBER	CD
of	null	O	IN
suspect	null	O	NNS
mix	null	O	VBG
make	null	O	VB
of	null	O	IN
kilogramme	null	O	NNS
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
900	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
use	null	O	VBG
police	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
catch	null	O	VBD
three	null	NUMBER	CD
of	null	O	IN
suspect	null	O	NNS
mix	null	O	VBG
make	null	O	VB
of	null	O	IN
kilogramme	null	O	NNS
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
900	null	MONEY	CD
German	null	MISC	NNP
intelligence	null	O	NN
police	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
catch	null	O	VBD
three	null	NUMBER	CD
of	null	O	IN
suspect	null	O	NNS
mix	null	O	VBG
make	null	O	VB
of	null	O	IN
kilogramme	null	O	NNS
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
900	null	MONEY	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
government	null	O	NN
by	null	O	IN
repay	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
raise	null	O	VBG
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
4.0	null	MONEY	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
government	null	O	NN
by	null	O	IN
repay	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
raise	null	O	VBG
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
4.0	null	MONEY	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
lbg	null	ORGANIZATION	NN
clinch	null	O	VBZ
say	null	O	VBD
snap	null	O	VBD
raise	null	O	VB
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
4.0	null	MONEY	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
Group	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
snap	null	O	VBD
raise	null	O	VB
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
4.0	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
use	null	O	VBG
police	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
catch	null	O	VBD
three	null	NUMBER	CD
of	null	O	IN
suspect	null	O	NNS
mix	null	O	VBG
make	null	O	VB
of	null	O	IN
kilogramme	null	O	NNS
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
900	null	MONEY	CD
German	null	MISC	NNP
intelligence	null	O	NN
police	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
catch	null	O	VBD
three	null	NUMBER	CD
of	null	O	IN
suspect	null	O	NNS
mix	null	O	VBG
make	null	O	VB
of	null	O	IN
kilogramme	null	O	NNS
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
900	null	MONEY	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
9pt	null	O	NNS
69	null	NUMBER	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
9pt	null	O	NNS
60	null	NUMBER	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
9pt	null	O	NNS
60	null	NUMBER	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
9pt	null	O	NNS
225	null	NUMBER	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
9pt	null	O	NNS
74	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
9pt	null	O	NNS
69	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
9pt	null	O	NNS
60	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
9pt	null	O	NNS
60	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
9pt	null	O	NNS
225	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
9pt	null	O	NNS
74	null	NUMBER	CD
danish	null	O	JJ
9pt	null	O	NNS
69	null	NUMBER	CD
danish	null	O	JJ
9pt	null	O	NNS
60	null	NUMBER	CD
danish	null	O	JJ
9pt	null	O	NNS
60	null	NUMBER	CD
danish	null	O	JJ
9pt	null	O	NNS
225	null	NUMBER	CD
danish	null	O	JJ
9pt	null	O	NNS
74	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
14	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
14	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
14	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
14	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
14	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
14	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
14	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
14	null	NUMBER	CD
Iran	null	LOCATION	NNP
defy	null	O	VBG
amass	null	O	VBN
kilogram	null	O	NNS
1,339	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Council	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
defy	null	O	VBG
amass	null	O	VBN
kilogram	null	O	NNS
1,339	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Scott	null	PERSON	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
Group	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBZ
snap	null	O	VBD
raise	null	O	VB
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
4.0	null	MONEY	CD
Netherlands	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
14	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
14	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
14	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
14	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
14	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
14	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
14	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
14	null	NUMBER	CD
moroccan	null	MISC	JJ
police	null	O	NNS
seize	null	O	VBD
tonne	null	O	NNS
110.8	null	NUMBER	CD
moroccan	null	MISC	JJ
police	null	O	NNS
seize	null	O	VBD
tonne	null	O	NNS
against	null	O	IN
tonne	null	O	NNS
117.7	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
Regiment	null	O	NNP
from	null	O	IN
troops	null	O	NNS
find	null	O	VBN
destroy	null	O	VBN
more	null	O	JJR
than	null	O	IN
kilo	null	O	NNS
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
12,125	null	MONEY	CD
Afghan	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
soldier	null	O	NNS
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
Regiment	null	O	NNP
from	null	O	IN
troops	null	O	NNS
find	null	O	VBN
destroy	null	O	VBN
more	null	O	JJR
than	null	O	IN
kilo	null	O	NNS
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
12,125	null	MONEY	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
Ladbrokes	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
customer	null	O	NN
stake	null	O	VBD
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
135,000	null	MONEY	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
win	null	O	VB
on	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
135,000	null	MONEY	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
if	null	O	IN
win	null	O	VB
mean	null	O	VBD
win	null	O	VB
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
675	null	MONEY	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
risk	null	O	VBG
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
135,000	null	MONEY	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
Ladbrokes	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
customer	null	O	NN
stake	null	O	VBD
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
135,000	null	MONEY	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
win	null	O	VB
on	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
135,000	null	MONEY	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
thrashing	null	O	NN
mean	null	O	VBD
win	null	O	VBD
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
675	null	MONEY	CD
Andorra	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
thrashing	null	O	NN
mean	null	O	VBD
win	null	O	VBD
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
675	null	MONEY	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
risk	null	O	VBG
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
135,000	null	MONEY	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
worsen	null	O	VBZ
widen	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
7.0	null	MONEY	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
worsen	null	O	VBZ
widen	null	O	VBD
from	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
6.5	null	MONEY	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
deficit	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
worsen	null	O	VBZ
widen	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
7.0	null	MONEY	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
deficit	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
worsen	null	O	VBZ
widen	null	O	VBD
from	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
6.5	null	MONEY	CD
UK	null	LOCATION	NNP
across	null	O	IN
live	null	O	JJ
broadcast	null	O	VB
rights	null	O	NNS
for	null	O	IN
pay	null	O	VBZ
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
13.5	null	MONEY	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
UK	null	LOCATION	NNP
across	null	O	IN
live	null	O	JJ
broadcast	null	O	VB
rights	null	O	NNS
for	null	O	IN
pay	null	O	VBZ
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
13.5	null	MONEY	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
match	null	O	VBZ
match	null	O	VBZ
live	null	O	VB
rights	null	O	NNS
for	null	O	IN
pay	null	O	VB
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
150	null	MONEY	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
NOTTINGHAM	null	O	NNP
Simmons	null	PERSON	NNP
81	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
NOTTINGHAM	null	O	NNP
Simmons	null	PERSON	NNP
81	null	NUMBER	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
between	null	O	IN
match	null	O	NN
NOTTINGHAM	null	O	NNP
Simmons	null	PERSON	NNP
81	null	NUMBER	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
NOTTINGHAM	null	O	NNP
Simmons	null	PERSON	NNP
81	null	NUMBER	CD
China	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Daily	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
report	null	O	VBD
find	null	O	VBD
paw	null	O	NNS
weigh	null	O	VBD
kilogram	null	O	NNS
384	null	NUMBER	CD
China	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Daily	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
report	null	O	VBD
find	null	O	VBD
paw	null	O	NNS
weigh	null	O	VBD
kilogram	null	O	NNS
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
845	null	MONEY	CD
Libya	null	LOCATION	NNP
supply	null	O	VBZ
tonne	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.5	null	NUMBER	CD
Switzerland	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
supply	null	O	VBZ
tonne	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.5	null	NUMBER	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
NOTTINGHAM	null	O	NNP
scoreboard	null	O	NN
Cricket	null	O	NNP
Simmons	null	PERSON	NNP
81	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
NOTTINGHAM	null	O	NNP
scoreboard	null	O	NN
Cricket	null	O	NNP
Simmons	null	PERSON	NNP
81	null	NUMBER	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
between	null	O	IN
Cricket	null	O	NNP
Simmons	null	PERSON	NNP
81	null	NUMBER	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
Indies	null	LOCATION	NNP
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
between	null	O	IN
Cricket	null	O	NNP
Simmons	null	PERSON	NNP
81	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
for	null	O	IN
ton	null	O	NNS
ton	null	O	NNS
171,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
for	null	O	IN
ton	null	O	NNS
45,000	null	NUMBER	CD
dutch	null	MISC	JJ
consume	null	O	VBP
maatje	null	O	NNS
into	null	O	IN
make	null	O	VBN
ton	null	O	NNS
30,000	null	NUMBER	CD
dutch	null	MISC	JJ
consume	null	O	VBP
ton	null	O	NNS
12,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Germany	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
export	null	O	VBN
ton	null	O	NNS
15,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Belgium	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
3,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Germany	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
export	null	O	VBN
ton	null	O	NNS
15,000	null	NUMBER	CD
North	null	LOCATION	NNP
America	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
report	null	O	VBN
release	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
kilogram	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
5.5	null	NUMBER	CD
America	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
report	null	O	VBN
release	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
kilogram	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
5.5	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
across	null	O	IN
sector	null	O	NNS
from	null	O	IN
trace	null	O	VBN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
of	null	O	IN
kilogram	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
5.5	null	NUMBER	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
sector	null	O	NNS
from	null	O	IN
trace	null	O	VBN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
of	null	O	IN
kilogram	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
5.5	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
sector	null	O	NNS
from	null	O	IN
trace	null	O	VBN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
of	null	O	IN
kilogram	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
5.5	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
industry	null	O	NN
report	null	O	VBD
kilogram	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
1.5	null	NUMBER	CD
spanish	null	MISC	JJ
club	null	O	NN
sign	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
record	null	O	NN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
60	null	MONEY	CD
spanish	null	MISC	JJ
club	null	O	NN
sign	null	O	NN
make	null	O	VB
offer	null	O	VBP
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
Fabregas	null	PERSON	NNP
throw	null	O	VBN
inevitable	null	O	JJ
with	null	O	IN
embark	null	O	VBG
on	null	O	IN
spree	null	O	NN
over	null	O	IN
week	null	DATE	NN
see	null	O	VBN
sign	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
record	null	O	NN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
60	null	MONEY	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
Fabregas	null	PERSON	NNP
throw	null	O	VBN
inevitable	null	O	JJ
with	null	O	IN
embark	null	O	VBG
on	null	O	IN
spree	null	O	NN
over	null	O	IN
week	null	DATE	NN
see	null	O	VBN
sign	null	O	NN
make	null	O	VB
offer	null	O	VBP
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
scottish	null	MISC	JJ
Rangers	null	ORGANIZATION	NNPS
join	null	O	VBG
in	null	O	IN
deal	null	O	NN
700,000	null	MONEY	CD
american	null	MISC	JJ
player	null	O	NN
deal	null	O	NN
700,000	null	MONEY	CD
Guernsey	null	LOCATION	NNP
Limited	null	O	NNP
company	null	O	NN
buy	null	O	VBD
for	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
959	null	MONEY	CD
spanish	null	MISC	JJ
title	null	O	NNS
win	null	O	VBN
Sociedad	null	PERSON	NNP
of	null	O	IN
captain	null	O	NN
as	null	O	IN
make	null	O	VBD
before	null	O	IN
move	null	O	VBG
in	null	O	IN
deal	null	O	NN
pound	null	MONEY	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
10.5	null	MONEY	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
earthquake	null	O	NN
after	null	O	IN
period	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
have	null	O	VBD
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
14	null	MONEY	CD
England	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
GMT	null	MISC	NNP
sell	null	O	VB
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
GMT	null	MISC	NNP
sell	null	O	VB
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
Zambia	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
of	null	ORGANIZATION	IN
Bank	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
accord	null	O	VBG
jump	null	O	VBD
from	null	O	IN
tonne	null	O	NNS
218,101	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
manchester	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
sell	null	O	VB
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
sell	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
sell	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
manchester	null	O	NNP
for	null	O	IN
bid	null	O	NN
accept	null	O	VB
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
sell	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
sell	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
Manchester	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
spend	null	O	VB
say	null	O	VBP
splash	null	O	VB
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Ferguson	null	PERSON	NNP
Manchester	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
spend	null	O	VB
say	null	O	VBP
splash	null	O	VB
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
35	null	NUMBER	CD
+33	null	NUMBER	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
35	null	NUMBER	CD
+33	null	NUMBER	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
35	null	NUMBER	CD
+33	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
swoop	null	O	NN
football	null	O	NN
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
sell	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
sell	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
brazilian	null	MISC	JJ
Kaka	null	PERSON	NNP
of	null	O	IN
transfer	null	O	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
56	null	MONEY	CD
italian	null	MISC	JJ
Milan	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
transfer	null	O	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
56	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
as	null	O	IN
such	null	O	JJ
front	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
compete	null	O	VB
look	null	O	VBP
clinch	null	O	VBN
transfer	null	O	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
56	null	MONEY	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
report	null	O	VBN
agree	null	O	VBN
worth	null	O	JJ
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
8.3	null	MONEY	CD
spanish	null	MISC	JJ
club	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
pre-contract	null	O	JJ
agree	null	O	VBN
worth	null	O	JJ
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
8.3	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
meet	null	O	VB
tag	null	O	NN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
32	null	MONEY	CD
argentine	null	MISC	JJ
demand	null	O	NNS
on	null	O	IN
remain	null	O	VBP
refuse	null	O	VBD
meet	null	O	VB
tag	null	O	NN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
32	null	MONEY	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
manchester	null	O	NNP
for	null	O	IN
bid	null	O	NN
accept	null	O	VB
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
sell	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
sell	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
brazilian	null	MISC	JJ
Kaka	null	PERSON	NNP
of	null	O	IN
transfer	null	O	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
56	null	MONEY	CD
italian	null	MISC	JJ
Milan	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
transfer	null	O	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
56	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
as	null	O	IN
such	null	O	JJ
front	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
compete	null	O	VB
look	null	O	VBP
clinch	null	O	VBN
transfer	null	O	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
56	null	MONEY	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
report	null	O	NNS
say	null	O	VBD
launch	null	O	VBN
bid	null	O	NN
pound	null	MONEY	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
45	null	MONEY	CD
Zambia	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
of	null	ORGANIZATION	IN
Bank	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
accord	null	O	VBG
jump	null	O	VBD
from	null	O	IN
tonne	null	O	NNS
218,101	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
Manchester	null	PERSON	NNP
for	null	O	IN
bid	null	O	NN
accept	null	O	VB
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
sell	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
sell	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
brazilian	null	MISC	JJ
Kaka	null	PERSON	NNP
of	null	O	IN
transfer	null	O	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
56	null	MONEY	CD
italian	null	MISC	JJ
Milan	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
transfer	null	O	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
56	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
as	null	O	IN
such	null	O	JJ
front	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
compete	null	O	VB
look	null	O	VBP
clinch	null	O	VBN
transfer	null	O	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
56	null	MONEY	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
report	null	O	VBN
agree	null	O	VBN
worth	null	O	JJ
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
8.3	null	MONEY	CD
spanish	null	MISC	JJ
club	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
pre-contract	null	O	JJ
agree	null	O	VBN
worth	null	O	JJ
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
8.3	null	MONEY	CD
Italy	null	LOCATION	NNP
Mallett	null	PERSON	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
player	null	O	NN
weigh	null	O	VBG
kilogram	null	O	NNS
92	null	NUMBER	CD
Italy	null	LOCATION	NNP
Mallett	null	PERSON	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
player	null	O	NN
weigh	null	O	VBG
kilogram	null	O	NNS
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
203	null	MONEY	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
94	null	NUMBER	CD
307	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
94	null	NUMBER	CD
307	null	NUMBER	CD
scottish	null	MISC	JJ
Leage	null	O	NNP
from	null	O	IN
match	null	O	NNS
live	null	O	JJ
stake	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
offer	null	O	VBN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
20	null	MONEY	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
League	null	MISC	NNP
Leage	null	O	NNP
from	null	O	IN
match	null	O	NNS
live	null	O	JJ
stake	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
offer	null	O	VBN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
20	null	MONEY	CD
England	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
sell	null	O	VB
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
sell	null	O	VB
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
swoop	null	O	NN
football	null	O	NN
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
sell	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
sell	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
brazilian	null	MISC	JJ
Kaka	null	PERSON	NNP
of	null	O	IN
transfer	null	O	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
56	null	MONEY	CD
italian	null	MISC	JJ
Milan	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
transfer	null	O	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
56	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
as	null	O	IN
such	null	O	JJ
front	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
compete	null	O	VB
look	null	O	VBP
clinch	null	O	VBN
transfer	null	O	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
56	null	MONEY	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
report	null	O	VBN
agree	null	O	VBN
worth	null	O	JJ
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
8.3	null	MONEY	CD
spanish	null	MISC	JJ
club	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
pre-contract	null	O	JJ
agree	null	O	VBN
worth	null	O	JJ
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
8.3	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
meet	null	O	VB
tag	null	O	NN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
32	null	MONEY	CD
argentine	null	MISC	JJ
demand	null	O	NNS
on	null	O	IN
remain	null	O	VBP
refuse	null	O	VBD
meet	null	O	VB
tag	null	O	NN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
32	null	MONEY	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
appear	null	O	VBZ
set	null	O	VBN
join	null	O	VB
agree	null	O	VBD
sell	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
sell	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
Portugal	null	LOCATION	NNP
winger	null	O	NN
sell	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
appearace	null	O	NNS
goal	null	O	NNS
appearance	null	O	NNS
make	null	O	VBZ
complete	null	O	VBZ
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
12.24	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
goal	null	O	NNS
goal	null	O	NNS
appearance	null	O	NNS
make	null	O	VBZ
complete	null	O	VBZ
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
12.24	null	MONEY	CD
Portugal	null	LOCATION	NNP
appearance	null	O	NNS
goal	null	O	NNS
appearance	null	O	NNS
make	null	O	VBZ
complete	null	O	VBZ
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
12.24	null	MONEY	CD
Portugal	null	LOCATION	NNP
goal	null	O	NNS
goal	null	O	NNS
appearance	null	O	NNS
make	null	O	VBZ
complete	null	O	VBZ
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
12.24	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
against	null	O	IN
pre-season	null	O	JJ
in	null	O	IN
score	null	O	NNS
debut	null	O	NN
make	null	O	VBZ
complete	null	O	VBZ
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
12.24	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
transfer	null	O	NN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
12.24	null	MONEY	CD
England	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
sell	null	O	VB
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
sell	null	O	VB
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
west	null	O	NN
20	null	NUMBER	CD
brazilian	null	MISC	JJ
Kaka	null	PERSON	NNP
of	null	O	IN
transfer	null	O	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
56	null	MONEY	CD
italian	null	MISC	JJ
Milan	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
transfer	null	O	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
56	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
as	null	O	IN
such	null	O	JJ
front	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
compete	null	O	VB
look	null	O	VBP
clinch	null	O	VBN
transfer	null	O	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
56	null	MONEY	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
bank	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
realize	null	O	VB
gain	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
5.3	null	MONEY	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
manchester	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
sell	null	O	VB
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
sell	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
sell	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
cent	null	O	NNS
to	null	O	TO
slip	null	O	VBD
from	null	O	IN
cent	null	MONEY	NNS
135.40	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
cent	null	O	NNS
to	null	O	TO
decline	null	O	VBD
from	null	O	IN
cent	null	MONEY	NNS
15.41	null	MONEY	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
swoop	null	O	NN
football	null	O	NN
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
sell	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
sell	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
brazilian	null	MISC	JJ
Kaka	null	PERSON	NNP
of	null	O	IN
transfer	null	O	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
56	null	MONEY	CD
italian	null	MISC	JJ
Milan	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
transfer	null	O	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
56	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
as	null	O	IN
such	null	O	JJ
front	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
compete	null	O	VB
look	null	O	VBP
clinch	null	O	VBN
transfer	null	O	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
56	null	MONEY	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
report	null	O	VBN
agree	null	O	VBN
worth	null	O	JJ
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
8.3	null	MONEY	CD
spanish	null	MISC	JJ
club	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
pre-contract	null	O	JJ
agree	null	O	VBN
worth	null	O	JJ
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
8.3	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
meet	null	O	VB
tag	null	O	NN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
32	null	MONEY	CD
argentine	null	MISC	JJ
demand	null	O	NNS
on	null	O	IN
remain	null	O	VBP
refuse	null	O	VBD
meet	null	O	VB
tag	null	O	NN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
32	null	MONEY	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
swoop	null	O	NN
football	null	O	NN
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
sell	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
sell	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
brazilian	null	MISC	JJ
Kaka	null	PERSON	NNP
of	null	O	IN
transfer	null	O	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
56	null	MONEY	CD
italian	null	MISC	JJ
Milan	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
transfer	null	O	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
56	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
as	null	O	IN
such	null	O	JJ
front	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
compete	null	O	VB
look	null	O	VBP
clinch	null	O	VBN
transfer	null	O	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
56	null	MONEY	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
report	null	O	VBN
agree	null	O	VBN
worth	null	O	JJ
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
8.3	null	MONEY	CD
spanish	null	MISC	JJ
club	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
pre-contract	null	O	JJ
agree	null	O	VBN
worth	null	O	JJ
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
8.3	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
meet	null	O	VB
tag	null	O	NN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
32	null	MONEY	CD
argentine	null	MISC	JJ
demand	null	O	NNS
on	null	O	IN
remain	null	O	VBP
refuse	null	O	VBD
meet	null	O	VB
tag	null	O	NN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
32	null	MONEY	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
swoop	null	O	NN
football	null	O	NN
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
sell	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
sell	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
report	null	O	VBN
agree	null	O	VBN
worth	null	O	JJ
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
8.3	null	MONEY	CD
spanish	null	MISC	JJ
club	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
pre-contract	null	O	JJ
agree	null	O	VBN
worth	null	O	JJ
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
8.3	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
meet	null	O	VB
tag	null	O	NN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
32	null	MONEY	CD
argentine	null	MISC	JJ
demand	null	O	NNS
on	null	O	IN
remain	null	O	VBP
refuse	null	O	VBD
meet	null	O	VB
tag	null	O	NN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
32	null	MONEY	CD
Thailand	null	LOCATION	NNP
seize	null	O	VBG
kilo	null	O	NNS
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
6.6	null	MONEY	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
Barry	null	PERSON	NNP
complete	null	O	VBD
surprise	null	O	NN
transfer	null	O	NN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
12	null	MONEY	CD
Guernsey	null	LOCATION	NNP
Limited	null	O	NNP
company	null	O	NN
buy	null	O	VBD
for	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
959	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
agree	null	O	VBN
sell	null	O	VB
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
spanish	null	LOCATION	JJ
side	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
sell	null	O	VB
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
Thursday	null	DATE	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
agree	null	O	VBN
sell	null	O	VB
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
spanish	null	MISC	JJ
giant	null	O	NNS
to	null	O	TO
sell	null	O	VB
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
british	null	ORGANIZATION	JJ
Army	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
spend	null	O	VBN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
14	null	MONEY	CD
Afghan	null	MISC	NNP
village	null	O	NN
get	null	O	VB
replica	null	O	NN
create	null	O	VBG
on	null	O	IN
spend	null	O	VBN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
14	null	MONEY	CD
Afghanistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
serve	null	O	VBG
spend	null	O	VBP
use	null	O	VBN
soldier	null	O	NNS
get	null	O	VB
replica	null	O	NN
create	null	O	VBG
on	null	O	IN
spend	null	O	VBN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
14	null	MONEY	CD
Portugal	null	LOCATION	NNP
star	null	O	NN
undergo	null	O	VB
expect	null	O	VBN
sign	null	O	VB
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
9.5	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
meet	null	O	VB
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
32	null	MONEY	CD
argentine	null	MISC	JJ
holder	null	O	NNS
set	null	O	VBD
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
32	null	MONEY	CD
Colombia	null	LOCATION	NNP
produce	null	O	VBZ
tonne	null	O	NNS
600	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Nations	null	ORGANIZATION	NNPS
to	null	O	TO
accord	null	O	VBG
produce	null	O	VBZ
tonne	null	O	NNS
600	null	NUMBER	CD
Colombia	null	LOCATION	NNP
marine	null	O	NNS
to	null	O	TO
accord	null	O	VBG
transport	null	O	VBN
tonne	null	O	NNS
400	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
from	null	O	IN
to	null	O	TO
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
2,800	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
announce	null	O	VBN
deal	null	O	VBP
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
spanish	null	MISC	JJ
giant	null	O	NNS
with	null	O	IN
term	null	O	NNS
discuss	null	O	VBZ
complete	null	O	VBN
deal	null	O	VBP
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
4-134	null	NUMBER	CD
307	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
4-134	null	NUMBER	CD
307	null	NUMBER	CD
Colombia	null	LOCATION	NNP
produce	null	O	VBZ
tonne	null	O	NNS
600	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Nations	null	ORGANIZATION	NNPS
to	null	O	TO
accord	null	O	VBG
produce	null	O	VBZ
tonne	null	O	NNS
600	null	NUMBER	CD
Colombia	null	LOCATION	NNP
marine	null	O	NNS
to	null	O	TO
accord	null	O	VBG
transport	null	O	VBN
tonne	null	O	NNS
400	null	NUMBER	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
run	null	O	NNS
307	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
run	null	O	NNS
307	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
give	null	O	VBD
ton	null	O	NNS
600,000	null	NUMBER	CD
North	null	O	NNP
ton	null	O	NNS
600,000	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
visit	null	O	NNS
reveal	null	O	VBD
give	null	O	VBD
ton	null	O	NNS
600,000	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
13	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
13	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
13	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
13	null	NUMBER	CD
Italy	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
family	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
childhood	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
spend	null	O	VBD
son	null	O	NN
factfile	null	O	NN
220lb	null	O	NNS
kg	null	O	SYM
99.8	null	NUMBER	CD
Italy	null	LOCATION	NNP
recall	null	O	VBZ
report	null	O	VBD
report	null	O	NN
order	null	O	VBN
import	null	O	VBN
recall	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
tonne	null	O	NNS
10,000	null	NUMBER	CD
italian	null	MISC	JJ
court	null	O	NN
order	null	O	VBN
import	null	O	VBN
recall	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
tonne	null	O	NNS
10,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Lithuania	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
import	null	O	VBN
recall	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
tonne	null	O	NNS
10,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Italy	null	LOCATION	NNP
recall	null	O	VBZ
report	null	O	NN
order	null	O	VBN
import	null	O	VBN
recall	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
tonne	null	O	NNS
10,000	null	NUMBER	CD
italian	null	MISC	JJ
court	null	O	NN
order	null	O	VBN
import	null	O	VBN
recall	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
tonne	null	O	NNS
10,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Lithuania	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
import	null	O	VBN
recall	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
tonne	null	O	NNS
10,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Afghanistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
produce	null	O	VBD
tonne	null	O	NNS
8,000	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
figure	null	O	NNS
to	null	O	TO
accord	null	O	VBG
produce	null	O	VBN
of	null	O	IN
bulk	null	O	NN
produce	null	O	VBD
tonne	null	O	NNS
8,000	null	NUMBER	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
tribunal	null	O	NN
by	null	O	IN
dismiss	null	O	VBN
claim	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
17,000	null	MONEY	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
13	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
13	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
13	null	NUMBER	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
ministry	null	O	NN
by	null	O	IN
estimate	null	O	NN
put	null	O	VBD
at	null	O	IN
kiloton	null	O	NNS
20	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
LONDON	null	LOCATION	NNP
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
receive	null	O	VBG
fee	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
receive	null	O	VBG
fee	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
PKF	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
at	null	O	IN
specialist	null	O	NN
recall	null	O	VBG
spend	null	O	VBD
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
69	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
company	null	O	NN
spend	null	O	VBD
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
69	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
Glazer	null	PERSON	NNP
borrow	null	O	VBD
stand	null	O	VBZ
at	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
650	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
buy	null	O	VB
borrow	null	O	VBD
stand	null	O	VBZ
at	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
650	null	MONEY	CD
Iran	null	LOCATION	NNP
on	null	O	IN
report	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
accord	null	O	VBG
defy	null	O	VBG
amass	null	O	VBN
kilogramme	null	O	NNS
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
2,946	null	MONEY	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
gendarme	null	O	NNS
say	null	O	VBD
arrest	null	O	VBN
enthusiast	null	O	NN
hoard	null	O	VBD
arsenal	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
weapon	null	O	NNS
tonne	null	O	NNS
5.5	null	NUMBER	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
Strasbourg	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
of	null	O	IN
tonne	null	O	NNS
weapon	null	O	NNS
hoard	null	O	VBN
gendarme	null	O	NNS
say	null	O	VBD
arrest	null	O	VBN
enthusiast	null	O	NN
hoard	null	O	VBD
arsenal	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
weapon	null	O	NNS
tonne	null	O	NNS
5.5	null	NUMBER	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
gendarme	null	O	NNS
say	null	O	VBD
arrest	null	O	VBN
enthusiast	null	O	NN
hoard	null	O	VBD
arsenal	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
weapon	null	O	NNS
tonne	null	O	NNS
5.5	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
actress	null	O	NN
model	null	O	VBD
worth	null	O	JJ
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
250,000	null	MONEY	CD
Liberia	null	LOCATION	NNP
export	null	O	NNS
decline	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
tonne	null	O	NNS
88,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Liberia	null	LOCATION	NNP
export	null	O	NNS
decline	null	O	VBD
from	null	O	IN
tonne	null	O	NNS
135,000	null	NUMBER	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
to	null	O	TO
280	null	NUMBER	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
to	null	O	TO
123	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
to	null	O	TO
280	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
to	null	O	TO
123	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
Women	null	O	NNP
score	null	O	NNS
Cricket	null	O	NNP
v	null	O	LS
win	null	O	VBN
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Fritz	null	PERSON	NNP
39	null	NUMBER	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Cricket	null	O	NNP
v	null	O	LS
win	null	O	VBN
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Fritz	null	PERSON	NNP
39	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Africa	null	LOCATION	NNP
v	null	O	LS
win	null	O	VBN
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Fritz	null	PERSON	NNP
39	null	NUMBER	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Fritz	null	PERSON	NNP
39	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
play	null	O	VBG
run	null	O	NNS
by	null	O	IN
win	null	O	VBN
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Fritz	null	PERSON	NNP
39	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
play	null	O	VBG
run	null	O	NNS
by	null	O	IN
win	null	O	VBN
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Fritz	null	PERSON	NNP
39	null	NUMBER	CD
Iran	null	LOCATION	NNP
on	null	O	IN
report	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
accord	null	O	VBG
defy	null	O	VBG
amass	null	O	VBN
kilogramme	null	O	NNS
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
2,946	null	MONEY	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
Women	null	O	NNP
score	null	O	NNS
Cricket	null	O	NNP
v	null	O	LS
win	null	O	VBN
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Fritz	null	PERSON	NNP
39	null	NUMBER	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Cricket	null	O	NNP
v	null	O	LS
win	null	O	VBN
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Fritz	null	PERSON	NNP
39	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Africa	null	LOCATION	NNP
v	null	O	LS
win	null	O	VBN
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Fritz	null	PERSON	NNP
39	null	NUMBER	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Fritz	null	PERSON	NNP
39	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
v	null	O	LS
run	null	O	NNS
by	null	O	IN
win	null	O	VBN
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Fritz	null	PERSON	NNP
39	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
v	null	O	LS
run	null	O	NNS
by	null	O	IN
win	null	O	VBN
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Fritz	null	PERSON	NNP
39	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
over	null	MONEY	NNS
in	null	O	IN
v	null	O	LS
run	null	O	NNS
by	null	O	IN
win	null	O	VBN
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Fritz	null	PERSON	NNP
39	null	NUMBER	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
wkt	null	O	NNS
280	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
wkt	null	O	NNS
280	null	NUMBER	CD
Taiwan	null	LOCATION	NNP
man	null	O	NN
hide	null	O	VBD
say	null	O	VBD
official	null	O	NNS
arrest	null	O	VBN
at	null	O	IN
Airport	null	LOCATION	NNP
with	null	O	IN
half-a-kilogram	null	O	NN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
1.1	null	MONEY	CD
australian	null	MISC	JJ
official	null	O	NNS
arrest	null	O	VBN
at	null	O	IN
Airport	null	LOCATION	NNP
with	null	O	IN
half-a-kilogram	null	O	NN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
1.1	null	MONEY	CD
taiwanese	null	MISC	JJ
man	null	O	NN
June	null	DATE	NNP
arrest	null	O	VBN
at	null	O	IN
Airport	null	LOCATION	NNP
with	null	O	IN
half-a-kilogram	null	O	NN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
1.1	null	MONEY	CD
australian	null	MISC	JJ
official	null	O	NNS
arrest	null	O	VBN
at	null	O	IN
Airport	null	LOCATION	NNP
with	null	O	IN
half-a-kilogram	null	O	NN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
1.1	null	MONEY	CD
Thailand	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
board	null	O	NN
try	null	O	VBG
catch	null	O	VBN
August	null	DATE	NNP
of	null	O	IN
trafficking	null	O	NN
gram	null	O	NNS
680	null	NUMBER	CD
Thailand	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
board	null	O	NN
try	null	O	VBG
catch	null	O	VBN
August	null	DATE	NNP
of	null	O	IN
trafficking	null	O	NN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
1.5	null	MONEY	CD
russian	null	LOCATION	JJ
Gazprom	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
control	null	O	VBN
Moscow	null	LOCATION	NNP
boost	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
third	null	O	NNS
to	null	O	TO
tonne	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
5.0	null	NUMBER	CD
russian	null	MISC	JJ
agency	null	O	NNS
by	null	O	IN
carry	null	O	VBN
remark	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
say	null	O	VBD
exceed	null	O	VB
tonne	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
5.0	null	NUMBER	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
balloon	null	O	NNS
record	null	O	VB
show	null	O	VBD
widen	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
19.9	null	MONEY	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
deficit	null	O	NN
widen	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
19.9	null	MONEY	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
forecast	null	O	VBN
borrowing	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
175	null	MONEY	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
5-82	null	NUMBER	CD
79	null	NUMBER	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
5-82	null	NUMBER	CD
101	null	NUMBER	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
5-82	null	NUMBER	CD
280	null	NUMBER	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
5-82	null	NUMBER	CD
101	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
5-82	null	NUMBER	CD
79	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
5-82	null	NUMBER	CD
101	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
5-82	null	NUMBER	CD
280	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
5-82	null	NUMBER	CD
101	null	NUMBER	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
chain	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
plan	null	O	VBD
raise	null	O	VB
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
445	null	MONEY	CD
England	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Club	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
at	null	O	IN
underway	null	O	NN
ranking	null	O	NN
get	null	O	VBP
championship	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
ahead	null	O	RB
title	null	O	NN
LONDON	null	LOCATION	NNP
Residence	null	O	NNP
tennis	null	O	NN
6	null	NUMBER	CD
Weight	null	O	NNP
Plays	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
188	null	NUMBER	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
Residence	null	O	NNP
tennis	null	O	NN
6	null	NUMBER	CD
Weight	null	O	NNP
Plays	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
188	null	NUMBER	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
Height	null	O	NNP
tennis	null	O	NN
6	null	NUMBER	CD
Weight	null	O	NNP
Plays	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
188	null	NUMBER	CD
swiss	null	MISC	JJ
to	null	O	TO
runner-up	null	O	JJ
Weight	null	O	NNP
Plays	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
188	null	NUMBER	CD
Switzerland	null	LOCATION	NNP
Residence	null	O	NNP
Basel	null	LOCATION	NNP
FEDERER	null	PERSON	NNP
Weight	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
187	null	NUMBER	CD
Switzerland	null	LOCATION	NNP
Height	null	O	NNP
Bottmingen	null	PERSON	NNP
FEDERER	null	PERSON	NNP
Weight	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
187	null	NUMBER	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
Open	null	MISC	NNP
at	null	O	IN
Victory	null	O	NNP
result	null	O	NN
title	null	O	NNS
singles	null	O	NNS
Plays	null	O	NNP
Weight	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
187	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
Residence	null	O	NNP
Dunblane	null	LOCATION	NNP
MURRAY	null	PERSON	NNP
bidding	null	O	NN
6	null	NUMBER	CD
Weight	null	O	NNP
Plays	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
185	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
Residence	null	O	NNP
Dunblane	null	LOCATION	NNP
MURRAY	null	PERSON	NNP
bidding	null	O	NN
6	null	NUMBER	CD
Weight	null	O	NNP
Plays	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
kg	null	O	NN
84	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
Height	null	O	NNP
Dunblane	null	LOCATION	NNP
MURRAY	null	PERSON	NNP
bidding	null	O	NN
6	null	NUMBER	CD
Weight	null	O	NNP
Plays	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
185	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
Height	null	O	NNP
Dunblane	null	LOCATION	NNP
MURRAY	null	PERSON	NNP
bidding	null	O	NN
6	null	NUMBER	CD
Weight	null	O	NNP
Plays	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
kg	null	O	NN
84	null	NUMBER	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
winner	null	O	NN
bidding	null	O	NN
6	null	NUMBER	CD
Weight	null	O	NNP
Plays	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
185	null	NUMBER	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
winner	null	O	NN
bidding	null	O	NN
6	null	NUMBER	CD
Weight	null	O	NNP
Plays	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
kg	null	O	NN
84	null	NUMBER	CD
Serbia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Residence	null	O	NNP
Belgrade	null	LOCATION	NNP
DJOKOVIC	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
176	null	NUMBER	CD
Serbia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Residence	null	O	NNP
Belgrade	null	LOCATION	NNP
DJOKOVIC	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
kg	null	O	NN
80	null	NUMBER	CD
Monaco	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Height	null	O	NNP
Carlo	null	PERSON	NNP
DJOKOVIC	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
176	null	NUMBER	CD
Monaco	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Height	null	O	NNP
Carlo	null	PERSON	NNP
DJOKOVIC	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
kg	null	O	NN
80	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	O	NNP
World	null	O	NNP
Height	null	O	NNP
have	null	O	VBZ
result	null	O	NN
6	null	NUMBER	CD
Weight	null	O	NNP
Plays	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
195	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	O	NNP
World	null	O	NNP
Height	null	O	NNP
have	null	O	VBZ
result	null	O	NN
6	null	NUMBER	CD
Weight	null	O	NNP
Plays	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
kg	null	O	NN
89	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Residence	null	O	NNP
Aug	null	DATE	NNP
World	null	O	NNP
Height	null	O	NNP
have	null	O	VBZ
result	null	O	NN
6	null	NUMBER	CD
Weight	null	O	NNP
Plays	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
195	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Residence	null	O	NNP
Aug	null	DATE	NNP
World	null	O	NNP
Height	null	O	NNP
have	null	O	VBZ
result	null	O	NN
6	null	NUMBER	CD
Weight	null	O	NNP
Plays	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
kg	null	O	NN
89	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Height	null	O	NNP
have	null	O	VBZ
result	null	O	NN
6	null	NUMBER	CD
Weight	null	O	NNP
Plays	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
195	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Height	null	O	NNP
have	null	O	VBZ
result	null	O	NN
6	null	NUMBER	CD
Weight	null	O	NNP
Plays	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
kg	null	O	NN
89	null	NUMBER	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
Sainsbury	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
raise	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
expansion	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
raise	null	O	VB
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
445	null	MONEY	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
chain	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
raise	null	O	VB
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
445	null	MONEY	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
chain	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
445	null	MONEY	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
chain	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
plan	null	O	VBD
raise	null	O	VB
about	null	O	RB
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
445	null	MONEY	CD
italian	null	MISC	JJ
police	null	O	NNS
arrest	null	O	VBD
spaniard	null	MISC	NN
tote	null	O	VBD
kilo	null	O	NNS
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
11	null	MONEY	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
judge	null	O	NNS
uphold	null	O	VBD
ruling	null	O	NN
pay	null	O	VB
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
1.8	null	MONEY	CD
italian	null	MISC	JJ
police	null	O	NNS
arrest	null	O	VBD
spaniard	null	MISC	NN
tote	null	O	VBD
kilo	null	O	NNS
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
11	null	MONEY	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
GKN	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
launch	null	O	VBZ
ax	null	O	VBZ
launch	null	O	VBD
bid	null	O	NN
raise	null	O	VB
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
423	null	MONEY	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
GKN	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
launch	null	O	VBD
bid	null	O	NN
raise	null	O	VB
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
423	null	MONEY	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
Filton	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
plant	null	O	NN
buy	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
136	null	MONEY	CD
England	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Club	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
beat	null	O	VBN
here	null	O	RB
on	null	O	IN
Plays	null	O	NNP
Monday	null	DATE	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
154	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Club	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
beat	null	O	VBN
here	null	O	RB
on	null	O	IN
Plays	null	O	NNP
Monday	null	DATE	NNP
kg	null	O	NN
70	null	NUMBER	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Residence	null	O	NNP
Moscow	null	LOCATION	NNP
Monday	null	DATE	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
154	null	NUMBER	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Residence	null	O	NNP
Moscow	null	LOCATION	NNP
Monday	null	DATE	NNP
kg	null	O	NN
70	null	NUMBER	CD
Monaco	null	LOCATION	NNP
Height	null	O	NNP
Carlo	null	PERSON	NNP
Monday	null	DATE	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
154	null	NUMBER	CD
Monaco	null	LOCATION	NNP
Height	null	O	NNP
Carlo	null	PERSON	NNP
Monday	null	DATE	NNP
kg	null	O	NN
70	null	NUMBER	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
Open	null	MISC	NNP
in	null	O	IN
tennis	null	O	NN
get	null	O	VBZ
under	null	O	IN
way	null	O	NN
at	null	O	IN
Club	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
beat	null	O	VBN
here	null	O	RB
on	null	O	IN
Plays	null	O	NNP
Monday	null	DATE	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
154	null	NUMBER	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
Open	null	MISC	NNP
in	null	O	IN
tennis	null	O	NN
get	null	O	VBZ
under	null	O	IN
way	null	O	NN
at	null	O	IN
Club	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
beat	null	O	VBN
here	null	O	RB
on	null	O	IN
Plays	null	O	NNP
Monday	null	DATE	NNP
kg	null	O	NN
70	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	O	NNP
WILLIAMS	null	PERSON	NNP
Plays	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
150	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	O	NNP
WILLIAMS	null	PERSON	NNP
Plays	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
kg	null	O	NN
68	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Residence	null	O	NNP
WILLIAMS	null	PERSON	NNP
Plays	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
150	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Residence	null	O	NNP
WILLIAMS	null	PERSON	NNP
Plays	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
kg	null	O	NN
68	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Height	null	O	NNP
Gardens	null	LOCATION	NNP
WILLIAMS	null	PERSON	NNP
Plays	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
150	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Height	null	O	NNP
Gardens	null	LOCATION	NNP
WILLIAMS	null	PERSON	NNP
Plays	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
kg	null	O	NN
68	null	NUMBER	CD
American	null	MISC	NNP
WILLIAMS	null	PERSON	NNP
Plays	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
150	null	NUMBER	CD
American	null	MISC	NNP
WILLIAMS	null	PERSON	NNP
Plays	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
kg	null	O	NN
68	null	NUMBER	CD
australian	null	MISC	JJ
Open	null	MISC	NNP
in	null	O	IN
victory	null	O	NN
by	null	O	IN
bolster	null	O	VBN
WILLIAMS	null	PERSON	NNP
Plays	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
150	null	NUMBER	CD
australian	null	MISC	JJ
Open	null	MISC	NNP
in	null	O	IN
victory	null	O	NN
by	null	O	IN
bolster	null	O	VBN
WILLIAMS	null	PERSON	NNP
Plays	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
kg	null	O	NN
68	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	O	NNP
WILLIAMS	null	PERSON	NNP
result	null	O	NN
1	null	NUMBER	CD
Plays	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
160	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	O	NNP
WILLIAMS	null	PERSON	NNP
result	null	O	NN
1	null	NUMBER	CD
Plays	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
kg	null	O	NN
72.5	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Residence	null	O	NNP
Lynwood	null	LOCATION	NNP
WILLIAMS	null	PERSON	NNP
result	null	O	NN
1	null	NUMBER	CD
Plays	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
160	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Residence	null	O	NNP
Lynwood	null	LOCATION	NNP
WILLIAMS	null	PERSON	NNP
result	null	O	NN
1	null	NUMBER	CD
Plays	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
kg	null	O	NN
72.5	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Height	null	O	NNP
Gardens	null	LOCATION	NNP
WILLIAMS	null	PERSON	NNP
result	null	O	NN
1	null	NUMBER	CD
Plays	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
160	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Height	null	O	NNP
Gardens	null	LOCATION	NNP
WILLIAMS	null	PERSON	NNP
result	null	O	NN
1	null	NUMBER	CD
Plays	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
kg	null	O	NN
72.5	null	NUMBER	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Residence	null	O	NNP
Moscow	null	LOCATION	NNP
DEMENTIEVA	null	PERSON	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
141	null	NUMBER	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Residence	null	O	NNP
Moscow	null	LOCATION	NNP
DEMENTIEVA	null	PERSON	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
kg	null	O	NN
64	null	NUMBER	CD
Monaco	null	LOCATION	NNP
Height	null	O	NNP
Carlo	null	PERSON	NNP
DEMENTIEVA	null	PERSON	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
141	null	NUMBER	CD
Monaco	null	LOCATION	NNP
Height	null	O	NNP
Carlo	null	PERSON	NNP
DEMENTIEVA	null	PERSON	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
kg	null	O	NN
64	null	NUMBER	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Residence	null	O	NNP
Petersburg	null	LOCATION	NNP
KUZNETSOVA	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Weight	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
161	null	NUMBER	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Residence	null	O	NNP
Petersburg	null	LOCATION	NNP
KUZNETSOVA	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Weight	null	O	NNP
kg	null	O	NN
73	null	NUMBER	CD
Monaco	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Height	null	O	NNP
Carlo	null	PERSON	NNP
KUZNETSOVA	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Weight	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
161	null	NUMBER	CD
Monaco	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Height	null	O	NNP
Carlo	null	PERSON	NNP
KUZNETSOVA	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Weight	null	O	NNP
kg	null	O	NN
73	null	NUMBER	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
Open	null	MISC	NNP
at	null	O	IN
Victory	null	O	NNP
Plays	null	O	NNP
Weight	null	O	NNP
lb	null	O	NNS
161	null	NUMBER	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
Open	null	MISC	NNP
at	null	O	IN
Victory	null	O	NNP
Plays	null	O	NNP
Weight	null	O	NNP
kg	null	O	NN
73	null	NUMBER	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
chain	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
raise	null	O	VB
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
445	null	MONEY	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
chain	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
fund	null	O	NNS
raise	null	O	VB
chain	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
raise	null	O	VB
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
445	null	MONEY	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
come	null	O	VBD
see	null	O	VB
to	null	O	TO
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
342,500	null	MONEY	CD
