Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
70	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
32	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
70	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
32	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
70	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
32	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
70	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
32	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
70	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
32	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
70	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
32	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
70	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
32	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
31	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
41	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
18	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
41	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
31	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
41	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
18	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
41	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
31	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
41	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
18	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
41	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
31	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
41	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
18	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
41	null	NUMBER	CD
Kuwaiti	null	MISC	NNP
size	null	O	NN
CITY	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
1	null	DATE	CD
KUWAIT	null	LOCATION	NNP
CITY	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
1	null	DATE	CD
kuwaiti	null	LOCATION	JJ
lawmaker	null	O	NN
CITY	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
1	null	DATE	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
70	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
32	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
70	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
32	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
70	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
32	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
70	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
32	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
70	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
32	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
70	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
32	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
70	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
32	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
70	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
32	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
70	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
32	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
70	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
32	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
70	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
32	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
70	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
32	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
70	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
32	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
70	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
32	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
70	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
32	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
31	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
41	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
18	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
31	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
41	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
18	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
31	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
41	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
18	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
31	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
41	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
18	null	NUMBER	CD
Kuwait	null	LOCATION	NNP
pump	null	O	NNS
barrel	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.2	null	NUMBER	CD
Kuwait	null	LOCATION	NNP
pump	null	O	NNS
barrel	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.2	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
7	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
7	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
7	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
7	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
7	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
7	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
7	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
7	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
7	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
7	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
7	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
7	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
7	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
7	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
7	null	NUMBER	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
42	null	NUMBER	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
13	null	NUMBER	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
42	null	NUMBER	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
13	null	NUMBER	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
42	null	NUMBER	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
13	null	NUMBER	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
42	null	NUMBER	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
13	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
Survey	null	O	NNP
estimate	null	O	VBD
barrel	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
31.4	null	NUMBER	CD
Greenland	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
part	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
barrel	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
31.4	null	NUMBER	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
42	null	NUMBER	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
13	null	NUMBER	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
42	null	NUMBER	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
13	null	NUMBER	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
42	null	NUMBER	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
13	null	NUMBER	CD
France	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
vanish	null	O	VBD
hunt	null	O	NN
41	null	NUMBER	CD
Paris	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
+33	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
vanish	null	O	VBD
hunt	null	O	NN
41	null	NUMBER	CD
Paris	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
+33	null	NUMBER	CD
north	null	LOCATION	JJ
leader	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
rescue	null	O	VBZ
hunt	null	O	NN
41	null	NUMBER	CD
Paris	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
+33	null	NUMBER	CD
France	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
plane	null	O	NN
hunting	null	O	NN
team	null	O	NNS
scour	null	O	VBP
,3	null	NUMBER	CD
france-brazil-air-accident	null	O	JJ
negotiation	null	O	NNS
on	null	O	IN
confident	null	O	JJ
pick	null	O	VB
say	null	O	VBD
rescue	null	O	VBZ
hunt	null	O	NN
41	null	NUMBER	CD
Paris	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
+33	null	NUMBER	CD
Egypt	null	LOCATION	NNP
clampdown	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
Muslims	null	MISC	NNPS
world	null	O	NN
41	null	NUMBER	CD
PARIS	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
+33	null	NUMBER	CD
Chinese	null	MISC	NNP
clampdown	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
Muslims	null	MISC	NNPS
world	null	O	NN
41	null	NUMBER	CD
PARIS	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
+33	null	NUMBER	CD
north	null	LOCATION	JJ
trial	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
clampdown	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
Muslims	null	MISC	NNPS
world	null	O	NN
41	null	NUMBER	CD
PARIS	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
+33	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
for	null	O	IN
begin	null	O	VBZ
Muslims	null	MISC	NNPS
world	null	O	NN
41	null	NUMBER	CD
PARIS	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
+33	null	NUMBER	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
crash	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
emerge	null	O	VBP
begin	null	O	VBZ
Muslims	null	MISC	NNPS
world	null	O	NN
41	null	NUMBER	CD
PARIS	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
+33	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
Obama	null	PERSON	NNP
be	null	O	VBZ
thlead-wrap	null	O	NN
crash	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
emerge	null	O	VBP
begin	null	O	VBZ
Muslims	null	MISC	NNPS
world	null	O	NN
41	null	NUMBER	CD
PARIS	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
+33	null	NUMBER	CD
America	null	LOCATION	NNP
between	null	O	IN
rift	null	O	NN
heal	null	O	VB
seek	null	O	VBG
make	null	O	VB
be	null	O	VBZ
thlead-wrap	null	O	NN
crash	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
emerge	null	O	VBP
begin	null	O	VBZ
Muslims	null	MISC	NNPS
world	null	O	NN
41	null	NUMBER	CD
PARIS	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
+33	null	NUMBER	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
rsa	null	O	NN
1	null	NUMBER	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
rsa	null	O	NN
1	null	NUMBER	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
rsa	null	O	NN
1	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
rsa	null	O	NN
1	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
rsa	null	O	NN
1	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
rsa	null	O	NN
1	null	NUMBER	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
rsa	null	O	NN
1	null	NUMBER	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
rsa	null	O	NN
1	null	NUMBER	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
rsa	null	O	NN
1	null	NUMBER	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
rsa	null	O	NN
1	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
rsa	null	O	NN
1	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
rsa	null	O	NN
1	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
rsa	null	O	NN
1	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
rsa	null	O	NN
1	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
rsa	null	O	NN
1	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
rsa	null	O	NN
1	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
rsa	null	O	NN
1	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
rsa	null	O	NN
1	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
10	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
10	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
10	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
10	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
10	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
10	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
10	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
10	null	NUMBER	CD
russian	null	MISC	JJ
economy	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
prospects	null	O	NNS
dependent	null	O	JJ
on	null	O	IN
price	null	O	NN
stand	null	O	VBZ
at	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
69	null	MONEY	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
10	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
10	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNPS
AUS	null	O	NNP
10	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNPS
AUS	null	O	NNP
10	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
10	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
10	null	NUMBER	CD
Sweden	null	LOCATION	NNP
0	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Denmark	null	LOCATION	NNP
0	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Slovakia	null	LOCATION	NNP
0	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Azerbaijan	null	LOCATION	NNP
0	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Wales	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
0	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Finland	null	LOCATION	NNP
0	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
liechtenstein	null	LOCATION	NN
0	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Kazakhstan	null	LOCATION	NNP
0	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
0	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Belarus	null	LOCATION	NNP
0	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Andorra	null	LOCATION	NNP
0	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Lithuania	null	LOCATION	NNP
0	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Romania	null	LOCATION	NNP
0	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Cyprus	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
0	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Montenegro	null	LOCATION	NNP
0	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Bulgaria	null	LOCATION	NNP
0	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
0	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Norway	null	LOCATION	NNP
0	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
russian	null	MISC	JJ
economy	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
prospects	null	O	NNS
dependent	null	O	JJ
on	null	O	IN
price	null	O	NN
stand	null	O	VBZ
at	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
69	null	MONEY	CD
Egypt	null	LOCATION	NNP
clampdown	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
address	null	O	VB
+	null	O	CC
36	null	NUMBER	CD
41	null	NUMBER	CD
PARIS	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
+33	null	NUMBER	CD
Chinese	null	MISC	NNP
clampdown	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
address	null	O	VB
+	null	O	CC
36	null	NUMBER	CD
41	null	NUMBER	CD
PARIS	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
+33	null	NUMBER	CD
North	null	LOCATION	NNP
Korea	null	LOCATION	NNP
on	null	O	IN
clampdown	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
address	null	O	VB
+	null	O	CC
36	null	NUMBER	CD
41	null	NUMBER	CD
PARIS	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
+33	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
put	null	O	VBZ
Korea	null	LOCATION	NNP
on	null	O	IN
clampdown	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
address	null	O	VB
+	null	O	CC
36	null	NUMBER	CD
41	null	NUMBER	CD
PARIS	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
+33	null	NUMBER	CD
France	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Obama	null	PERSON	NNP
arrive	null	O	VBZ
blast	null	O	NN
address	null	O	VB
+	null	O	CC
36	null	NUMBER	CD
41	null	NUMBER	CD
PARIS	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
+33	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
Obama	null	PERSON	NNP
arrive	null	O	VBZ
blast	null	O	NN
address	null	O	VB
+	null	O	CC
36	null	NUMBER	CD
41	null	NUMBER	CD
PARIS	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
+33	null	NUMBER	CD
Egypt	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
arrive	null	O	VBZ
blast	null	O	NN
address	null	O	VB
+	null	O	CC
36	null	NUMBER	CD
41	null	NUMBER	CD
PARIS	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
+33	null	NUMBER	CD
America	null	LOCATION	NNP
between	null	O	IN
breach	null	O	NN
heal	null	O	VB
seek	null	O	VBG
herald	null	O	VBN
tight	null	O	JJ
Egypt	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
arrive	null	O	VBZ
blast	null	O	NN
address	null	O	VB
+	null	O	CC
36	null	NUMBER	CD
41	null	NUMBER	CD
PARIS	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
+33	null	NUMBER	CD
Sweden	null	LOCATION	NNP
16	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Denmark	null	LOCATION	NNP
16	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Albania	null	LOCATION	NNP
16	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Portugal	null	LOCATION	NNP
16	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Slovakia	null	LOCATION	NNP
16	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Azerbaijan	null	LOCATION	NNP
16	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Wales	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
16	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Finland	null	LOCATION	NNP
16	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
liechtenstein	null	LOCATION	NN
16	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Kazakhstan	null	LOCATION	NNP
16	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
16	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Belarus	null	LOCATION	NNP
16	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Andorra	null	LOCATION	NNP
16	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Ukraine	null	LOCATION	NNP
16	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Lithuania	null	LOCATION	NNP
16	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Romania	null	LOCATION	NNP
16	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Serbia	null	LOCATION	NNP
16	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Austria	null	LOCATION	NNP
16	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Cyprus	null	LOCATION	NNP
16	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Montenegro	null	LOCATION	NNP
16	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Bulgaria	null	LOCATION	NNP
16	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
16	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Norway	null	LOCATION	NNP
16	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Iceland	null	LOCATION	NNP
16	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
16	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Slovakia	null	LOCATION	NNP
0	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Azerbaijan	null	LOCATION	NNP
0	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Wales	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
0	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Finland	null	LOCATION	NNP
0	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
liechtenstein	null	LOCATION	NN
0	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Kazakhstan	null	LOCATION	NNP
0	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
0	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Belarus	null	LOCATION	NNP
0	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Andorra	null	LOCATION	NNP
0	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Cyprus	null	LOCATION	NNP
0	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Montenegro	null	LOCATION	NNP
0	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Bulgaria	null	LOCATION	NNP
0	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
0	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Norway	null	LOCATION	NNP
0	null	NUMBER	CD
33	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
16	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
16	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
16	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
16	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
16	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
16	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
16	null	NUMBER	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
Kent	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
95	null	NUMBER	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
Kent	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
73	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
Kent	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
95	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
Kent	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
73	null	NUMBER	CD
danish	null	O	JJ
Kent	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
95	null	NUMBER	CD
danish	null	O	JJ
Kent	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
73	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
38	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
38	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
38	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
38	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
38	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
38	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
38	null	NUMBER	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
Mathews	null	PERSON	NNP
Bowling	null	O	NNP
Mubarak	null	PERSON	NNP
11	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
16	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
16	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
16	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
16	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
16	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
16	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
16	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
16	null	NUMBER	CD
Slovakia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Finland	null	LOCATION	NNP
forssell	null	ORGANIZATION	NN
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Azerbaijan	null	LOCATION	NNP
Wales	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Finland	null	LOCATION	NNP
forssell	null	ORGANIZATION	NN
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Wales	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Finland	null	LOCATION	NNP
forssell	null	ORGANIZATION	NN
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Finland	null	LOCATION	NNP
forssell	null	ORGANIZATION	NN
33	null	NUMBER	CD
liechtenstein	null	LOCATION	NN
Finland	null	LOCATION	NNP
forssell	null	ORGANIZATION	NN
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Kazakhstan	null	LOCATION	NNP
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
liechtenstein	null	LOCATION	NN
Finland	null	LOCATION	NNP
forssell	null	ORGANIZATION	NN
33	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
liechtenstein	null	LOCATION	NN
Finland	null	LOCATION	NNP
forssell	null	ORGANIZATION	NN
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Belarus	null	LOCATION	NNP
Norway	null	LOCATION	NNP
football	null	O	NN
liechtenstein	null	LOCATION	NN
Finland	null	LOCATION	NNP
forssell	null	ORGANIZATION	NN
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Andorra	null	LOCATION	NNP
Norway	null	LOCATION	NNP
football	null	O	NN
liechtenstein	null	LOCATION	NN
Finland	null	LOCATION	NNP
forssell	null	ORGANIZATION	NN
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Norway	null	LOCATION	NNP
football	null	O	NN
liechtenstein	null	LOCATION	NN
Finland	null	LOCATION	NNP
forssell	null	ORGANIZATION	NN
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
18	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
18	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
18	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
38	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
38	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
38	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
38	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
38	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
38	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
38	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
38	null	NUMBER	CD
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
sentence	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
defeat	null	O	VBN
triumph	null	O	NNS
PARIS	null	LOCATION	NNP
40	null	NUMBER	CD
+33	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
journalist	null	O	NNS
defeat	null	O	VBN
triumph	null	O	NNS
PARIS	null	LOCATION	NNP
40	null	NUMBER	CD
+33	null	NUMBER	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
source	null	O	NN
+	null	O	CC
defeat	null	O	VBN
triumph	null	O	NNS
PARIS	null	LOCATION	NNP
40	null	NUMBER	CD
+33	null	NUMBER	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
,4	null	NUMBER	CD
from	null	O	IN
pull	null	O	VBD
+	null	O	CC
defeat	null	O	VBN
triumph	null	O	NNS
PARIS	null	LOCATION	NNP
40	null	NUMBER	CD
+33	null	NUMBER	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
9pt	null	O	NNS
95	null	NUMBER	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
9pt	null	O	NNS
271	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
9pt	null	O	NNS
95	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
9pt	null	O	NNS
271	null	NUMBER	CD
danish	null	O	JJ
9pt	null	O	NNS
95	null	NUMBER	CD
danish	null	O	JJ
9pt	null	O	NNS
271	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
33	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
10	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
33	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
10	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
33	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
10	null	NUMBER	CD
Scott	null	PERSON	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
33	null	NUMBER	CD
Scott	null	PERSON	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
10	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
West	null	PERSON	NNP
10	null	NUMBER	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
White	null	O	NNP
5	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
White	null	O	NNP
5	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
White	null	O	NNP
5	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
White	null	O	NNP
5	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
White	null	O	NNP
5	null	NUMBER	CD
iraqi	null	MISC	JJ
pm	null	O	NN
meet	null	O	VBZ
chief	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
Baghdad	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
10	null	DATE	CD
iraqi	null	LOCATION	JJ
al-Maliki	null	PERSON	NNP
meet	null	O	VBD
meet	null	O	VBZ
chief	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
Baghdad	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
10	null	DATE	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
total	null	O	JJ
of	null	O	IN
executive	null	O	NN
meet	null	O	VBD
meet	null	O	VBZ
chief	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
Baghdad	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
10	null	DATE	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
White	null	O	NNP
5	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
White	null	O	NNP
5	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
White	null	O	NNP
5	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
White	null	O	NNP
5	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
White	null	O	NNP
5	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
White	null	O	NNP
5	null	NUMBER	CD
libyan	null	MISC	JJ
union	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
president	null	O	NN
al-Asta	null	PERSON	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
have	null	O	VBP
company	null	O	NNS
52	null	NUMBER	CD
italian	null	MISC	JJ
company	null	O	NNS
52	null	NUMBER	CD
Libya	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
have	null	O	VBP
company	null	O	NNS
52	null	NUMBER	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
White	null	O	NNP
5	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
White	null	O	NNP
5	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
White	null	O	NNP
5	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
White	null	O	NNP
5	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
White	null	O	NNP
5	null	NUMBER	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
unit	null	O	NN
shed	null	O	VB
job	null	O	NNS
560	null	NUMBER	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
unit	null	O	NN
shed	null	O	VB
job	null	O	NNS
June	null	DATE	NNP
announce	null	O	VBD
cut	null	O	VBG
about	null	O	IN
job	null	O	NNS
560	null	NUMBER	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
arm	null	O	NN
Insurance	null	O	NNP
announce	null	O	VBD
June	null	DATE	NNP
job	null	O	NNS
560	null	NUMBER	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
arm	null	O	NN
Insurance	null	O	NNP
announce	null	O	VBD
cut	null	O	VBG
about	null	O	IN
job	null	O	NNS
560	null	NUMBER	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
Axa	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
arm	null	O	NN
Insurance	null	O	NNP
announce	null	O	VBD
June	null	DATE	NNP
job	null	O	NNS
560	null	NUMBER	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
Axa	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
arm	null	O	NN
Insurance	null	O	NNP
announce	null	O	VBD
cut	null	O	VBG
about	null	O	IN
job	null	O	NNS
560	null	NUMBER	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
94	null	NUMBER	CD
277	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
94	null	NUMBER	CD
277	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
NOTTINGHAM	null	O	NNP
Cricket	null	O	NNP
Franklin	null	PERSON	NNP
Cusack	null	PERSON	NNP
42	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
Cricket	null	O	NNP
Franklin	null	PERSON	NNP
Cusack	null	PERSON	NNP
42	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
between	null	O	IN
match	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
June	null	DATE	NNP
Cusack	null	PERSON	NNP
42	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
scoreboard	null	O	NN
Cricket	null	O	NNP
Guptill	null	PERSON	NNP
McCallan	null	PERSON	NNP
Cusack	null	PERSON	NNP
42	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
scoreboard	null	O	NN
Cricket	null	O	NNP
Guptill	null	PERSON	NNP
McCallan	null	PERSON	NNP
Cusack	null	PERSON	NNP
42	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
between	null	O	IN
scoreboard	null	O	NN
Cricket	null	O	NNP
Guptill	null	PERSON	NNP
McCallan	null	PERSON	NNP
Cusack	null	PERSON	NNP
42	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
ENG	null	O	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
Mills	null	O	NNP
22	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
Mills	null	O	NNP
7	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
Mills	null	O	NNP
7	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
Mills	null	O	NNP
22	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
Mills	null	O	NNP
7	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
Mills	null	O	NNP
7	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	O	NNP
83	null	NUMBER	CD
72	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	O	NNP
83	null	NUMBER	CD
72	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	O	NNP
83	null	NUMBER	CD
72	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	O	NNP
83	null	NUMBER	CD
72	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	O	NNP
83	null	NUMBER	CD
72	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	O	NNP
83	null	NUMBER	CD
72	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	O	NNP
83	null	NUMBER	CD
72	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	O	NNP
83	null	NUMBER	CD
72	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
83	null	NUMBER	CD
72	null	NUMBER	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
4-134	null	NUMBER	CD
295	null	NUMBER	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
4-134	null	NUMBER	CD
277	null	NUMBER	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
4-134	null	NUMBER	CD
248	null	NUMBER	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
4-134	null	NUMBER	CD
317	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
4-134	null	NUMBER	CD
295	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
4-134	null	NUMBER	CD
277	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
4-134	null	NUMBER	CD
248	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
4-134	null	NUMBER	CD
317	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
Mills	null	O	NNP
22	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
Mills	null	O	NNP
7	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
Mills	null	O	NNP
7	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
Mills	null	O	NNP
22	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
Mills	null	O	NNP
7	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
Mills	null	O	NNP
7	null	NUMBER	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
run	null	O	NNS
295	null	NUMBER	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
run	null	O	NNS
220	null	NUMBER	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
run	null	O	NNS
277	null	NUMBER	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
run	null	O	NNS
248	null	NUMBER	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
run	null	O	NNS
317	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
run	null	O	NNS
295	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
run	null	O	NNS
220	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
run	null	O	NNS
277	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
run	null	O	NNS
248	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
run	null	O	NNS
317	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
11	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
11	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
11	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
11	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
11	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
11	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
srus	null	O	NN
11	null	NUMBER	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
discuss	null	O	VBD
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
Jose	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
15	null	DATE	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
Jose	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
15	null	DATE	CD
iraqi	null	MISC	JJ
pm	null	O	NN
meet	null	O	VBZ
meet	null	O	VBD
June	null	DATE	NNP
17	null	DATE	CD
russian	null	MISC	JJ
Lukoil	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
head	null	O	NN
June	null	DATE	NNP
17	null	DATE	CD
iraqi	null	LOCATION	JJ
oil	null	O	NN
develop	null	O	VB
which	null	O	WDT
June	null	DATE	NNP
17	null	DATE	CD
Iraq	null	LOCATION	NNP
al-Maliki	null	PERSON	NNP
meet	null	O	VBD
June	null	DATE	NNP
17	null	DATE	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
scoreboard	null	O	NN
between	null	O	IN
Morkel	null	PERSON	NNP
out	null	O	IN
Botha	null	PERSON	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
scoreboard	null	O	NN
between	null	O	IN
Morkel	null	PERSON	NNP
out	null	O	IN
Botha	null	PERSON	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
scoreboard	null	O	NN
between	null	O	IN
Morkel	null	PERSON	NNP
out	null	O	IN
Botha	null	PERSON	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
Africa	null	LOCATION	NNP
Morkel	null	PERSON	NNP
out	null	O	IN
Botha	null	PERSON	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
Africa	null	LOCATION	NNP
Morkel	null	PERSON	NNP
out	null	O	IN
Botha	null	PERSON	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Africa	null	LOCATION	NNP
Africa	null	LOCATION	NNP
Morkel	null	PERSON	NNP
out	null	O	IN
Botha	null	PERSON	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
Japan	null	LOCATION	NNP
for	null	O	IN
match	null	O	NNS
match	null	O	NNS
149	null	NUMBER	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
Mendis	null	PERSON	NNP
41	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
Mendis	null	PERSON	NNP
41	null	NUMBER	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
Mendis	null	PERSON	NNP
41	null	NUMBER	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
Mendis	null	PERSON	NNP
41	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
NOTTINGHAM	null	O	NNP
Cricket	null	O	NNP
not	null	O	RB
out	null	O	IN
Botha	null	PERSON	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
NOTTINGHAM	null	O	NNP
Cricket	null	O	NNP
not	null	O	RB
out	null	O	IN
Botha	null	PERSON	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
Kingdom	null	LOCATION	NNP
Cricket	null	O	NNP
not	null	O	RB
out	null	O	IN
Botha	null	PERSON	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
Africa	null	LOCATION	NNP
between	null	O	IN
match	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
June	null	DATE	NNP
Pratap	null	PERSON	NNP
c	null	O	NN
Morkel	null	PERSON	NNP
Cricket	null	O	NNP
not	null	O	RB
out	null	O	IN
Botha	null	PERSON	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
Africa	null	LOCATION	NNP
between	null	O	IN
match	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
June	null	DATE	NNP
Pratap	null	PERSON	NNP
c	null	O	NN
Morkel	null	PERSON	NNP
Cricket	null	O	NNP
not	null	O	RB
out	null	O	IN
Botha	null	PERSON	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Africa	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
Pratap	null	PERSON	NNP
c	null	O	NN
Morkel	null	PERSON	NNP
Cricket	null	O	NNP
not	null	O	RB
out	null	O	IN
Botha	null	PERSON	NNP
8	null	NUMBER	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
to	null	O	TO
165	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
to	null	O	TO
165	null	NUMBER	CD
Kuwait	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
facility	null	O	NNS
through	null	O	IN
daily	null	SET	NN
pump	null	O	NNS
around	null	O	IN
barrel	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
2.2	null	NUMBER	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
NOTTINGHAM	null	O	NNP
Cricket	null	O	NNP
McCullum	null	PERSON	NNP
Mills	null	PERSON	NNP
Vettori	null	PERSON	NNP
Jayawardene	null	PERSON	NNP
lbw	null	O	NN
out	null	O	IN
41	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
NOTTINGHAM	null	O	NNP
Cricket	null	O	NNP
McCullum	null	PERSON	NNP
Mills	null	PERSON	NNP
Vettori	null	PERSON	NNP
Jayawardene	null	PERSON	NNP
lbw	null	O	NN
out	null	O	IN
41	null	NUMBER	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
Zealand	null	LOCATION	NNP
between	null	O	IN
match	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
scoreboard	null	O	NN
NOTTINGHAM	null	O	NNP
Cricket	null	O	NNP
McCullum	null	PERSON	NNP
Mills	null	PERSON	NNP
Vettori	null	PERSON	NNP
Jayawardene	null	PERSON	NNP
lbw	null	O	NN
out	null	O	IN
41	null	NUMBER	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
Cricket	null	O	NNP
McCullum	null	PERSON	NNP
Mills	null	PERSON	NNP
Vettori	null	PERSON	NNP
Jayawardene	null	PERSON	NNP
lbw	null	O	NN
out	null	O	IN
41	null	NUMBER	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
wkt	null	O	NNS
165	null	NUMBER	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
wkt	null	O	NNS
57	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
wkt	null	O	NNS
165	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
wkt	null	O	NNS
57	null	NUMBER	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
Board	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
contain	null	O	VB
barrel	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
666	null	NUMBER	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
round	null	O	NN
Jose	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
15	null	DATE	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
round	null	O	NN
Jose	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
15	null	DATE	CD
russian	null	LOCATION	JJ
Gazprom	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
control	null	O	VBN
Moscow	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
17	null	DATE	CD
Iran	null	LOCATION	NNP
Minister	null	O	NNP
in	null	O	IN
call	null	O	VBN
rally	null	O	NNS
mourning	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
day	null	DURATION	NN
41	null	NUMBER	CD
PARIS	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
+33	null	NUMBER	CD
Somalia	null	LOCATION	NNP
blast	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
kill	null	O	VBN
rally	null	O	NNS
mourning	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
day	null	DURATION	NN
41	null	NUMBER	CD
PARIS	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
+33	null	NUMBER	CD
Iran	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
supporter	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
thousand	null	O	NNS
,7	null	NUMBER	CD
iran-politics	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
meet	null	O	VBP
kill	null	O	VBN
rally	null	O	NNS
mourning	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
day	null	DURATION	NN
41	null	NUMBER	CD
PARIS	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
+33	null	NUMBER	CD
russian	null	MISC	JJ
MOSCOW	null	LOCATION	NNP
open	null	O	VBZ
open	null	O	VBD
giant	null	O	JJ
June	null	DATE	NNP
18	null	DATE	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
giant	null	O	JJ
June	null	DATE	NNP
18	null	DATE	CD
russian	null	LOCATION	JJ
mega-store	null	O	NN
open	null	O	VBD
giant	null	O	JJ
June	null	DATE	NNP
18	null	DATE	CD
