U.S.	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
Pound	null	MONEY	NNP
dollar	null	O	NN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	O	NNS
1.49440	null	NUMBER	CD
1.48850	null	NUMBER	CD
U.S.	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	O	NNS
1.49440	null	NUMBER	CD
1.48850	null	NUMBER	CD
japanese	null	MONEY	JJ
yen	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	O	NN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	O	NNS
1.49440	null	NUMBER	CD
1.48850	null	NUMBER	CD
U.S.	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
1.49440	null	NUMBER	CD
1.48850	null	NUMBER	CD
North	null	LOCATION	NNP
future	null	O	NNS
rate	null	O	NN
5,190.24	null	NUMBER	CD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
ftse	null	O	VBP
dollar	null	O	NNS
1.49440	null	NUMBER	CD
1.48850	null	NUMBER	CD
U.S.	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
rate	null	O	NN
5,190.24	null	NUMBER	CD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
ftse	null	O	VBP
dollar	null	O	NNS
1.49440	null	NUMBER	CD
1.48850	null	NUMBER	CD
U.S.	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
rate	null	O	NN
5,190.24	null	NUMBER	CD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
ftse	null	O	VBP
dollar	null	O	NNS
1.49440	null	NUMBER	CD
1.48850	null	NUMBER	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
rate	null	O	NN
5,190.24	null	NUMBER	CD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
ftse	null	O	VBP
dollar	null	O	NNS
1.49440	null	NUMBER	CD
1.48850	null	NUMBER	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
0486	null	NUMBER	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
dollar	null	O	NNS
from	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
1.0391	null	MONEY	CD
canadian	null	MONEY	JJ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
from	null	O	IN
dollar	null	O	NNS
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
0486	null	NUMBER	CD
canadian	null	MONEY	JJ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
1.0391	null	MONEY	CD
japanese	null	MONEY	JJ
yen	null	MONEY	NNS
91.29	null	MONEY	CD
japanese	null	MONEY	JJ
yen	null	MONEY	NNS
to	null	O	TO
rise	null	O	VBD
from	null	O	IN
yen	null	O	NNS
91.06	null	NUMBER	CD
japanese	null	MISC	JJ
yen	null	O	NNS
from	null	O	IN
rise	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
yen	null	MONEY	NNS
91.29	null	MONEY	CD
japanese	null	MISC	JJ
yen	null	O	NNS
91.06	null	NUMBER	CD
german	null	MISC	JJ
export	null	O	NNS
reach	null	O	VBD
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
994.9	null	MONEY	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
Fund	null	O	NNP
provide	null	O	VBZ
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
700,000	null	MONEY	CD
Yemen	null	LOCATION	NNP
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
700,000	null	MONEY	CD
U.S.	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VBZ
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
700,000	null	MONEY	CD
Yemeni	null	LOCATION	NNP
woman	null	O	NN
empower	null	O	VB
fund	null	O	VBG
for	null	O	IN
provide	null	O	VBZ
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
700,000	null	MONEY	CD
Yemen	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
finance	null	O	VB
project	null	O	NNS
18	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
currency	null	O	NN
from	null	O	IN
away	null	O	RB
switch	null	O	VB
persuade	null	O	VBD
jump	null	O	VBD
above	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
1.42	null	MONEY	CD
Taiwan	null	LOCATION	NNP
order	null	O	NNS
fall	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
25.13	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
25.13	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
currency	null	O	NN
from	null	O	IN
away	null	O	RB
switch	null	O	VB
persuade	null	O	VBP
say	null	O	VBP
jump	null	O	VBZ
above	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
1.42	null	MONEY	CD
swedish	null	MISC	JJ
government	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
krona	null	O	NNS
creditor	null	O	NN
owe	null	O	VBZ
krona	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
924	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
offer	null	O	VB
to	null	O	TO
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
9.5	null	MONEY	CD
UNITED	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
state	null	ORGANIZATION	NNS
2009	null	DATE	CD
Feb	null	DATE	NNP
12	null	DATE	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
plane	null	O	NN
2009	null	DATE	CD
Feb	null	DATE	NNP
12	null	DATE	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
government	null	O	NN
offer	null	O	VBZ
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
3.3	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
3.3	null	NUMBER	CD
Russian	null	MISC	NNP
bank	null	O	NNS
need	null	O	VBP
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
28.4	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
currency	null	O	NN
from	null	O	IN
switch	null	O	VB
persuade	null	O	VBD
jump	null	O	VBD
above	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
1.42	null	MONEY	CD
japanese	null	MISC	JJ
yen	null	O	NN
against	null	O	IN
jump	null	O	VBD
from	null	O	IN
yen	null	MONEY	NNS
134.94	null	MONEY	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
boost	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
move	null	O	NN
worth	null	O	NN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
60.28	null	MONEY	CD
german	null	MISC	JJ
french	null	MISC	JJ
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
boost	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
move	null	O	NN
worth	null	O	NN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
60.28	null	MONEY	CD
spanish	null	LOCATION	JJ
french	null	MISC	JJ
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
boost	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
move	null	O	NN
worth	null	O	NN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
60.28	null	MONEY	CD
swiss	null	MISC	JJ
franc	null	O	NNS
yen	null	MONEY	NN
at	null	O	IN
late	null	O	RB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
against	null	MONEY	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
1.4183	null	MONEY	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
face	null	O	VB
host	null	O	VBZ
on	null	O	IN
June	null	DATE	NNP
20	null	DATE	CD
Iraq	null	LOCATION	NNP
host	null	O	VBZ
on	null	O	IN
June	null	DATE	NNP
20	null	DATE	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Africa	null	LOCATION	NNP
host	null	O	VBZ
on	null	O	IN
June	null	DATE	NNP
20	null	DATE	CD
Belarus	null	LOCATION	NNP
refuse	null	O	VBN
tranche	null	O	NN
euro	null	MONEY	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
358	null	MONEY	CD
russian	null	LOCATION	JJ
loan	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
tranche	null	O	NN
euro	null	MONEY	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
358	null	MONEY	CD
russian	null	MISC	JJ
ruble	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
in	null	O	IN
receive	null	O	VBG
on	null	O	IN
insist	null	O	VBN
refuse	null	O	VBN
tranche	null	O	NN
euro	null	MONEY	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
358	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
30,000	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
currency	null	O	NN
from	null	O	IN
away	null	O	RB
switch	null	O	VB
persuade	null	O	VBD
jump	null	O	VBD
above	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
1.42	null	MONEY	CD
japanese	null	MISC	JJ
currency	null	O	NN
against	null	O	IN
fall	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
yen	null	MONEY	NNS
94.54	null	MONEY	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
boost	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
move	null	O	NN
worth	null	O	NN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
60.28	null	MONEY	CD
german	null	MISC	JJ
french	null	MISC	JJ
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
boost	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
move	null	O	NN
worth	null	O	NN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
60.28	null	MONEY	CD
spanish	null	LOCATION	JJ
french	null	MISC	JJ
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
boost	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
move	null	O	NN
worth	null	O	NN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
60.28	null	MONEY	CD
swiss	null	MISC	JJ
franc	null	O	NNS
yen	null	MONEY	NN
at	null	O	IN
late	null	O	RB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
against	null	MONEY	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
1.4230	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
9.5	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
9.5	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
firm	null	O	NN
production	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
portion	null	O	NN
keep	null	O	VB
offer	null	O	VB
to	null	O	TO
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
9.5	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
currency	null	O	NN
from	null	O	IN
switch	null	O	VB
persuade	null	O	VBP
say	null	O	VBD
jump	null	O	VBZ
above	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
1.42	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
offer	null	O	VBD
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
9.5	null	MONEY	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
production	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
portion	null	O	NN
keep	null	O	VB
aid	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
offer	null	O	VBD
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
9.5	null	MONEY	CD
Belgium	null	LOCATION	NNP
budget	null	O	NN
reach	null	O	VB
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
12	null	MONEY	CD
Afghanistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
for	null	O	IN
budget	null	O	NN
reach	null	O	VB
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
12	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
Obama	null	PERSON	NNP
rating	null	O	NNS
beat	null	O	VBP
by	null	O	IN
point	null	O	NNS
26	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
of	null	O	IN
those	null	O	DT
beat	null	O	VBP
by	null	O	IN
point	null	O	NNS
26	null	NUMBER	CD
Kuwait	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
point	null	O	NNS
26	null	NUMBER	CD
Jordan	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
point	null	O	NNS
point	null	O	NNS
26	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
Emirates	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
point	null	O	NNS
point	null	O	NNS
26	null	NUMBER	CD
Arabia	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
point	null	O	NNS
point	null	O	NNS
26	null	NUMBER	CD
Egypt	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
point	null	O	NNS
point	null	O	NNS
26	null	NUMBER	CD
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
point	null	O	NNS
26	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
currency	null	O	NN
from	null	O	IN
away	null	O	RB
switch	null	O	VB
persuade	null	O	VBD
jump	null	O	VBD
above	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
1.42	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
complex	null	O	NN
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
2.4	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
currency	null	O	NN
from	null	O	IN
away	null	O	RB
switch	null	O	VB
persuade	null	O	VBD
jump	null	O	VBD
above	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
1.42	null	MONEY	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
Communications	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
rise	null	O	VBD
rupee	null	O	NNS
14.95	null	NUMBER	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
back	null	O	RB
persuade	null	O	VBN
leave	null	O	VB
with	null	O	IN
lure	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
contract	null	O	NN
worth	null	O	JJ
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
7.4	null	MONEY	CD
Georgia	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
slowdown	null	O	NN
follow	null	O	VBG
in	null	O	IN
despite	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
3.2	null	MONEY	CD
indian	null	MISC	JJ
League	null	MISC	NNP
in	null	O	IN
value	null	O	VBD
at	null	O	IN
dollar	null	O	NNS
700,000	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
700,000	null	NUMBER	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
pm	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBZ
quit	null	O	VB
predict	null	O	VBZ
insist	null	O	VBD
LONDON	null	LOCATION	NNP
May	null	DATE	NNP
31	null	DATE	CD
british	null	LOCATION	JJ
Brown	null	PERSON	NNP
LONDON	null	LOCATION	NNP
May	null	DATE	NNP
31	null	DATE	CD
indian	null	MISC	JJ
League	null	MISC	NNP
in	null	O	IN
value	null	O	VBD
at	null	O	IN
dollar	null	O	NNS
700,000	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
700,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
budget	null	O	VBN
over	null	O	IN
ruble	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
230	null	MONEY	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
flow	null	O	NNS
restore	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
move	null	O	NN
buy	null	O	VB
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
60	null	MONEY	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
flow	null	O	NNS
restore	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
move	null	O	NN
buy	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
85	null	MONEY	CD
german	null	MISC	JJ
french	null	MISC	JJ
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
flow	null	O	NNS
restore	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
move	null	O	NN
buy	null	O	VB
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
60	null	MONEY	CD
german	null	MISC	JJ
french	null	MISC	JJ
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
flow	null	O	NNS
restore	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
move	null	O	NN
buy	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
85	null	MONEY	CD
spanish	null	LOCATION	JJ
french	null	MISC	JJ
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
flow	null	O	NNS
restore	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
move	null	O	NN
buy	null	O	VB
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
60	null	MONEY	CD
spanish	null	LOCATION	JJ
french	null	MISC	JJ
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
flow	null	O	NNS
restore	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
move	null	O	NN
buy	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
85	null	MONEY	CD
Germany	null	LOCATION	NNP
act	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
4.2	null	MONEY	CD
Germany	null	LOCATION	NNP
act	null	O	VB
would	null	O	MD
make	null	O	VB
loan	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
1.5	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
discuss	null	O	VB
sale	null	O	NNS
include	null	O	VBG
request	null	O	NN
buy	null	O	VB
to	null	O	TO
fighter	null	O	NNS
F-35	null	O	NNP
75	null	NUMBER	CD
Israel	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
sale	null	O	NNS
include	null	O	VBG
request	null	O	NN
buy	null	O	VB
to	null	O	TO
fighter	null	O	NNS
F-35	null	O	NNP
75	null	NUMBER	CD
Sweden	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
3,307,332	null	NUMBER	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
to	null	O	TO
3,307,332	null	NUMBER	CD
Sweden	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
3,307,332	null	NUMBER	CD
Monaco	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
3,307,332	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
3,307,332	null	NUMBER	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
to	null	O	TO
3,307,332	null	NUMBER	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
pm	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBZ
quit	null	O	VB
predict	null	O	VBZ
insist	null	O	VBD
LONDON	null	LOCATION	NNP
May	null	DATE	NNP
31	null	DATE	CD
british	null	LOCATION	JJ
Brown	null	PERSON	NNP
LONDON	null	LOCATION	NNP
May	null	DATE	NNP
31	null	DATE	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
Obama	null	PERSON	NNP
rating	null	O	NNS
beat	null	O	VBP
by	null	O	IN
point	null	O	NNS
26	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
of	null	O	IN
those	null	O	DT
beat	null	O	VBP
by	null	O	IN
point	null	O	NNS
26	null	NUMBER	CD
Kuwait	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
point	null	O	NNS
26	null	NUMBER	CD
Jordan	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
point	null	O	NNS
point	null	O	NNS
26	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
Emirates	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
point	null	O	NNS
point	null	O	NNS
26	null	NUMBER	CD
Arabia	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
point	null	O	NNS
point	null	O	NNS
26	null	NUMBER	CD
Egypt	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
point	null	O	NNS
point	null	O	NNS
26	null	NUMBER	CD
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
point	null	O	NNS
26	null	NUMBER	CD
Fiji	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	ORGANIZATION	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	ORGANIZATION	CD
Fiji	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	ORGANIZATION	CD
Wales	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	ORGANIZATION	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	ORGANIZATION	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	ORGANIZATION	CD
Fiji	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	ORGANIZATION	CD
Wales	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	ORGANIZATION	CD
Kenya	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	ORGANIZATION	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	ORGANIZATION	CD
Samoa	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	ORGANIZATION	CD
South	null	O	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	ORGANIZATION	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	ORGANIZATION	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	ORGANIZATION	CD
Kenya	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	ORGANIZATION	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	ORGANIZATION	CD
Samoa	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	ORGANIZATION	CD
England	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	ORGANIZATION	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	ORGANIZATION	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	ORGANIZATION	CD
Portugal	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	ORGANIZATION	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	ORGANIZATION	CD
Argentina	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	ORGANIZATION	CD
Portugal	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	ORGANIZATION	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	ORGANIZATION	CD
England	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	ORGANIZATION	CD
Georgia	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	ORGANIZATION	CD
Argentina	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	ORGANIZATION	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	ORGANIZATION	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	ORGANIZATION	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	ORGANIZATION	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	ORGANIZATION	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	ORGANIZATION	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	ORGANIZATION	CD
Georgia	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	ORGANIZATION	CD
Canada	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	ORGANIZATION	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
1	null	NUMBER	CD
27	null	ORGANIZATION	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
government	null	O	NN
offer	null	O	VBZ
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
3.3	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
3.3	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
30,000	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
discuss	null	O	VB
sale	null	O	NNS
include	null	O	VBG
request	null	O	NN
buy	null	O	VB
to	null	O	TO
fighter	null	O	NNS
F-35	null	O	NNP
75	null	NUMBER	CD
Israel	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
sale	null	O	NNS
include	null	O	VBG
request	null	O	NN
buy	null	O	VB
to	null	O	TO
fighter	null	O	NNS
F-35	null	O	NNP
75	null	NUMBER	CD
israeli	null	MISC	JJ
official	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
expect	null	O	VBN
discuss	null	O	VB
sale	null	O	NNS
include	null	O	VBG
request	null	O	NN
buy	null	O	VB
to	null	O	TO
fighter	null	O	NNS
F-35	null	O	NNP
75	null	NUMBER	CD
Bulgaria	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
aid	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
freeze	null	O	VB
total	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
825	null	MONEY	CD
Bulgaria	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
aid	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
freeze	null	O	VB
total	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
1.2	null	MONEY	CD
Bulgaria	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
aid	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
freeze	null	O	VB
prompt	null	O	VBD
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
220	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
complex	null	O	NN
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
2.4	null	NUMBER	CD
Denmark	null	LOCATION	NNP
send	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
1.34	null	MONEY	CD
Denmark	null	LOCATION	NNP
send	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
1.92	null	MONEY	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
copenhagen	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
offer	null	O	VBZ
send	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
1.34	null	MONEY	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
copenhagen	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
offer	null	O	VBZ
send	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
1.92	null	MONEY	CD
Denmark	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
copenhagen	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
offer	null	O	VBZ
send	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
1.34	null	MONEY	CD
Denmark	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
copenhagen	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
offer	null	O	VBZ
send	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
1.92	null	MONEY	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
war	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
catch	null	O	VBN
help	null	O	VB
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
1.34	null	MONEY	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
war	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
catch	null	O	VBN
help	null	O	VB
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
1.92	null	MONEY	CD
Germany	null	LOCATION	NNP
slump	null	O	NN
by	null	O	IN
hit	null	O	VBN
help	null	O	VB
apply	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
650	null	MONEY	CD
Germany	null	LOCATION	NNP
slump	null	O	NN
by	null	O	IN
hit	null	O	VBN
help	null	O	VB
apply	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
930	null	MONEY	CD
Germany	null	LOCATION	NNP
slump	null	O	NN
by	null	O	IN
hit	null	O	VBN
help	null	O	VB
apply	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
in	null	O	IN
guarantee	null	O	NNS
line	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
200	null	MONEY	CD
Sweden	null	LOCATION	NNP
cost	null	O	NN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
100	null	MONEY	CD
Sweden	null	LOCATION	NNP
cost	null	O	NN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
140	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
amid	null	O	IN
dollar	null	O	NN
hope	null	O	VBZ
LONDON	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
2	null	DATE	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
recovery	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
hope	null	O	NNS
raise	null	O	VBN
possible	null	O	JJ
as	null	O	RB
return	null	O	VB
announcement	null	O	NN
after	null	O	IN
gain	null	O	VBN
gain	null	O	NNS
on	null	O	IN
dollar	null	O	NN
hope	null	O	VBZ
LONDON	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
2	null	DATE	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
banking	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
recovery	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
hope	null	O	NNS
after	null	O	IN
spike	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
1.4314	null	MONEY	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
boost	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
move	null	O	NN
worth	null	O	NN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
60.28	null	MONEY	CD
german	null	MISC	JJ
french	null	MISC	JJ
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
boost	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
move	null	O	NN
worth	null	O	NN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
60.28	null	MONEY	CD
spanish	null	MISC	JJ
french	null	MISC	JJ
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
boost	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
move	null	O	NN
worth	null	O	NN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
60.28	null	MONEY	CD
brazilian	null	MISC	JJ
playmaker	null	O	NN
sign	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
65	null	NUMBER	CD
spanish	null	MISC	JJ
Ser	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
report	null	O	VBD
football	null	O	NN
sign	null	O	NNS
playmaker	null	O	NN
sign	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
65	null	NUMBER	CD
irish	null	MISC	JJ
Ryanair	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
face	null	O	VBD
loss	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
169	null	MONEY	CD
irish	null	MISC	JJ
Ryanair	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
face	null	O	VBD
loss	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
239	null	MONEY	CD
irish	null	MISC	JJ
Ryanair	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
report	null	O	VBD
loss	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
169	null	MONEY	CD
irish	null	MISC	JJ
Ryanair	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
report	null	O	VBD
loss	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
239	null	MONEY	CD
Oman	null	LOCATION	NNP
MADRID	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
sell	null	O	VBZ
say	null	O	VBD
sell	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
to	null	O	TO
division	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
Oil	null	O	NNP
for	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
155.2	null	MONEY	CD
Oman	null	LOCATION	NNP
MADRID	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
sell	null	O	VBZ
say	null	O	VBD
sell	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
to	null	O	TO
division	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
Oil	null	O	NNP
for	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
217.2	null	MONEY	CD
spanish	null	MISC	JJ
Natural	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
sell	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
to	null	O	TO
division	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
Oil	null	O	NNP
for	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
155.2	null	MONEY	CD
spanish	null	MISC	JJ
Natural	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
sell	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
to	null	O	TO
division	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
Oil	null	O	NNP
for	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
217.2	null	MONEY	CD
Oman	null	LOCATION	NNP
Oil	null	O	NNP
for	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
155.2	null	MONEY	CD
Oman	null	LOCATION	NNP
Oil	null	O	NNP
for	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
217.2	null	MONEY	CD
spanish	null	LOCATION	JJ
mayor	null	O	NN
fine	null	O	VBN
fine	null	O	VBN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
6,840	null	MONEY	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
town	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
mayor	null	O	NN
June	null	DATE	NNP
fine	null	O	VBN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
6,840	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
430	null	NUMBER	CD
Zimbabwe	null	LOCATION	NNP
brussels	null	O	NNS
for	null	O	IN
announce	null	O	VBZ
announce	null	O	VBD
allocate	null	O	VBN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
11	null	MONEY	CD
Zimbabwe	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
help	null	O	VB
allocate	null	O	VBN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
11	null	MONEY	CD
Zimbabwe	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
aid	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
freeze	null	O	NN
have	null	O	VBZ
send	null	O	VB
aid	null	O	NN
give	null	O	VBN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
90	null	MONEY	CD
irish	null	MISC	JJ
Ryanair	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
report	null	O	VBD
loss	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
169	null	MONEY	CD
irish	null	MISC	JJ
Ryanair	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
report	null	O	VBD
loss	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
239	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
complex	null	O	NN
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
2.4	null	NUMBER	CD
Macau	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
value	null	O	NN
stand	null	O	VBD
at	null	O	IN
yuan	null	MONEY	NN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
13.4	null	MONEY	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
hold	null	O	VBZ
value	null	O	NN
stand	null	O	VBD
at	null	O	IN
yuan	null	MONEY	NN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
13.4	null	MONEY	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
carrier	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
stand	null	O	VBD
at	null	O	IN
yuan	null	MONEY	NN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
13.4	null	MONEY	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
contributor	null	O	NN
deploy	null	O	VBG
around	null	O	IN
8,300	null	NUMBER	CD
Afghanistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
contributor	null	O	NN
deploy	null	O	VBG
around	null	O	IN
8,300	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
after	null	O	IN
contributor	null	O	NN
deploy	null	O	VBG
around	null	O	IN
8,300	null	NUMBER	CD
south	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
base	null	O	VBN
force	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
part	null	O	NN
as	null	O	IN
deploy	null	O	VBG
around	null	O	IN
8,300	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
HDFC	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
rise	null	O	VBD
rupee	null	O	NNS
96.4	null	NUMBER	CD
North	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
North	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
North	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
North	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
North	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
North	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
North	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
North	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
North	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
North	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
North	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
North	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
North	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
North	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
American	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
American	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
American	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
American	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
American	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
American	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
American	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
American	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
American	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
American	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
American	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
American	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
American	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
American	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
Honduras	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
Mexico	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
America	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
America	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
America	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
America	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
America	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
America	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
America	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
America	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
America	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
America	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
America	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
America	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
America	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
America	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
USA	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Rica	null	LOCATION	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
Germany	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
crisis	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
symbol	null	O	NN
HRE	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
benefit	null	O	VBN
from	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
102	null	MONEY	CD
german	null	MISC	JJ
voter	null	O	NNS
pick	null	O	VB
99	null	NUMBER	CD
of	null	O	IN
deputy	null	O	NNS
736	null	MONEY	CD
Zimbabwe	null	LOCATION	NNP
brussels	null	O	NNS
for	null	O	IN
announce	null	O	VBZ
say	null	O	VBD
allocate	null	O	VBN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
11.3	null	MONEY	CD
Zimbabwe	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
aid	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
freeze	null	O	NN
have	null	O	VBZ
mean	null	O	VBG
send	null	O	VB
aid	null	O	NN
total	null	O	VBD
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
90	null	MONEY	CD
german	null	MISC	JJ
Porsche	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
reaffirm	null	O	VBD
finish	null	O	VB
at	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
253.20	null	MONEY	CD
Luxembourg	null	LOCATION	NNP
rise	null	O	VB
to	null	O	TO
top	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
list	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
13,458	null	MONEY	CD
Luxembourg	null	LOCATION	NNP
rise	null	O	VB
to	null	O	TO
top	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
list	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
spend	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
2006	null	DATE	CD
top	null	O	VBG
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
9,099	null	MONEY	CD
Luxembourg	null	LOCATION	NNP
rise	null	O	VB
to	null	O	TO
top	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
list	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
spend	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
2006	null	DATE	CD
top	null	O	VBG
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
Sweden	null	LOCATION	NNP
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
8,998	null	MONEY	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
top	null	O	VBG
2006	null	DATE	CD
in	null	O	IN
spend	null	O	VBN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
13,458	null	MONEY	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
9,099	null	MONEY	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
Sweden	null	LOCATION	NNP
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
8,998	null	MONEY	CD
Sweden	null	LOCATION	NNP
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
top	null	O	VBG
2006	null	DATE	CD
in	null	O	IN
spend	null	O	VBN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
13,458	null	MONEY	CD
Sweden	null	LOCATION	NNP
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
9,099	null	MONEY	CD
Sweden	null	LOCATION	NNP
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
8,998	null	MONEY	CD
Bulgaria	null	LOCATION	NNP
offer	null	O	VBG
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
1,200	null	MONEY	CD
Romania	null	LOCATION	NNP
Bulgaria	null	LOCATION	NNP
offer	null	O	VBG
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
1,200	null	MONEY	CD
russian	null	MISC	JJ
bank	null	O	NNS
need	null	O	VBP
say	null	O	VBD
agency	null	O	NN
MOSCOW	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
need	null	O	VBP
total	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
28.4	null	MONEY	CD
russian	null	LOCATION	JJ
bank	null	O	NNS
need	null	O	VBP
total	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
28.4	null	MONEY	CD
japanese	null	MISC	JJ
currency	null	O	NN
against	null	O	IN
Tuesday	null	DATE	NNP
on	null	O	IN
fall	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
yen	null	MONEY	NNS
96.46	null	MONEY	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
boost	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
move	null	O	NN
worth	null	O	NN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
60.28	null	MONEY	CD
german	null	MISC	JJ
french	null	MISC	JJ
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
boost	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
move	null	O	NN
worth	null	O	NN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
60.28	null	MONEY	CD
spanish	null	LOCATION	JJ
french	null	MISC	JJ
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
boost	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
move	null	O	NN
worth	null	O	NN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
60.28	null	MONEY	CD
Greenland	null	LOCATION	NNP
receive	null	O	VBZ
subsidy	null	O	NNS
krone	null	MONEY	NN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
456	null	MONEY	CD
Denmark	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
subsidy	null	O	NNS
krone	null	MONEY	NN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
456	null	MONEY	CD
brazilian	null	MISC	JJ
playmaker	null	O	NN
sign	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
65	null	NUMBER	CD
spanish	null	MISC	JJ
Ser	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
report	null	O	VBD
football	null	O	NN
sign	null	O	NNS
playmaker	null	O	NN
sign	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
65	null	NUMBER	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
government	null	O	NN
offer	null	O	VBZ
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
3.3	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
3.3	null	NUMBER	CD
Bulgaria	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
aid	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
freeze	null	O	VB
total	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
825	null	MONEY	CD
Bulgaria	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
aid	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
freeze	null	O	VB
total	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
1.2	null	MONEY	CD
Bulgaria	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
to	null	O	TO
axe	null	O	VB
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
220	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
250	null	NUMBER	CD
Taiwan	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
operator	null	O	NNS
say	null	O	VBP
make	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
fee	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	O	NNS
dollar	null	O	NNS
25	null	NUMBER	CD
Taiwan	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
dollar	null	O	NNS
25	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
25	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
20	null	NUMBER	CD
irish	null	MISC	JJ
airline	null	O	NN
report	null	O	VBD
loss	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
169	null	MONEY	CD
irish	null	MISC	JJ
airline	null	O	NN
report	null	O	VBD
loss	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
239	null	MONEY	CD
Irish	null	MISC	NNP
Ryanair	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBZ
face	null	O	VBD
loss	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
169	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
150	null	NUMBER	CD
Namibia	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
dollar	null	O	NNS
120,000	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
120,000	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
in	null	O	IN
enhance	null	O	VBN
announce	null	O	VBD
arrange	null	O	VBN
let	null	O	VB
watch	null	O	VBP
owner	null	O	NNS
360	null	NUMBER	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
owner	null	O	NNS
360	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
owner	null	O	NNS
360	null	NUMBER	CD
Ukraine	null	LOCATION	NNP
need	null	O	VBZ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
350	null	MONEY	CD
spanish	null	MISC	JJ
queen	null	O	NN
take	null	O	VBZ
give	null	O	VBD
fly	null	O	VBD
for	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
15	null	MONEY	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
Sofia	null	LOCATION	NNP
give	null	O	VBD
fly	null	O	VBD
for	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
15	null	MONEY	CD
Greenland	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
people	null	O	NNS
on	null	O	IN
meeting	null	O	NN
insist	null	O	VBD
expense	null	O	NN
wife	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
meal	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
spending	null	O	NN
krone	null	O	NN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
190	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
30,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
contributor	null	O	NN
deploy	null	O	VBG
around	null	O	IN
8,300	null	NUMBER	CD
Afghanistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
contributor	null	O	NN
deploy	null	O	VBG
around	null	O	IN
8,300	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
after	null	O	IN
contributor	null	O	NN
deploy	null	O	VBG
around	null	O	IN
8,300	null	NUMBER	CD
south	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
base	null	O	VBN
force	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
part	null	O	NN
as	null	O	IN
deploy	null	O	VBG
around	null	O	IN
8,300	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
250	null	NUMBER	CD
Taiwan	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
dollar	null	O	NNS
25	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
25	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
20	null	NUMBER	CD
Greenland	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
people	null	O	NNS
on	null	O	IN
meeting	null	O	NN
insist	null	O	VBD
expense	null	O	NN
wife	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
meal	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
spending	null	O	NN
krone	null	O	NN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
190	null	MONEY	CD
Greenland	null	LOCATION	NNP
receive	null	O	VBZ
subsidy	null	O	NNS
krone	null	MONEY	NN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
456	null	MONEY	CD
Denmark	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
subsidy	null	O	NNS
krone	null	MONEY	NN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
456	null	MONEY	CD
british	null	LOCATION	JJ
loan	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
5.8	null	MONEY	CD
brazilian	null	MISC	JJ
playmaker	null	O	NN
sign	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
65	null	NUMBER	CD
spanish	null	MISC	JJ
Ser	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
report	null	O	VBD
football	null	O	NN
sign	null	O	NNS
playmaker	null	O	NN
sign	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
65	null	NUMBER	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
side	null	O	NN
Chelsea	null	PERSON	NNP
land	null	O	VBN
deny	null	O	VBD
table	null	O	VBN
bid	null	O	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
85	null	MONEY	CD
english	null	MISC	JJ
side	null	O	NN
Chelsea	null	PERSON	NNP
land	null	O	VBN
deny	null	O	VBD
table	null	O	VBN
bid	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
brazilian	null	MISC	JJ
couple	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
salary	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
10	null	MONEY	CD
brazilian	null	MISC	JJ
for	null	O	IN
bid	null	O	NN
million	null	MONEY	CD
85	null	MONEY	CD
brazilian	null	MISC	JJ
couple	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
salary	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
10	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
complex	null	O	NN
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
2.4	null	NUMBER	CD
Poland	null	LOCATION	NNP
announce	null	O	VBD
sale	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
total	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
zloty	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
82	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Trust	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
sale	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
total	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
zloty	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
82	null	MONEY	CD
Greenland	null	LOCATION	NNP
receive	null	O	VBZ
subsidy	null	O	NNS
krone	null	MONEY	NN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
456	null	MONEY	CD
Denmark	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
subsidy	null	O	NNS
krone	null	MONEY	NN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
456	null	MONEY	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
member	null	O	NN
accuse	null	O	VBN
of	null	O	IN
pay	null	O	VBG
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
580,000	null	MONEY	CD
UK	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Party	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
head	null	O	NN
Farage	null	PERSON	NNP
admit	null	O	VBD
pocket	null	O	VBD
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
2.3	null	MONEY	CD
italian	null	MISC	JJ
deputy	null	O	NNS
earn	null	O	VBP
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
11,700	null	MONEY	CD
italian	null	MISC	JJ
deputy	null	O	NNS
earn	null	O	VBP
take	null	O	VBZ
pocket	null	O	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
1,200	null	MONEY	CD
bulgarian	null	MISC	JJ
counterpart	null	O	NN
take	null	O	VBZ
earn	null	O	VBP
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
11,700	null	MONEY	CD
bulgarian	null	MISC	JJ
counterpart	null	O	NN
take	null	O	VBZ
pocket	null	O	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
1,200	null	MONEY	CD
lithuanian	null	LOCATION	JJ
lawmaker	null	O	NN
pocket	null	O	NNS
take	null	O	VBZ
earn	null	O	VBP
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
11,700	null	MONEY	CD
lithuanian	null	LOCATION	JJ
lawmaker	null	O	NN
pocket	null	O	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
1,200	null	MONEY	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
mep	null	MISC	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
7,000	null	NUMBER	CD
7,670	null	MONEY	CD
german	null	MISC	JJ
french	null	MISC	JJ
mep	null	MISC	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
7,000	null	NUMBER	CD
7,670	null	MONEY	CD
australian	null	MONEY	JJ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
6.48	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
6.48	null	NUMBER	CD
swedish	null	MISC	JJ
lender	null	O	NNS
face	null	O	VBP
estimate	null	O	VBN
lose	null	O	VB
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
16	null	MONEY	CD
swedish	null	MISC	JJ
lender	null	O	NNS
face	null	O	VBP
estimate	null	O	VBN
lose	null	O	VB
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
22.5	null	MONEY	CD
swedish	null	MISC	JJ
bank	null	O	NNS
lose	null	O	VB
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
16	null	MONEY	CD
swedish	null	MISC	JJ
bank	null	O	NNS
lose	null	O	VB
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
22.5	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
discuss	null	O	VB
sale	null	O	NNS
include	null	O	VBG
request	null	O	NN
buy	null	O	VB
to	null	O	TO
fighter	null	O	NNS
F-35	null	O	NNP
75	null	NUMBER	CD
Israel	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
sale	null	O	NNS
include	null	O	VBG
request	null	O	NN
buy	null	O	VB
to	null	O	TO
fighter	null	O	NNS
F-35	null	O	NNP
75	null	NUMBER	CD
israeli	null	MISC	JJ
official	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
expect	null	O	VBN
discuss	null	O	VB
sale	null	O	NNS
include	null	O	VBG
request	null	O	NN
buy	null	O	VB
to	null	O	TO
fighter	null	O	NNS
F-35	null	O	NNP
75	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
1.4	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
245	null	NUMBER	CD
irish	null	MISC	JJ
Ryanair	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
face	null	O	VBD
loss	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
169	null	MONEY	CD
irish	null	MISC	JJ
Ryanair	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
face	null	O	VBD
loss	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
239	null	MONEY	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
double	null	O	VBN
announce	null	O	VBD
spend	null	O	VB
yuan	null	MONEY	NN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
70	null	MONEY	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
export	null	O	VBD
worth	null	O	NN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
9.31	null	MONEY	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
export	null	O	VBD
worth	null	O	NN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
13.2	null	MONEY	CD
Germany	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
crisis	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
symbol	null	O	NN
HRE	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
benefit	null	O	VBN
from	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
102	null	MONEY	CD
Netherlands	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
13	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
13	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
13	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
13	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
13	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
13	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
13	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
13	null	NUMBER	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
Fund	null	O	NNP
in	null	O	IN
invest	null	O	VB
euro	null	O	NNS
bln	null	O	NN
1.5	null	NUMBER	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
Fund	null	O	NNP
in	null	O	IN
invest	null	O	VB
fund	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
invest	null	O	VB
to	null	O	TO
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
1.5	null	MONEY	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
Fund	null	O	NNP
in	null	O	IN
invest	null	O	VB
fund	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
invest	null	O	VB
to	null	O	TO
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
2.1	null	MONEY	CD
Zambian	null	MISC	NNP
plead	null	O	NNS
plead	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
charge	null	O	NNS
link	null	O	VBN
to	null	O	TO
theft	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
3.5	null	MONEY	CD
zambian	null	MISC	JJ
official	null	O	NN
plead	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
charge	null	O	NNS
link	null	O	VBN
to	null	O	TO
theft	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
3.5	null	MONEY	CD
Ukraine	null	LOCATION	NNP
need	null	O	VBZ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
350	null	MONEY	CD
Taiwan	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
30.95	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
30.95	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
Simonyi	null	PERSON	NNP
from	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
25	null	MONEY	CD
Ukraine	null	LOCATION	NNP
need	null	O	VBZ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
350	null	MONEY	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
with	null	O	IN
sign	null	O	VBD
build	null	O	VB
plant	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
82	null	MONEY	CD
Denmark	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
subsidy	null	O	NNS
krone	null	MONEY	NN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
456	null	MONEY	CD
Sweden	null	LOCATION	NNP
as	null	O	IN
investor	null	O	NNS
Fund	null	O	NNP
offer	null	O	VBD
package	null	O	NN
billion	null	MONEY	CD
7.5	null	MONEY	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
Corp	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
company	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
manage	null	O	VBZ
worth	null	O	JJ
rupee	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
63	null	MONEY	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
Corp	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
company	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
manage	null	O	VBZ
worth	null	O	JJ
rupee	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
547	null	MONEY	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
state	null	O	NN
own	null	O	VBZ
end	null	O	VB
own	null	O	VBG
snub	null	O	VBP
worth	null	O	JJ
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
4.5	null	MONEY	CD
Germany	null	LOCATION	NNP
get	null	O	VBN
from	null	O	IN
premium	null	O	NN
worth	null	O	JJ
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
2,500	null	MONEY	CD
Germany	null	LOCATION	NNP
get	null	O	VBN
from	null	O	IN
premium	null	O	NN
worth	null	O	JJ
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
3,580	null	MONEY	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
Bouygues	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
fall	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
28.07	null	MONEY	CD
german	null	MISC	JJ
aid	null	O	NN
avoid	null	O	VB
seek	null	O	VBG
fall	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
1.94	null	MONEY	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Africa	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
megawatt	null	O	NNS
import	null	O	VB
spend	null	O	VBG
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
185,000	null	MONEY	CD
Namibia	null	LOCATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
megawatt	null	O	NNS
megawatt	null	O	NNS
import	null	O	VB
spend	null	O	VBG
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
185,000	null	MONEY	CD
Germany	null	LOCATION	NNP
Landesbanken	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
casualty	null	O	NNS
force	null	O	VBG
tap	null	O	VB
package	null	O	NN
worth	null	O	JJ
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
480	null	MONEY	CD
Germany	null	LOCATION	NNP
Landesbanken	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
casualty	null	O	NNS
force	null	O	VBG
tap	null	O	VB
package	null	O	NN
worth	null	O	JJ
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
685	null	MONEY	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
club	null	O	NN
play	null	O	VB
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
80	null	MONEY	CD
English	null	MISC	NNP
club	null	O	NN
play	null	O	VB
offer	null	O	VB
salary	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
12	null	MONEY	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
partner	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
trade	null	O	NN
around	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
60	null	MONEY	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
partner	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
trade	null	O	NN
around	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
85.4	null	MONEY	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
ahead	null	O	RB
partner	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
trade	null	O	NN
around	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
60	null	MONEY	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
ahead	null	O	RB
partner	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
trade	null	O	NN
around	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
85.4	null	MONEY	CD
japanese	null	MISC	JJ
currency	null	O	NN
against	null	O	IN
climb	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
yen	null	MONEY	NNS
96.30	null	MONEY	CD
dutch	null	MISC	JJ
state	null	O	NN
sell	null	O	VBZ
say	null	O	VBD
sell	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
350	null	MONEY	CD
dutch	null	MISC	JJ
state	null	O	NN
June	null	DATE	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
sell	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
350	null	MONEY	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
Plc	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
Insurance	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
sell	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
350	null	MONEY	CD
dutch	null	MISC	JJ
government	null	O	NN
acquire	null	O	VBD
buy	null	O	VBD
for	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
16.8	null	MONEY	CD
dutch	null	MISC	JJ
operation	null	O	NNS
buy	null	O	VBD
for	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
16.8	null	MONEY	CD
Italy	null	LOCATION	NNP
Unicredit	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
climb	null	O	VBG
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
1.97	null	MONEY	CD
Italy	null	LOCATION	NNP
Unicredit	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
climb	null	O	VBG
gain	null	O	VBG
to	null	O	TO
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
43.41	null	MONEY	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
Generale	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
gain	null	O	VBG
climb	null	O	VBG
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
1.97	null	MONEY	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
Generale	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
gain	null	O	VBG
to	null	O	TO
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
43.41	null	MONEY	CD
Netherlands	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
13	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
13	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
13	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
13	null	NUMBER	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
13	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
13	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
13	null	NUMBER	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
Barclays	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
sell	null	O	VBN
worth	null	O	JJ
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
1.44	null	MONEY	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
supply	null	O	VBD
for	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
437	null	MONEY	CD
Ukraine	null	LOCATION	NNP
supply	null	O	VBD
for	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
437	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
rewarding	null	O	JJ
with	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
3.5	null	MONEY	CD
Serbia	null	LOCATION	NNP
rewarding	null	O	JJ
with	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
3.5	null	MONEY	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
have	null	O	VBZ
troops	null	O	NNS
40,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Japan	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
base	null	O	VBN
troops	null	O	NNS
40,000	null	NUMBER	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
group	null	O	NN
by	null	O	IN
take	null	O	VBN
run	null	O	VBG
keep	null	O	VB
loan	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
1.5	null	MONEY	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
bank	null	O	NN
pump	null	O	VB
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
58	null	MONEY	CD
Sweden	null	LOCATION	NNP
as	null	O	IN
investor	null	O	NNS
Fund	null	O	NNP
offer	null	O	VBD
package	null	O	NN
billion	null	MONEY	CD
7.5	null	MONEY	CD
moroccan	null	MISC	JJ
custom	null	O	NNS
seize	null	O	VBP
seize	null	O	VBD
tonne	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
worth	null	O	JJ
about	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
17.3	null	MONEY	CD
moroccan	null	MISC	JJ
custom	null	O	NNS
seize	null	O	VBP
seize	null	O	VBD
tonne	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
worth	null	O	JJ
about	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
24.5	null	MONEY	CD
moroccan	null	LOCATION	JJ
officer	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
tonne	null	O	NNS
seize	null	O	VBD
tonne	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
worth	null	O	JJ
about	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
17.3	null	MONEY	CD
moroccan	null	LOCATION	JJ
officer	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
tonne	null	O	NNS
seize	null	O	VBD
tonne	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
worth	null	O	JJ
about	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
24.5	null	MONEY	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
supply	null	O	VBD
for	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
437	null	MONEY	CD
Ukraine	null	LOCATION	NNP
supply	null	O	VBD
for	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
437	null	MONEY	CD
Germany	null	LOCATION	NNP
have	null	O	VBN
worth	null	O	JJ
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
2,500	null	MONEY	CD
Germany	null	LOCATION	NNP
have	null	O	VBN
worth	null	O	JJ
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
3,580	null	MONEY	CD
Liechtenstein	null	LOCATION	NNP
center	null	O	NN
by	null	O	IN
management	null	O	NN
under	null	O	IN
asset	null	O	NNS
fall	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
franc	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
225.44	null	MONEY	CD
Liechtenstein	null	LOCATION	NNP
center	null	O	NN
by	null	O	IN
management	null	O	NN
under	null	O	IN
asset	null	O	NNS
fall	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
franc	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
148.4	null	MONEY	CD
Germany	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
employ	null	O	VBZ
Opel	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
give	null	O	VBN
loan	null	O	NN
protect	null	O	VB
provide	null	O	VBG
1.5	null	NUMBER	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
rsa	null	O	NN
28	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
rsa	null	O	NN
28	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
Larsen	null	PERSON	NNP
rise	null	O	VBD
rupee	null	O	NNS
46.55	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
Larsen	null	PERSON	NNP
rise	null	O	VBD
rise	null	O	VBD
rupee	null	O	NNS
9.3	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
DLF	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
rise	null	O	VBD
rupee	null	O	NNS
13.3	null	NUMBER	CD
Bulgaria	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
subsidy	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
800	null	MONEY	CD
Bulgaria	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
subsidy	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
1.1	null	MONEY	CD
Bulgaria	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
subsidy	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
cut	null	O	VBN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
220	null	MONEY	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
go	null	O	VBG
with	null	O	IN
game	null	O	NN
offer	null	O	VBZ
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
500,000	null	MONEY	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
prosecutor	null	O	NNS
euro-candidate	null	MISC	NN
in	null	O	IN
PARIS	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
4	null	DATE	CD
french	null	LOCATION	JJ
prosecutor	null	O	NNS
euro-candidate	null	MISC	NN
in	null	O	IN
PARIS	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
4	null	DATE	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
rsa	null	O	NN
28	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
rsa	null	O	NN
28	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
rsa	null	O	NN
28	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
Technologies	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
fall	null	O	VBD
rupee	null	O	NNS
36.4	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
Technologies	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
fall	null	O	VBD
fall	null	O	VBD
rupee	null	O	NNS
36.3	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
of	null	ORGANIZATION	IN
Bank	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
fall	null	O	VBD
fall	null	O	VBD
rupee	null	O	NNS
36.4	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
of	null	ORGANIZATION	IN
Bank	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
fall	null	O	VBD
rupee	null	O	NNS
36.3	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
discuss	null	O	VB
sale	null	O	NNS
include	null	O	VBG
request	null	O	NN
buy	null	O	VB
to	null	O	TO
fighter	null	O	NNS
F-35	null	O	NNP
75	null	NUMBER	CD
Israel	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
sale	null	O	NNS
include	null	O	VBG
request	null	O	NN
buy	null	O	VB
to	null	O	TO
fighter	null	O	NNS
F-35	null	O	NNP
75	null	NUMBER	CD
israeli	null	MISC	JJ
official	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
expect	null	O	VBN
discuss	null	O	VB
sale	null	O	NNS
include	null	O	VBG
request	null	O	NN
buy	null	O	VB
to	null	O	TO
fighter	null	O	NNS
F-35	null	O	NNP
75	null	NUMBER	CD
Latvia	null	LOCATION	NNP
fail	null	O	VBZ
force	null	O	VBN
do	null	O	VB
without	null	O	IN
tranche	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
2.0	null	MONEY	CD
India	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
report	null	O	VBD
jump	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
rupee	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
21.61	null	MONEY	CD
India	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
report	null	O	VBD
jump	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
rupee	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
460.7	null	MONEY	CD
India	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
report	null	O	VBD
jump	null	O	VBD
in	null	O	IN
year	null	DATE	NN
on	null	O	IN
revenue	null	O	NNS
climb	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
rupee	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
81.37	null	MONEY	CD
lithuanian	null	MISC	JJ
host	null	O	NN
June	null	DATE	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
swiss	null	MONEY	JJ
franc	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
26	null	MONEY	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
for	null	O	IN
budget	null	O	NN
double	null	O	VBG
franc	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
26	null	MONEY	CD
Ukraine	null	LOCATION	NNP
pay	null	O	VB
Ukraine	null	LOCATION	NNP
pay	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
May	null	DATE	NNP
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
352	null	MONEY	CD
russian	null	MISC	JJ
bill	null	O	NN
pay	null	O	VB
Ukraine	null	LOCATION	NNP
pay	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
May	null	DATE	NNP
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
352	null	MONEY	CD
Ukraine	null	LOCATION	NNP
pay	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
May	null	DATE	NNP
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
352	null	MONEY	CD
russian	null	MISC	JJ
bill	null	O	NN
pay	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
May	null	DATE	NNP
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
352	null	MONEY	CD
russian	null	LOCATION	JJ
Gazprom	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
payment	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
authorise	null	O	VBN
release	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
hryvnia	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
350	null	MONEY	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
company	null	O	NNS
invest	null	O	VB
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
704	null	MONEY	CD
Tajikistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
construction	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
include	null	O	VBZ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
457	null	MONEY	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
bank	null	O	NN
pump	null	O	VB
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
58	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Reserve	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
establish	null	O	VBN
scheme	null	O	NNS
with	null	O	IN
compare	null	O	VBN
small	null	O	JJ
plan	null	O	VBZ
buy	null	O	VB
underpin	null	O	VB
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
60	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Reserve	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
establish	null	O	VBN
scheme	null	O	NNS
with	null	O	IN
compare	null	O	VBN
small	null	O	JJ
plan	null	O	VBZ
buy	null	O	VB
underpin	null	O	VB
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
85	null	MONEY	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
Reserve	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
establish	null	O	VBN
scheme	null	O	NNS
with	null	O	IN
compare	null	O	VBN
small	null	O	JJ
plan	null	O	VBZ
buy	null	O	VB
underpin	null	O	VB
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
60	null	MONEY	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
Reserve	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
establish	null	O	VBN
scheme	null	O	NNS
with	null	O	IN
compare	null	O	VBN
small	null	O	JJ
plan	null	O	VBZ
buy	null	O	VB
underpin	null	O	VB
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
85	null	MONEY	CD
USA	null	O	NNP
CAN	null	O	NNP
1.7	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	O	NNP
CAN	null	O	NNP
1.7	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	O	NNP
CAN	null	O	NNP
1.7	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	O	NNP
CAN	null	O	NNP
1.7	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
CAN	null	O	NNP
1.7	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
CAN	null	O	NNP
1.7	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
CAN	null	O	NNP
1.7	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
CAN	null	O	NNP
1.7	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	O	NNP
CAN	null	O	NNP
1.7	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	O	NNP
CAN	null	O	NNP
1.7	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
CAN	null	O	NNP
1.7	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	O	NNP
CAN	null	O	NNP
1.7	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	O	NNP
CAN	null	O	NNP
1.7	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
CAN	null	O	NNP
1.7	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
on	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
70	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
on	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
above	null	O	IN
soar	null	O	VBZ
oil	null	O	NN
spike	null	O	VBN
above	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
70	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
slow	null	O	VBD
news	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
reach	null	O	VBG
spike	null	O	VBN
oil	null	O	NN
soar	null	O	VBZ
above	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
70	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
slow	null	O	VBD
news	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
reach	null	O	VBG
spike	null	O	VBN
above	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
70	null	MONEY	CD
ukrainian	null	MISC	JJ
Yushchenko	null	PERSON	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
authorise	null	O	VBN
release	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
hryvnia	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
350	null	MONEY	CD
russian	null	LOCATION	JJ
Gazprom	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
payment	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
authorise	null	O	VBN
release	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
hryvnia	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
350	null	MONEY	CD
swedish	null	MISC	JJ
guarantee	null	O	NNS
approve	null	O	VBZ
say	null	O	VBD
approve	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
500	null	MONEY	CD
swedish	null	MISC	JJ
guarantee	null	O	NNS
approve	null	O	VBZ
say	null	O	VBD
approve	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
709	null	MONEY	CD
swedish	null	MISC	JJ
guarantee	null	O	NNS
approve	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
500	null	MONEY	CD
swedish	null	MISC	JJ
guarantee	null	O	NNS
approve	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
709	null	MONEY	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
operation	null	O	NNS
cover	null	O	VBG
venture	null	O	NN
agree	null	O	VBD
in	null	O	IN
deal	null	O	NN
expect	null	O	VBN
save	null	O	VB
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
10	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
10	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
5.8	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
tie-up	null	O	NN
billion	null	MONEY	CD
19.5	null	MONEY	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
Chinalco	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
with	null	O	IN
tie-up	null	O	NN
billion	null	MONEY	CD
19.5	null	MONEY	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
Chinalco	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
with	null	O	IN
tie-up	null	O	NN
cancel	null	O	VBZ
in	null	O	IN
favor	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
venture	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
Billiton	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
issue	null	O	NN
billion	null	MONEY	CD
15.2	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
issue	null	O	NN
billion	null	MONEY	CD
15.2	null	MONEY	CD
Ukraine	null	LOCATION	NNP
pay	null	O	VB
Ukraine	null	LOCATION	NNP
pay	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
May	null	DATE	NNP
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
352	null	MONEY	CD
russian	null	MISC	JJ
bill	null	O	NN
pay	null	O	VB
Ukraine	null	LOCATION	NNP
pay	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
May	null	DATE	NNP
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
352	null	MONEY	CD
Ukraine	null	LOCATION	NNP
pay	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
May	null	DATE	NNP
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
352	null	MONEY	CD
russian	null	MISC	JJ
bill	null	O	NN
pay	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
May	null	DATE	NNP
of	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
352	null	MONEY	CD
russian	null	LOCATION	JJ
Gazprom	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
payment	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
authorise	null	O	VBN
release	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
hryvnia	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
million	null	MONEY	CD
350	null	MONEY	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
deal	null	O	VB
scrap	null	O	VBZ
announce	null	O	VBZ
issue	null	O	NN
scrap	null	O	VBN
deal	null	O	NN
dollar	null	O	NN
billion	null	MONEY	CD
19.5	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NN
billion	null	MONEY	CD
19.5	null	MONEY	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
Chinalco	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
with	null	O	IN
scrap	null	O	VBN
deal	null	O	NN
dollar	null	O	NN
billion	null	MONEY	CD
19.5	null	MONEY	CD
USA	null	O	NNP
Na	null	O	NNP
1.7	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Na	null	O	NNP
1.7	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	LOCATION	NNP
Na	null	O	NNP
1.7	null	NUMBER	CD
USA	null	O	NNP
Na	null	O	NNP
1.7	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
Golf	null	O	NNP
make	null	O	VBZ
fire	null	O	VBD
share	null	O	VB
after	null	O	IN
round	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
Classic	null	MISC	NNP
1.7	null	NUMBER	CD
american	null	MISC	JJ
McPherson	null	PERSON	NNP
with	null	O	IN
share	null	O	VB
after	null	O	IN
round	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
Classic	null	MISC	NNP
1.7	null	NUMBER	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
Generale	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
gain	null	O	VBG
close	null	O	VB
at	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
44.69	null	MONEY	CD
Germany	null	LOCATION	NNP
Bank	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Generale	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
gain	null	O	VBG
close	null	O	VB
at	null	O	IN
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
44.69	null	MONEY	CD
australian	null	MONEY	JJ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
billion	null	MONEY	CD
6.56	null	MONEY	CD
australian	null	MISC	JJ
dollar	null	O	NN
higher	null	O	JJR
at	null	O	IN
cent	null	O	NNS
80.46	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
cent	null	O	NNS
80.46	null	NUMBER	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
Chinalco	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
favor	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
venture	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
Billiton	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
issue	null	O	NN
billion	null	MONEY	CD
15.2	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
issue	null	O	NN
billion	null	MONEY	CD
15.2	null	MONEY	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
19.5	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
195	null	NUMBER	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
firm	null	O	NN
by	null	O	IN
investment	null	O	NN
which	null	O	WDT
dollar	null	O	NNS
million	null	NUMBER	CD
195	null	NUMBER	CD
australian	null	MISC	JJ
dollar	null	O	NNS
28.29	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
5.8	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
hand	null	O	VB
as	null	O	IN
part	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
deal	null	O	NN
which	null	O	WDT
yield	null	O	VB
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
10	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
yield	null	O	VB
which	null	O	WDT
deal	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
part	null	O	NN
as	null	O	IN
hand	null	O	VB
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
5.8	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
billion	null	NUMBER	CD
10	null	NUMBER	CD
australian	null	MONEY	JJ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
74.86	null	MONEY	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
Motors	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
rise	null	O	VBD
rupee	null	O	NNS
19.6	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
Motors	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
rise	null	O	VBD
rise	null	O	VBD
rupee	null	O	NNS
64.3	null	NUMBER	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
Technologies	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
rise	null	O	VBD
rupee	null	O	NNS
63.5	null	NUMBER	CD
America	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
of	null	ORGANIZATION	IN
Bank	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
stake	null	O	NN
sell	null	O	VBN
