italian	null	O	JJ
Statistics	null	ORGANIZATION	NNPS
Office	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
accord	null	O	VBG
high	null	O	JJ
at	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
6.8	null	PERCENT	CD
italian	null	O	JJ
Statistics	null	ORGANIZATION	NNPS
Office	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
accord	null	O	VBG
high	null	O	JJ
expect	null	O	VBN
rise	null	O	VB
to	null	O	TO
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
8.4	null	PERCENT	CD
italian	null	O	JJ
Statistics	null	ORGANIZATION	NNPS
Office	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
accord	null	O	VBG
high	null	O	JJ
expect	null	O	VBN
rise	null	O	VB
reach	null	O	VBG
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
10.7	null	PERCENT	CD
Italy	null	LOCATION	NNP
rate	null	O	NN
high	null	O	JJ
at	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
6.8	null	PERCENT	CD
Italy	null	LOCATION	NNP
rate	null	O	NN
high	null	O	JJ
expect	null	O	VBN
rise	null	O	VB
to	null	O	TO
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
8.4	null	PERCENT	CD
Italy	null	LOCATION	NNP
rate	null	O	NN
high	null	O	JJ
expect	null	O	VBN
rise	null	O	VB
reach	null	O	VBG
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
10.7	null	PERCENT	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
with	null	O	IN
compare	null	O	VBN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
73	null	PERCENT	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
97	null	PERCENT	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
with	null	O	IN
compare	null	O	VBN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
73	null	PERCENT	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
97	null	PERCENT	CD
U.S.	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
Pound	null	MONEY	NNP
dollar	null	O	NN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	O	NNS
ftse	null	O	VBP
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.5	null	PERCENT	CD
U.S.	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	O	NNS
ftse	null	O	VBP
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.5	null	PERCENT	CD
japanese	null	MONEY	JJ
yen	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	O	NN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
dollar	null	O	NNS
ftse	null	O	VBP
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.5	null	PERCENT	CD
U.S.	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
ftse	null	O	VBP
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.5	null	PERCENT	CD
North	null	LOCATION	NNP
future	null	O	NNS
rate	null	O	NN
5,190.24	null	NUMBER	CD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.5	null	PERCENT	CD
U.S.	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
rate	null	O	NN
5,190.24	null	NUMBER	CD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.5	null	PERCENT	CD
U.S.	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
rate	null	O	NN
5,190.24	null	NUMBER	CD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.5	null	PERCENT	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
rate	null	O	NN
5,190.24	null	NUMBER	CD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.5	null	PERCENT	CD
Germany	null	LOCATION	NNP
production	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
Ministry	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
statistics	null	O	NNS
to	null	O	TO
accord	null	O	VBG
hit	null	O	VBD
rise	null	O	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
22.2	null	PERCENT	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
sell	null	O	VBP
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
70	null	PERCENT	CD
Malaysia	null	LOCATION	NNP
for	null	O	IN
contract	null	O	VBD
at	null	O	IN
rate	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
year	null	DATE	NN
3.9	null	PERCENT	CD
Malaysia	null	LOCATION	NNP
for	null	O	IN
contract	null	O	VBD
compare	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
contraction	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
6.2	null	PERCENT	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
economy	null	O	NN
expand	null	O	VBD
year	null	DURATION	NN
8.9	null	PERCENT	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
economy	null	O	NN
expand	null	O	VBD
year	null	DURATION	NN
year	null	DURATION	NN
7.7	null	PERCENT	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
Bureau	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
statistics	null	O	NNS
to	null	O	TO
accord	null	O	VBG
expand	null	O	VBD
year	null	DURATION	NN
8.9	null	PERCENT	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
Bureau	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
statistics	null	O	NNS
to	null	O	TO
accord	null	O	VBG
expand	null	O	VBD
year	null	DURATION	NN
year	null	DURATION	NN
7.7	null	PERCENT	CD
brazilian	null	MISC	JJ
Institute	null	O	NNP
to	null	O	TO
accord	null	O	VBG
be	null	O	VBD
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
1.2	null	PERCENT	CD
Brazil	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
sale	null	O	NNS
hit	null	O	VBD
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
19.6	null	PERCENT	CD
Brazil	null	LOCATION	NNP
economy	null	O	NN
grow	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
year	null	DATE	NN
3.5	null	PERCENT	CD
Brazil	null	LOCATION	NNP
economy	null	O	NN
grow	null	O	VB
after	null	O	IN
contract	null	O	VBG
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.7	null	PERCENT	CD
Ukraine	null	LOCATION	NNP
match	null	O	NN
miss	null	O	VBD
choice	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
most	null	O	JJS
of	null	O	IN
start	null	O	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
100	null	PERCENT	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
start	null	O	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
100	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
own	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
60	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
slide	null	O	NN
continue	null	O	VBZ
fall	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
28	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
revenue	null	O	NN
fall	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
28	null	PERCENT	CD
America	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
of	null	ORGANIZATION	IN
Association	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
accord	null	O	VBG
fall	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
28	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
automaker	null	O	NN
close	null	O	VB
slash	null	O	NNS
lower	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
sale	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
term	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
help	null	O	VB
restructure	null	O	NN
receive	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
60	null	PERCENT	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
government	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VB
receive	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
12	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
show	null	O	VBD
fall	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.1	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
show	null	O	VBD
fall	null	O	VBD
rise	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.5	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
spending	null	O	NN
continue	null	O	VBZ
fall	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.1	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
spending	null	O	NN
fall	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.1	null	PERCENT	CD
Americans	null	MISC	NNPS
among	null	O	IN
highlight	null	O	VBG
show	null	O	VBD
fall	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.1	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
rate	null	O	NN
rise	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
high	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
5.7	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
rate	null	O	NN
rise	null	O	VBD
compare	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
4.5	null	PERCENT	CD
Pakistani	null	MISC	NNP
official	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
end	null	O	VB
with	null	O	IN
remain	null	O	VBG
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
10	null	PERCENT	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
manufacturing	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
expansion	null	O	NN
show	null	O	VBD
say	null	O	VBD
close	null	O	VBD
close	null	O	VB
Kong	null	LOCATION	NNP
3.95	null	PERCENT	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
send	null	O	VBD
plunge	null	O	VBZ
send	null	O	VBD
from	null	O	IN
abroad	null	O	RB
fall	null	O	VBD
compare	null	O	VBN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
19	null	PERCENT	CD
Mexico	null	LOCATION	NNP
City	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
plunge	null	O	VBZ
send	null	O	VBD
from	null	O	IN
abroad	null	O	RB
fall	null	O	VBD
compare	null	O	VBN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
19	null	PERCENT	CD
south	null	O	NN
hit	null	O	VBD
fall	null	O	VBD
compare	null	O	VBN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
19	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
border	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
south	null	O	NN
hit	null	O	VBD
fall	null	O	VBD
compare	null	O	VBN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
19	null	PERCENT	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	RB
SINGAPORE	null	LOCATION	NNP
2.19	null	PERCENT	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	RB
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VBD
higher	null	O	JJR
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
2.19	null	PERCENT	CD
SINGAPORE	null	LOCATION	NNP
2.19	null	PERCENT	CD
SINGAPORE	null	LOCATION	NNP
close	null	O	RB
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VBD
higher	null	O	JJR
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
2.19	null	PERCENT	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	RB
SINGAPORE	null	LOCATION	NNP
2.19	null	PERCENT	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VBD
higher	null	O	JJR
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
2.19	null	PERCENT	CD
Taiwan	null	LOCATION	NNP
order	null	O	NNS
fall	null	O	VBD
year	null	DURATION	NN
20.90	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
to	null	O	TO
fall	null	O	VBD
year	null	DURATION	NN
20.90	null	PERCENT	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	RB
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
2.19	null	PERCENT	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	RB
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VBD
higher	null	O	JJR
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
2.19	null	PERCENT	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
2.19	null	PERCENT	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
close	null	O	RB
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VBD
higher	null	O	JJR
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
2.19	null	PERCENT	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	RB
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
2.19	null	PERCENT	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VBD
higher	null	O	JJR
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
2.19	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Congress	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
before	null	O	IN
put	null	O	VBN
bill	null	O	NN
under	null	O	IN
reduce	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
17	null	PERCENT	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
reduce	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
17	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
icon	null	O	NN
enter	null	O	VBZ
process	null	O	NN
aim	null	O	VBG
cut	null	O	VB
reduce	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
50	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
give	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
60	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
give	null	O	VB
provide	null	O	VB
receive	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
12	null	PERCENT	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
government	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VB
give	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
60	null	PERCENT	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
government	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VB
receive	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
12	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
own	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
60	null	PERCENT	CD
Indonesia	null	LOCATION	NNP
rate	null	O	NN
ease	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
6.04	null	PERCENT	CD
Indonesia	null	LOCATION	NNP
rate	null	O	NN
ease	null	O	VBD
from	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
7.31	null	PERCENT	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
law	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
shake-up	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
include	null	O	VBD
measure	null	O	NN
oppose	null	O	VBP
two-third	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
those	null	O	DT
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
64	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
industry	null	O	NN
performance	null	O	NN
amid	null	O	IN
fall	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
45	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Treasury	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
propose	null	O	VBN
plan	null	O	NN
approve	null	O	VBD
creditor	null	O	NNS
hold	null	O	VBG
about	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
54	null	PERCENT	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
law	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
reform	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
include	null	O	VBD
measure	null	O	NN
oppose	null	O	VBP
two-third	null	ORDINAL	JJ
of	null	O	IN
Spaniards	null	O	NNPS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
64	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
icon	null	O	NN
enter	null	O	VBZ
with	null	O	IN
billion	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
financing	null	O	NN
agreement	null	O	NNS
cut	null	O	VB
reduce	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
50	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
show	null	O	VBD
fall	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.1	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
show	null	O	VBD
fall	null	O	VBD
rise	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.5	null	PERCENT	CD
Pakistani	null	MISC	NNP
official	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
end	null	O	VB
with	null	O	IN
remain	null	O	VBG
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
10	null	PERCENT	CD
Kuwait	null	LOCATION	NNP
constitute	null	O	VBP
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
10	null	PERCENT	CD
Kuwait	null	LOCATION	NNP
pump	null	O	VBG
contribute	null	O	VBZ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
95	null	PERCENT	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
economy	null	O	NN
shrink	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
5.4	null	PERCENT	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
registration	null	O	NNS
fall	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
38.7	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
icon	null	O	NN
enter	null	O	VBZ
with	null	O	IN
billion	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
financing	null	O	NN
agreement	null	O	NNS
cut	null	O	VB
reduce	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
50	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
give	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
60	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
give	null	O	VB
provide	null	O	VB
receive	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
12	null	PERCENT	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
government	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VB
give	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
60	null	PERCENT	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
government	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VB
receive	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
12	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
automaker	null	O	NN
close	null	O	VB
slash	null	O	NNS
lower	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
sale	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
term	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
indian	null	MISC	JJ
dive	null	O	NN
plunge	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
33	null	PERCENT	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
unlike	null	O	IN
account	null	O	VBP
for	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
15	null	PERCENT	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
economy	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
15	null	PERCENT	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
carmaker	null	O	NN
report	null	O	VBD
jump	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
15.8	null	PERCENT	CD
South	null	O	NNP
India	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
report	null	O	VBD
rise	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
8.4	null	PERCENT	CD
India	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
report	null	O	VBD
rise	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
8.4	null	PERCENT	CD
south	null	LOCATION	JJ
country	null	O	NN
carmaker	null	O	NN
India	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
report	null	O	VBD
rise	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
8.4	null	PERCENT	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
economy	null	O	NN
grow	null	O	VBD
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
6.7	null	PERCENT	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Securities	null	ORGANIZATION	NNPS
say	null	O	VBD
hike	null	O	VBN
to	null	O	TO
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
7.0	null	PERCENT	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Securities	null	ORGANIZATION	NNPS
say	null	O	VBD
hike	null	O	VBN
from	null	O	IN
earlier	null	O	RBR
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
5.5	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
share	null	O	NN
see	null	O	VBN
fall	null	DATE	NN
from	null	O	IN
peak	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
54	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
share	null	O	NN
see	null	O	VBN
fall	null	DATE	NN
to	null	O	TO
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
22	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
network	null	O	NN
shrink	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
42	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
plant	null	O	NNS
cut	null	O	VB
shrink	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
42	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
prowess	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
symbol	null	O	NN
once	null	DATE	RB
enter	null	O	VBZ
process	null	O	NN
aim	null	O	VBG
for	null	O	IN
so	null	O	RB
bankruptcy	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
financing	null	O	NN
agreement	null	O	NNS
cut	null	O	VB
reduce	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
50	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
give	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
60	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
give	null	O	VB
provide	null	O	VB
receive	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
12	null	PERCENT	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
government	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VB
give	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
60	null	PERCENT	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
government	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VB
receive	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
12	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
automaker	null	O	NN
close	null	O	VB
slash	null	O	NNS
lower	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
sale	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
term	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
Malaysia	null	LOCATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
share	null	O	VBN
Strait	null	LOCATION	NNP
through	null	O	IN
pass	null	O	VBP
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
30	null	PERCENT	CD
Indonesia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Malaysia	null	LOCATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
share	null	O	VBN
Strait	null	LOCATION	NNP
through	null	O	IN
pass	null	O	VBP
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
30	null	PERCENT	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
Malaysia	null	LOCATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
share	null	O	VBN
Strait	null	LOCATION	NNP
through	null	O	IN
pass	null	O	VBP
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
30	null	PERCENT	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
Bank	null	O	NNP
be	null	O	VBZ
expect	null	O	VBN
keep	null	O	VB
rate	null	O	NNS
unchanged	null	O	JJ
at	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.5	null	PERCENT	CD
Thailand	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
sell	null	O	VBN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
95	null	PERCENT	CD
Laos	null	LOCATION	NNP
revenue	null	O	NNS
estimate	null	O	VBN
sell	null	O	VBN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
95	null	PERCENT	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
GDP	null	O	NNP
fall	null	O	VBZ
fall	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
5.4	null	PERCENT	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
GDP	null	O	NNP
fall	null	O	VBZ
fall	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
5.4	null	PERCENT	CD
Canada	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
provide	null	O	VBN
show	null	O	VBD
plunge	null	O	VBN
less	null	O	JJR
than	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
6.7	null	PERCENT	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
in	null	O	IN
contract	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
5.7	null	PERCENT	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
neighbor	null	O	NN
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
in	null	O	IN
contract	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
5.7	null	PERCENT	CD
Ireland	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
18	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	ORGANIZATION	NNPS
AUS	null	O	NNP
18	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
18	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
18	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
18	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
18	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
18	null	NUMBER	CD
italian	null	MISC	JJ
company	null	O	NN
give	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
20	null	PERCENT	CD
Ireland	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
18	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNPS
AUS	null	O	NNP
18	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
18	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
18	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
18	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
18	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
18	null	NUMBER	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
GDP	null	O	NNP
fall	null	O	VBZ
fall	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
5.4	null	PERCENT	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
GDP	null	O	NNP
fall	null	O	VBZ
fall	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
5.4	null	PERCENT	CD
italian	null	MISC	JJ
company	null	O	NN
give	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
20	null	PERCENT	CD
Japan	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
lower	null	O	JJR
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
21.6	null	PERCENT	CD
Japan	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
lower	null	O	JJR
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
lower	null	O	JJR
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
35	null	PERCENT	CD
Japan	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
lower	null	O	JJR
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
39	null	PERCENT	CD
Japan	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
lower	null	O	JJR
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
17	null	PERCENT	CD
Kazakhstan	null	LOCATION	NNP
hold	null	O	VBZ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
20	null	PERCENT	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
border	null	O	VBG
republic	null	O	NN
Kazakhstan	null	LOCATION	NNP
hold	null	O	VBZ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
20	null	PERCENT	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
border	null	O	VBG
republic	null	O	NN
Kazakhstan	null	LOCATION	NNP
hold	null	O	VBZ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
20	null	PERCENT	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
overtake	null	O	VBG
producer	null	O	NN
aim	null	O	VBZ
hold	null	O	VBZ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
20	null	PERCENT	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
overtake	null	O	VBG
producer	null	O	NN
aim	null	O	VBZ
hold	null	O	VBZ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
20	null	PERCENT	CD
malaysian	null	MISC	JJ
share	null	O	NNS
rise	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
1.67	null	PERCENT	CD
malaysian	null	MISC	JJ
share	null	O	NNS
LUMPUR	null	LOCATION	NNP
1.67	null	PERCENT	CD
Pakistani	null	MISC	NNP
official	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
end	null	O	VB
with	null	O	IN
remain	null	O	VBG
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
10	null	PERCENT	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
Bank	null	O	NNP
be	null	O	VBZ
expect	null	O	VBN
keep	null	O	VB
rate	null	O	NNS
unchanged	null	O	JJ
at	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.5	null	PERCENT	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
sale	null	O	NNS
drop	null	O	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
38.7	null	PERCENT	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
sale	null	O	NNS
drop	null	O	NN
show	null	O	VBD
fall	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
38.7	null	PERCENT	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
registration	null	O	NNS
fall	null	O	VBD
show	null	O	VBD
drop	null	O	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
38.7	null	PERCENT	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
registration	null	O	NNS
fall	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
38.7	null	PERCENT	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
registration	null	O	NNS
be	null	O	VBD
by	null	O	IN
unit	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
42.7	null	PERCENT	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
sector	null	O	NN
third-biggest	null	O	JJ
account	null	O	NNS
for	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
10	null	PERCENT	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
sector	null	O	NN
third-biggest	null	O	JJ
account	null	O	NNS
for	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
15	null	PERCENT	CD
armenian	null	ORGANIZATION	JJ
Congress	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
take	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
17	null	PERCENT	CD
Armenia	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
member	null	O	NN
Republicans	null	MISC	NNPS
poll	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
46	null	PERCENT	CD
Armenia	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
member	null	O	NN
garner	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
22	null	PERCENT	CD
australian	null	MISC	JJ
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	RB
SYDNEY	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
1	null	DATE	CD
australian	null	MISC	JJ
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	RB
SYDNEY	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
1	null	DATE	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
operation	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
16	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
court	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
file	null	O	VBN
emerge	null	O	VBZ
receive	null	O	VB
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
11.7	null	PERCENT	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
operation	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
19	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
automaker	null	O	NN
close	null	O	VB
slash	null	O	NNS
lower	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
sale	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
term	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
help	null	O	VB
restructure	null	O	NN
receive	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
60	null	PERCENT	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
government	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VB
receive	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
12	null	PERCENT	CD
russian	null	MISC	JJ
Sberbank	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
own	null	O	VB
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
35	null	PERCENT	CD
russian	null	MISC	JJ
Sberbank	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
own	null	O	VB
control	null	O	VB
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
20	null	PERCENT	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
International	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
control	null	O	VB
own	null	O	VB
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
35	null	PERCENT	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
International	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
control	null	O	VB
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
20	null	PERCENT	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
post	null	O	NNS
Monday	null	DATE	NNP
post	null	O	VBD
show	null	O	VBD
shrink	null	O	VBD
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
5.4	null	PERCENT	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
Monday	null	DATE	NNP
post	null	O	VBD
show	null	O	VBD
shrink	null	O	VBD
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
5.4	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
recession	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
impact	null	O	NN
ripple	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
note	null	O	VBG
shrink	null	O	VBN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
5.7	null	PERCENT	CD
Canada	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
note	null	O	VBG
shrink	null	O	VBN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
5.7	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
GDP	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
shrink	null	O	VBN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
5.7	null	PERCENT	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
export	null	O	NNS
fall	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
8.7	null	PERCENT	CD
Pakistani	null	MISC	NNP
official	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
end	null	O	VB
with	null	O	IN
remain	null	O	VBG
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
10	null	PERCENT	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
post	null	O	VBZ
,2	null	NUMBER	CD
show	null	O	VBZ
plunge	null	O	VBN
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
5.4	null	PERCENT	CD
indian	null	MISC	JJ
dive	null	O	NN
slide	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
33	null	PERCENT	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
export	null	O	NNS
for	null	O	IN
dive	null	O	NN
slide	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
33	null	PERCENT	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
15	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
court	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
file	null	O	VBN
emerge	null	O	VBZ
receive	null	O	VB
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
11.7	null	PERCENT	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VB
shanghaus	null	O	NNS
3.36	null	PERCENT	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VB
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
3.36	null	PERCENT	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VB
shanghaus	null	O	NNS
3.36	null	PERCENT	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
3.36	null	PERCENT	CD
Taiwan	null	LOCATION	NNP
tie	null	O	NNS
over	null	O	IN
confidence	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
rise	null	O	VBN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
33	null	PERCENT	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
with	null	O	IN
tie	null	O	NNS
over	null	O	IN
confidence	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
rise	null	O	VBN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
33	null	PERCENT	CD
SINGAPORE	null	LOCATION	NNP
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
2.19	null	PERCENT	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
pay	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
stake	null	O	NN
13.76	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
million	null	NUMBER	CD
dollar	null	O	NNS
pay	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
stake	null	O	NN
13.76	null	PERCENT	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
Obama	null	PERSON	NNP
rating	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
opinion	null	O	NN
have	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
33	null	PERCENT	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
of	null	O	IN
those	null	O	DT
beat	null	O	VBP
rating	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
opinion	null	O	NN
have	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
33	null	PERCENT	CD
Kuwait	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
point	null	O	NNS
by	null	O	IN
beat	null	O	VBP
rating	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
opinion	null	O	NN
have	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
33	null	PERCENT	CD
Jordan	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
point	null	O	NNS
point	null	O	NNS
by	null	O	IN
beat	null	O	VBP
rating	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
opinion	null	O	NN
have	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
33	null	PERCENT	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
Emirates	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
point	null	O	NNS
point	null	O	NNS
by	null	O	IN
beat	null	O	VBP
rating	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
opinion	null	O	NN
have	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
33	null	PERCENT	CD
Arabia	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
point	null	O	NNS
point	null	O	NNS
by	null	O	IN
beat	null	O	VBP
rating	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
opinion	null	O	NN
have	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
33	null	PERCENT	CD
Egypt	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
point	null	O	NNS
point	null	O	NNS
by	null	O	IN
beat	null	O	VBP
rating	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
opinion	null	O	NN
have	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
33	null	PERCENT	CD
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
point	null	O	NNS
by	null	O	IN
beat	null	O	VBP
rating	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
opinion	null	O	NN
have	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
33	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
network	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
sale	null	O	NNS
reach	null	O	VBP
profitable	null	O	JJ
lower	null	O	VBN
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
obtain	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
60	null	PERCENT	CD
japanese	null	MISC	JJ
price	null	O	NNS
giant	null	O	NN
between	null	O	IN
deal	null	O	NN
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
33	null	NUMBER	CD
44	null	PERCENT	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
company	null	O	NNS
demand	null	O	VBN
slash	null	O	VBN
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
chinese	null	LOCATION	JJ
company	null	O	NNS
give	null	O	VB
driver	null	O	NN
import	null	O	NNS
account	null	O	VBP
for	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
50	null	PERCENT	CD
Brazil	null	LOCATION	NNP
CVRD	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Billiton	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
with	null	O	IN
reach	null	O	VBN
2005	null	DATE	CD
in	null	O	IN
spike	null	O	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
9.5	null	PERCENT	CD
Brazil	null	LOCATION	NNP
CVRD	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Billiton	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
with	null	O	IN
reach	null	O	VBN
2005	null	DATE	CD
in	null	O	IN
spike	null	O	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
rise	null	O	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
19	null	PERCENT	CD
Brazil	null	LOCATION	NNP
CVRD	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Billiton	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
with	null	O	IN
reach	null	O	VBN
2005	null	DATE	CD
in	null	O	IN
spike	null	O	NN
71.5	null	PERCENT	CD
Indonesia	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
cut	null	O	VB
to	null	O	TO
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
7.0	null	PERCENT	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VB
shanghaus	null	O	NNS
3.36	null	PERCENT	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VB
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
3.36	null	PERCENT	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VB
shanghaus	null	O	NNS
3.36	null	PERCENT	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
3.36	null	PERCENT	CD
Italy	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
vote	null	O	VBG
make	null	O	VBG
one	null	NUMBER	CD
may	null	DATE	MD
cite	null	O	VBN
by	null	O	IN
Berlusconi	null	PERSON	NNP
suggest	null	O	VBD
take	null	O	VB
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
icon	null	O	NN
enter	null	O	VBZ
process	null	O	NN
aim	null	O	VBG
cut	null	O	VB
reduce	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
50	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
give	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
60	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
give	null	O	VB
provide	null	O	VB
receive	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
12	null	PERCENT	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
government	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VB
give	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
60	null	PERCENT	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
government	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VB
receive	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
12	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
automaker	null	O	NN
close	null	O	VB
slash	null	O	NNS
lower	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
sale	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
term	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
3.36	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
icon	null	O	NN
enter	null	O	VBZ
process	null	O	NN
aim	null	O	VBG
for	null	O	IN
bankruptcy	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
financing	null	O	NN
agreement	null	O	NNS
cut	null	O	VB
reduce	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
50	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
give	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
60	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
give	null	O	VB
provide	null	O	VB
receive	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
12	null	PERCENT	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
government	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VB
give	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
60	null	PERCENT	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
government	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VB
receive	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
12	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
automaker	null	O	NN
close	null	O	VB
slash	null	O	NNS
lower	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
sale	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
term	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
Ireland	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
18	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNPS
AUS	null	O	NNP
18	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
18	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
18	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
18	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
18	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	O	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
18	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
18	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
18	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
AUS	null	O	NNP
18	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
president	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
approval	null	O	NN
be	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
25	null	PERCENT	CD
Egypt	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
25	null	PERCENT	CD
Arabia	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
29	null	PERCENT	CD
Arabia	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
from	null	O	IN
rating	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
May	null	DATE	NNP
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
six	null	NUMBER	CD
12	null	PERCENT	CD
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
decline	null	O	VBD
fall	null	O	VBD
from	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
13	null	PERCENT	CD
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
decline	null	O	VBD
from	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
22	null	PERCENT	CD
Tunisia	null	LOCATION	NNP
see	null	O	VBD
with	null	O	IN
rise	null	O	VBG
to	null	O	TO
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
37	null	PERCENT	CD
Tunisia	null	LOCATION	NNP
see	null	O	VBD
with	null	O	IN
rise	null	O	VBG
from	null	O	IN
rating	null	O	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
14	null	PERCENT	CD
north	null	O	RB
Africa	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
Tunisia	null	LOCATION	NNP
see	null	O	VBD
with	null	O	IN
rise	null	O	VBG
to	null	O	TO
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
37	null	PERCENT	CD
north	null	O	RB
Africa	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
Tunisia	null	LOCATION	NNP
see	null	O	VBD
with	null	O	IN
rise	null	O	VBG
from	null	O	IN
rating	null	O	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
14	null	PERCENT	CD
Syria	null	LOCATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
15	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
president	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
approve	null	O	VBD
say	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
15	null	PERCENT	CD
malaysian	null	MISC	JJ
share	null	O	NNS
rise	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
1.67	null	PERCENT	CD
malaysian	null	MISC	JJ
share	null	O	NNS
LUMPUR	null	LOCATION	NNP
1.67	null	PERCENT	CD
indian	null	MISC	JJ
population	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
of	null	O	IN
city	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
figure	null	O	NN
Indians	null	MISC	NNPS
against	null	O	IN
be	null	O	VBP
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
30	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
network	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
obtain	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
60	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
market	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
share	null	O	NN
fall	null	O	VBD
from	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
21	null	PERCENT	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
Communications	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
rise	null	O	VBD
rupee	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
4.89	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
meltdown	null	O	NN
from	null	O	IN
result	null	O	VBG
turmoil	null	O	NN
follow	null	O	VBG
take	null	O	VBD
pump	null	O	VBN
company	null	O	NNS
hold	null	O	VBZ
stake	null	O	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
79.9	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
giant	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
provide	null	O	VBN
promise	null	O	VBD
in	null	O	IN
move	null	O	NNS
allow	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
60	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
giant	null	O	NN
represent	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
35.4	null	PERCENT	CD
armenian	null	ORGANIZATION	JJ
Congress	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
take	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
17	null	PERCENT	CD
Armenia	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
member	null	O	NN
Republicans	null	MISC	NNPS
poll	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
46	null	PERCENT	CD
Armenia	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
member	null	O	NN
poll	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
22	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
icon	null	O	NN
enter	null	O	VBZ
with	null	O	IN
billion	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
financing	null	O	NN
agreement	null	O	NNS
cut	null	O	VB
reduce	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
50	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
give	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
60	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
give	null	O	VB
provide	null	O	VB
receive	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
12	null	PERCENT	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
government	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VB
give	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
60	null	PERCENT	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
government	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VB
receive	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
12	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
automaker	null	O	NN
close	null	O	VB
slash	null	O	NNS
lower	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
sale	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
term	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
Georgia	null	LOCATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBZ
blame	null	O	VBZ
contract	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
1.5	null	PERCENT	CD
Georgia	null	LOCATION	NNP
economy	null	O	NN
contract	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
1.5	null	PERCENT	CD
Georgia	null	LOCATION	NNP
economy	null	O	NN
dependent	null	O	JJ
slow	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
2.1	null	PERCENT	CD
Georgia	null	LOCATION	NNP
economy	null	O	NN
dependent	null	O	JJ
slow	null	O	VBD
from	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
12.4	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
crime	null	O	NN
drop	null	O	VBD
report	null	O	VBD
decline	null	O	VBG
compare	null	O	VBN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
2.5	null	PERCENT	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
in	null	O	IN
crime	null	O	NN
drop	null	O	VBD
report	null	O	VBD
decline	null	O	VBG
compare	null	O	VBN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
2.5	null	PERCENT	CD
russian	null	MISC	JJ
economy	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
forecast	null	O	NN
downgrade	null	O	VBG
to	null	O	TO
contraction	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
6.5	null	PERCENT	CD
indian	null	MISC	JJ
dive	null	O	NN
plunge	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
33	null	PERCENT	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
unlike	null	O	IN
account	null	O	VBP
for	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
15	null	PERCENT	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
economy	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
15	null	PERCENT	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
carmaker	null	O	NN
report	null	O	VBD
jump	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
15.8	null	PERCENT	CD
South	null	O	NNP
India	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
report	null	O	VBD
rise	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
8.4	null	PERCENT	CD
India	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
report	null	O	VBD
rise	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
8.4	null	PERCENT	CD
south	null	LOCATION	JJ
country	null	O	NN
carmaker	null	O	NN
India	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
report	null	O	VBD
rise	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
8.4	null	PERCENT	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
economy	null	O	NN
grow	null	O	VBD
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
6.7	null	PERCENT	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Securities	null	ORGANIZATION	NNPS
say	null	O	VBD
hike	null	O	VBN
to	null	O	TO
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
7.0	null	PERCENT	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Securities	null	ORGANIZATION	NNPS
say	null	O	VBD
hike	null	O	VBN
from	null	O	IN
earlier	null	O	RBR
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
5.5	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Treasury	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
propose	null	O	VBN
plan	null	O	NN
approve	null	O	VBN
hold	null	O	VBG
approve	null	O	VBP
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
54	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Treasury	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
propose	null	O	VBN
plan	null	O	NN
approve	null	O	VBN
hold	null	O	VBG
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
54	null	PERCENT	CD
indian	null	MISC	JJ
media	null	O	NNS
dub	null	O	VBN
curry	null	O	VBP
term	null	O	NN
use	null	O	VBN
by	null	O	IN
youth	null	O	NNS
behind	null	O	IN
violence	null	O	NN
indian	null	MISC	JJ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
30	null	PERCENT	CD
indian	null	MISC	JJ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
30	null	PERCENT	CD
Yemen	null	LOCATION	NNP
make	null	O	VBP
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
70	null	PERCENT	CD
Iran	null	LOCATION	NNP
reel	null	O	VBG
under	null	O	IN
rate	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
25	null	PERCENT	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
suggest	null	O	VBD
bother	null	O	VB
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
55	null	PERCENT	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
expect	null	O	VBP
turnout	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
expect	null	O	VBN
garner	null	O	VB
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
17	null	PERCENT	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
election	null	O	NNS
at	null	O	IN
turnout	null	O	NN
low	null	O	JJ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
38	null	PERCENT	CD
UK	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Party	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
like	null	O	IN
party	null	O	NNS
expect	null	O	VBN
low	null	O	JJ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
38	null	PERCENT	CD
british	null	ORGANIZATION	JJ
Party	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Party	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
like	null	O	IN
party	null	O	NNS
expect	null	O	VBN
low	null	O	JJ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
38	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
35	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
55	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
10	null	PERCENT	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
35	null	PERCENT	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
55	null	PERCENT	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
10	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
35	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
55	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
10	null	PERCENT	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
35	null	PERCENT	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
55	null	PERCENT	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
10	null	PERCENT	CD
indian	null	MISC	JJ
media	null	O	NNS
dub	null	O	VBN
pick	null	O	VBG
on	null	O	IN
term	null	O	NN
use	null	O	VBN
by	null	O	IN
some	null	O	DT
of	null	O	IN
youth	null	O	NNS
behind	null	O	IN
violence	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBP
indian	null	MISC	JJ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
30	null	PERCENT	CD
indian	null	MISC	JJ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
30	null	PERCENT	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
election	null	O	NNS
at	null	O	IN
turnout	null	O	NN
low	null	O	JJ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
38	null	PERCENT	CD
Turkey	null	LOCATION	NNP
for	null	O	IN
threat	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
80	null	PERCENT	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
expect	null	O	VBP
turnout	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Treasury	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
propose	null	O	VBN
plan	null	O	NN
approve	null	O	VBD
creditor	null	O	NNS
hold	null	O	VBG
about	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
54	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
35	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
55	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
10	null	PERCENT	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
35	null	PERCENT	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
55	null	PERCENT	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
10	null	PERCENT	CD
Israel	null	LOCATION	NNP
population	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
20	null	PERCENT	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
economy	null	O	NN
expand	null	O	VBN
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
6.7	null	PERCENT	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
deficit	null	O	NN
be	null	O	VBZ
at	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
6.2	null	PERCENT	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
election	null	O	NNS
at	null	O	IN
turnout	null	O	NN
low	null	O	JJ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
38	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
share	null	O	NN
slip	null	O	VBN
to	null	O	TO
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
26	null	PERCENT	CD
Kuwait	null	LOCATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBZ
sit	null	O	VBZ
on	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
10	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Treasury	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
propose	null	O	VBN
plan	null	O	NN
approve	null	O	VBN
hold	null	O	VBG
approve	null	O	VBP
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
54	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Treasury	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
propose	null	O	VBN
plan	null	O	NN
approve	null	O	VBN
hold	null	O	VBG
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
54	null	PERCENT	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
include	null	O	VBZ
Malays	null	O	NNP
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
60	null	PERCENT	CD
indian	null	MISC	JJ
community	null	O	NNS
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
include	null	O	VBZ
Malays	null	O	NNP
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
60	null	PERCENT	CD
Brazil	null	LOCATION	NNP
territory	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
43	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
hold	null	O	VB
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
72.5	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
invest	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
with	null	O	IN
convert	null	O	VBN
to	null	O	TO
stake	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
72.5	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
35	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
55	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
10	null	PERCENT	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
35	null	PERCENT	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
55	null	PERCENT	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
10	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Reserve	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
move	null	O	NNS
worth	null	O	JJ
correspond	null	O	VBZ
to	null	O	TO
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.6	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Reserve	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
move	null	O	NNS
worth	null	O	JJ
around	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
10	null	PERCENT	CD
England	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
of	null	ORGANIZATION	IN
Reserve	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
move	null	O	NNS
worth	null	O	JJ
correspond	null	O	VBZ
to	null	O	TO
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.6	null	PERCENT	CD
England	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
of	null	ORGANIZATION	IN
Reserve	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
move	null	O	NNS
worth	null	O	JJ
around	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
10	null	PERCENT	CD
russian	null	LOCATION	JJ
lender	null	O	NN
stake	null	O	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
20	null	PERCENT	CD
russian	null	LOCATION	JJ
lender	null	O	NN
stake	null	O	NN
hold	null	O	VB
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
35	null	PERCENT	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
election	null	O	NNS
at	null	O	IN
turnout	null	O	NN
low	null	O	JJ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
38	null	PERCENT	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
lead	null	O	VBN
demand	null	O	VBG
cut	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
emission	null	O	NNS
cut	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
17	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
negotiator	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
translate	null	O	VB
ratchet	null	O	VB
to	null	O	TO
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
83	null	PERCENT	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
demand	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
Taiwan	null	LOCATION	NNP
chii-ming	null	PERSON	NN
defend	null	O	VBN
claim	null	O	VBG
rise	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
point	null	O	NNS
1.4	null	NUMBER	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
with	null	O	IN
pact	null	O	NN
forge	null	O	VBG
by	null	O	IN
rise	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
point	null	O	NNS
1.4	null	NUMBER	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
include	null	O	VBZ
Malays	null	O	NNP
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
60	null	PERCENT	CD
indian	null	MISC	JJ
community	null	O	NNS
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
include	null	O	VBZ
Malays	null	O	NNP
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
60	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
share	null	O	NN
see	null	O	VBN
fall	null	DATE	NN
from	null	O	IN
peak	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
54	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
share	null	O	NN
see	null	O	VBN
fall	null	DATE	NN
to	null	O	TO
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
22	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
network	null	O	NN
shrink	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
plant	null	O	NNS
cut	null	O	VB
shrink	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
Obama	null	PERSON	NNP
rating	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
opinion	null	O	NN
have	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
33	null	PERCENT	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
of	null	O	IN
those	null	O	DT
beat	null	O	VBP
rating	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
opinion	null	O	NN
have	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
33	null	PERCENT	CD
Kuwait	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
point	null	O	NNS
by	null	O	IN
beat	null	O	VBP
rating	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
opinion	null	O	NN
have	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
33	null	PERCENT	CD
Jordan	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
point	null	O	NNS
point	null	O	NNS
by	null	O	IN
beat	null	O	VBP
rating	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
opinion	null	O	NN
have	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
33	null	PERCENT	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
Emirates	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
point	null	O	NNS
point	null	O	NNS
by	null	O	IN
beat	null	O	VBP
rating	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
opinion	null	O	NN
have	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
33	null	PERCENT	CD
Arabia	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
point	null	O	NNS
point	null	O	NNS
by	null	O	IN
beat	null	O	VBP
rating	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
opinion	null	O	NN
have	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
33	null	PERCENT	CD
Egypt	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
point	null	O	NNS
point	null	O	NNS
by	null	O	IN
beat	null	O	VBP
rating	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
opinion	null	O	NN
have	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
33	null	PERCENT	CD
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
point	null	O	NNS
by	null	O	IN
beat	null	O	VBP
rating	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
opinion	null	O	NN
have	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
33	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Treasury	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
propose	null	O	VBN
plan	null	O	NN
approve	null	O	VBN
creditor	null	O	NNS
approve	null	O	VBP
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
54	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Treasury	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
propose	null	O	VBN
plan	null	O	NN
approve	null	O	VBN
creditor	null	O	NNS
hold	null	O	VBG
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
54	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
industry	null	O	NN
performance	null	O	NN
amid	null	O	IN
fall	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
45	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
ship	null	O	VBG
represent	null	O	VBG
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
1.6	null	PERCENT	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
lead	null	O	VBD
lead	null	O	VBD
with	null	O	IN
rise	null	O	VBG
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
29.9	null	PERCENT	CD
China	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
venture	null	O	NNS
lead	null	O	VBD
with	null	O	IN
rise	null	O	VBG
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
29.9	null	PERCENT	CD
Kuwait	null	LOCATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBZ
sit	null	O	VBZ
on	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
10	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Treasury	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
propose	null	O	VBN
plan	null	O	NN
approve	null	O	VBN
hold	null	O	VBG
approve	null	O	VBP
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
54	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Treasury	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
propose	null	O	VBN
plan	null	O	NN
approve	null	O	VBN
hold	null	O	VBG
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
54	null	PERCENT	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
student	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
group	null	O	NN
form	null	O	VBP
estimate	null	O	VBP
make	null	O	VB
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
30	null	PERCENT	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
suggest	null	O	VBD
bother	null	O	VB
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
55	null	PERCENT	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
expect	null	O	VBP
turnout	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
expect	null	O	VBN
garner	null	O	VB
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
17	null	PERCENT	CD
japanese	null	MISC	JJ
sale	null	O	NNS
fall	null	DATE	NN
fall	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
19.4	null	PERCENT	CD
Japan	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
sale	null	O	NNS
fall	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
19.4	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
industry	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
drop	null	O	NN
plummet	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
51	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
automaker	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
rise	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
11	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
sale	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
drop	null	O	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
38	null	PERCENT	CD
japanese	null	MISC	JJ
price	null	O	NNS
open	null	O	VBD
with	null	O	IN
rise	null	O	VBG
point	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
1.0	null	PERCENT	CD
Kuwait	null	LOCATION	NNP
member	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
Organisation	null	O	NNP
pump	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
Kazakhstan	null	LOCATION	NNP
hold	null	O	VBZ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
20	null	PERCENT	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
border	null	O	VBG
republic	null	O	NN
Kazakhstan	null	LOCATION	NNP
hold	null	O	VBZ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
20	null	PERCENT	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
border	null	O	VBG
republic	null	O	NN
Kazakhstan	null	LOCATION	NNP
hold	null	O	VBZ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
20	null	PERCENT	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
overtake	null	O	VBG
producer	null	O	NN
aim	null	O	VBZ
hold	null	O	VBZ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
20	null	PERCENT	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
overtake	null	O	VBG
producer	null	O	NN
aim	null	O	VBZ
hold	null	O	VBZ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
20	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Congress	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
look	null	O	VBG
at	null	O	IN
legislation	null	O	NN
cut	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
17	null	PERCENT	CD
Switzerland	null	LOCATION	NNP
enter	null	O	VBZ
show	null	O	VBD
enter	null	O	VBD
shrink	null	O	VBD
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.8	null	PERCENT	CD
Switzerland	null	LOCATION	NNP
enter	null	O	VBD
shrink	null	O	VBD
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.8	null	PERCENT	CD
Macau	null	LOCATION	NNP
show	null	O	VBD
with	null	O	IN
jump	null	O	VBG
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
8.1	null	PERCENT	CD
Taiwan	null	LOCATION	NNP
tie	null	O	NNS
over	null	O	IN
confidence	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
rise	null	O	VBN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
33	null	PERCENT	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
with	null	O	IN
tie	null	O	NNS
over	null	O	IN
confidence	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
rise	null	O	VBN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
33	null	PERCENT	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VB
shanghaus	null	O	NNS
3.36	null	PERCENT	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VB
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
3.36	null	PERCENT	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VB
shanghaus	null	O	NNS
3.36	null	PERCENT	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
3.36	null	PERCENT	CD
Switzerland	null	LOCATION	NNP
enter	null	O	VBZ
show	null	O	VBD
enter	null	O	VBD
shrink	null	O	VBD
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.8	null	PERCENT	CD
Switzerland	null	LOCATION	NNP
enter	null	O	VBD
shrink	null	O	VBD
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.8	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
deal	null	O	NN
under	null	O	IN
double	null	O	VB
from	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
18	null	PERCENT	CD
japanese	null	MISC	JJ
price	null	O	NNS
rise	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
1.63	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
manufacturing	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
file	null	O	VBD
hand	null	O	VBG
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
60	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
hand	null	O	VBG
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
60	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
population	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.6	null	PERCENT	CD
Pakistani	null	MISC	NNP
official	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
end	null	O	VB
with	null	O	IN
remain	null	O	VBG
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
10	null	PERCENT	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
rate	null	O	NNS
leave	null	O	VBD
at	null	O	IN
low	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
3.0	null	PERCENT	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
bank	null	O	NN
fear	null	O	VBD
rate	null	O	NNS
leave	null	O	VBD
at	null	O	IN
low	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
3.0	null	PERCENT	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
rate	null	O	NNS
fall	null	O	VBN
from	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
7.25	null	PERCENT	CD
australian	null	ORGANIZATION	JJ
bureau	null	ORGANIZATION	NN
say	null	O	VBD
add	null	O	VB
point	null	O	NNS
2.2	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
show	null	O	VBD
fall	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.1	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
show	null	O	VBD
fall	null	O	VBD
rise	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.5	null	PERCENT	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
consumption	null	O	NN
drop	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
4	null	PERCENT	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
import	null	O	VBN
tonne	null	O	NNS
drop	null	O	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
4.5	null	PERCENT	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
GDP	null	O	NNP
grow	null	O	VBD
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
6.1	null	PERCENT	CD
malaysian	null	MISC	JJ
share	null	O	NNS
rise	null	O	VBD
Tuesday	null	DATE	NNP
0.17	null	PERCENT	CD
malaysian	null	MISC	JJ
share	null	O	NNS
LUMPUR	null	LOCATION	NNP
0.17	null	PERCENT	CD
Kazakhstan	null	LOCATION	NNP
hold	null	O	VBZ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
20	null	PERCENT	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
border	null	O	VBG
republic	null	O	NN
Kazakhstan	null	LOCATION	NNP
hold	null	O	VBZ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
20	null	PERCENT	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
border	null	O	VBG
republic	null	O	NN
Kazakhstan	null	LOCATION	NNP
hold	null	O	VBZ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
20	null	PERCENT	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
overtake	null	O	VBG
producer	null	O	NN
aim	null	O	VBZ
hold	null	O	VBZ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
20	null	PERCENT	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
overtake	null	O	VBG
producer	null	O	NN
aim	null	O	VBZ
hold	null	O	VBZ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
20	null	PERCENT	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
asset	null	O	NNS
unsafe	null	O	JJ
consider	null	O	VBN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
87	null	PERCENT	CD
China	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Corp.	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
take	null	O	VBD
stake	null	O	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
10	null	PERCENT	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
Bank	null	O	NNP
be	null	O	VBZ
expect	null	O	VBN
keep	null	O	VB
at	null	O	IN
record	null	O	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.5	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
industry	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
drop	null	O	NN
plummet	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
51	null	PERCENT	CD
indian	null	MISC	JJ
population	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
of	null	O	IN
city	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
figure	null	O	NN
Indians	null	MISC	NNPS
against	null	O	IN
be	null	O	VBP
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
30	null	PERCENT	CD
Switzerland	null	LOCATION	NNP
enter	null	O	VBZ
show	null	O	VBD
enter	null	O	VBD
shrink	null	O	VBD
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.8	null	PERCENT	CD
Switzerland	null	LOCATION	NNP
enter	null	O	VBD
shrink	null	O	VBD
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.8	null	PERCENT	CD
malaysian	null	MISC	JJ
share	null	O	NNS
rise	null	O	VBD
Tuesday	null	DATE	NNP
0.17	null	PERCENT	CD
malaysian	null	MISC	JJ
share	null	O	NNS
LUMPUR	null	LOCATION	NNP
0.17	null	PERCENT	CD
England	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
purchase	null	O	NNS
of	null	ORGANIZATION	IN
Fed	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
correspond	null	O	VBP
to	null	O	TO
8.0	null	NUMBER	CD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
2.0	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
value	null	O	NN
suggest	null	O	VBG
say	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
25	null	PERCENT	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
case	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
80	null	PERCENT	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
Bank	null	O	NNP
due	null	O	JJ
expect	null	O	VBN
keep	null	O	VB
rate	null	O	NNS
unchanged	null	O	JJ
at	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.5	null	PERCENT	CD
Kuwait	null	LOCATION	NNP
member	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
Organisation	null	O	NNP
pump	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
spending	null	O	NN
fall	null	O	VBD
show	null	O	VBG
datum	null	O	NNS
welcome	null	O	VBN
leap	null	O	NN
2.60	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
spending	null	O	NN
fall	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.1	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
spending	null	O	NN
fall	null	O	VBD
rise	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.5	null	PERCENT	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
Mobile	null	O	NNP
tumble	null	O	VBD
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
3.9	null	PERCENT	CD
China	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
of	null	ORGANIZATION	IN
Bank	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
fall	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
1.1	null	PERCENT	CD
SINGAPORE	null	LOCATION	NNP
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.18	null	PERCENT	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VB
shanghaus	null	O	NNS
0.11	null	PERCENT	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VB
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VBD
lead	null	O	VBN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.11	null	PERCENT	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VB
shanghaus	null	O	NNS
0.11	null	PERCENT	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VBD
lead	null	O	VBN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.11	null	PERCENT	CD
China	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Insurance	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
end	null	O	VBD
fall	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
1.1	null	PERCENT	CD
China	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
of	null	ORGANIZATION	IN
Bank	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
fall	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
1.1	null	PERCENT	CD
Australia	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
of	null	ORGANIZATION	IN
Bank	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
leave	null	O	VB
at	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
3.0	null	PERCENT	CD
Greenland	null	LOCATION	NNP
island	null	O	NN
cover	null	O	VBN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
80	null	PERCENT	CD
Greenland	null	LOCATION	NNP
island	null	O	NN
contain	null	O	VBZ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
10	null	PERCENT	CD
indonesian	null	ORGANIZATION	JJ
Institute	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
publish	null	O	VBN
poll	null	O	NN
find	null	O	VBD
vote	null	O	VB
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
70	null	PERCENT	CD
indonesian	null	ORGANIZATION	JJ
Institute	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
publish	null	O	VBN
poll	null	O	NN
find	null	O	VBD
vote	null	O	VB
compare	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
21	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Treasury	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
propose	null	O	VBN
plan	null	O	NN
approve	null	O	VBD
creditor	null	O	NNS
hold	null	O	VBG
about	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
54	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
35	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
55	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
10	null	PERCENT	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
35	null	PERCENT	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
55	null	PERCENT	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
10	null	PERCENT	CD
British	null	MISC	NNP
bank	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
Shares	null	O	NNP
by	null	O	IN
GMT	null	MISC	NNP
tumble	null	O	VB
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
15	null	PERCENT	CD
Macau	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
value	null	O	NN
hold	null	O	VBZ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
51	null	PERCENT	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
hold	null	O	VBZ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
51	null	PERCENT	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
carrier	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
stand	null	O	VBD
value	null	O	NN
hold	null	O	VBZ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
51	null	PERCENT	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
Bank	null	O	NNP
be	null	O	VBZ
expect	null	O	VBN
keep	null	O	VB
at	null	O	IN
record	null	O	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.5	null	PERCENT	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
share	null	O	NNS
higher	null	O	RBR
price	null	O	NNS
morning	null	TIME	NN
1.92	null	PERCENT	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
price	null	O	NNS
morning	null	TIME	NN
1.92	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
automaker	null	O	NN
close	null	O	VB
slash	null	O	NNS
lower	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
sale	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
term	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
help	null	O	VB
restructure	null	O	NN
receive	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
60	null	PERCENT	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
government	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VB
receive	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
12	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
35	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
55	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
10	null	PERCENT	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
35	null	PERCENT	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
55	null	PERCENT	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
10	null	PERCENT	CD
Malaysia	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
export	null	O	NNS
worth	null	O	JJ
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
grow	null	O	VBG
at	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
34	null	PERCENT	CD
Thailand	null	LOCATION	NNP
price	null	O	NNS
fall	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
3.3	null	PERCENT	CD
Japan	null	LOCATION	NNP
post	null	O	VBD
shrink	null	O	VBN
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
15.2	null	PERCENT	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
Mobile	null	O	NNP
tumble	null	O	VBD
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
3.9	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Association	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
fall	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
16.1	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Association	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
fall	null	O	VBD
follow	null	O	VBG
drop	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
14.2	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Association	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
fall	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
16.1	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Association	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
fall	null	O	VBD
follow	null	O	VBG
drop	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
14.2	null	PERCENT	CD
American	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Association	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
Journal	null	O	NNP
in	null	O	IN
publish	null	O	VBD
study	null	O	NN
find	null	O	VBD
overweight	null	O	JJ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
32	null	PERCENT	CD
American	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Association	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
Journal	null	O	NNP
in	null	O	IN
publish	null	O	VBD
study	null	O	NN
find	null	O	VBD
overweight	null	O	JJ
obese	null	O	JJ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
16	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
child	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
32	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
child	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
overweight	null	O	JJ
obese	null	O	JJ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
16	null	PERCENT	CD
Germany	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
holiday	null	O	NN
rise	null	O	VBD
point	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
3.20	null	PERCENT	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
car	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
sale	null	O	NNS
rise	null	O	NN
committee	null	O	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
12.4	null	PERCENT	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
car	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
sale	null	O	NNS
rise	null	O	NN
committee	null	O	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
in	null	O	IN
Paris	null	LOCATION	NNP
rise	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
12.4	null	PERCENT	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
car	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
sale	null	O	NNS
rise	null	O	NN
committee	null	O	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
in	null	O	IN
Paris	null	LOCATION	NNP
rise	null	O	VBD
compare	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
month	null	DATE	NN
follow	null	O	VBG
slide	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
7.0	null	PERCENT	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
sale	null	O	NNS
rise	null	O	VBD
Paris	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
12.4	null	PERCENT	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
sale	null	O	NNS
rise	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
12.4	null	PERCENT	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
sale	null	O	NNS
rise	null	O	VBD
compare	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
month	null	DATE	NN
follow	null	O	VBG
slide	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
7.0	null	PERCENT	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
manufacturer	null	O	NNS
Paris	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
12.4	null	PERCENT	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
manufacturer	null	O	NNS
Paris	null	LOCATION	NNP
rise	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
12.4	null	PERCENT	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
manufacturer	null	O	NNS
Paris	null	LOCATION	NNP
rise	null	O	VBD
compare	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
month	null	DATE	NN
follow	null	O	VBG
slide	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
7.0	null	PERCENT	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
38.7	null	PERCENT	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
8.59	null	PERCENT	CD
Italy	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
38.7	null	PERCENT	CD
Italy	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
8.59	null	PERCENT	CD
Japan	null	LOCATION	NNP
economy	null	O	NN
shrink	null	O	VBG
at	null	O	IN
month	null	DURATION	NN
4.0	null	PERCENT	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
economy	null	O	NN
grow	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
6.1	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
sale	null	O	NNS
fall	null	O	VBP
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
38	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
sale	null	O	NNS
fall	null	O	VBP
Toyota	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
appear	null	O	VBD
recover	null	O	VBG
post	null	O	VBD
drop	null	O	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
38	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
market	null	O	NN
appear	null	O	VBD
say	null	O	VBD
Toyota	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
fall	null	O	VBP
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
38	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
market	null	O	NN
recover	null	O	VBG
post	null	O	VBD
drop	null	O	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
38	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	DATE	NNP
sale	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
drop	null	O	NN
post	null	O	VBD
recover	null	O	VBG
appear	null	O	VBD
say	null	O	VBD
Toyota	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
fall	null	O	VBP
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
38	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	DATE	NNP
sale	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
drop	null	O	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
38	null	PERCENT	CD
australian	null	MISC	JJ
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	RB
SYDNEY	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
1	null	DATE	CD
australian	null	MISC	JJ
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	RB
SYDNEY	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
1	null	DATE	CD
Iran	null	LOCATION	NNP
earnings	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
80	null	PERCENT	CD
Iran	null	LOCATION	NNP
Centre	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
head	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
account	null	O	VBP
for	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
60	null	PERCENT	CD
Taiwan	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
turnover	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
fall	null	O	VBD
point	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.07	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
turnover	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
fall	null	O	VBD
point	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.07	null	PERCENT	CD
North	null	LOCATION	NNP
island	null	O	NN
see	null	O	VBD
bring	null	O	VBG
decade	null	DURATION	NN
of	null	O	IN
prosperity	null	O	NN
average	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
4.0	null	PERCENT	CD
Iceland	null	LOCATION	NNP
inhabitant	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
island	null	O	NN
see	null	O	VBD
bring	null	O	VBG
decade	null	DURATION	NN
of	null	O	IN
prosperity	null	O	NN
average	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
4.0	null	PERCENT	CD
Iceland	null	LOCATION	NNP
economy	null	O	NN
contract	null	O	NN
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
10.6	null	PERCENT	CD
german	null	MISC	JJ
parliament	null	O	NN
pass	null	O	VBD
reject	null	O	VBN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
90	null	PERCENT	CD
Sweden	null	LOCATION	NNP
come	null	O	VBZ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
45	null	PERCENT	CD
Switzerland	null	LOCATION	NNP
enter	null	O	VBZ
enter	null	O	VBD
shrink	null	O	VBD
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.8	null	PERCENT	CD
Switzerland	null	LOCATION	NNP
enter	null	O	VBD
shrink	null	O	VBD
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.8	null	PERCENT	CD
swiss	null	MISC	JJ
office	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBN
cut	null	O	VBN
by	null	O	IN
owe	null	O	VBG
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
27	null	PERCENT	CD
Switzerland	null	LOCATION	NNP
surplus	null	O	NN
cut	null	O	VBN
by	null	O	IN
owe	null	O	VBG
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
27	null	PERCENT	CD
swiss	null	MISC	JJ
import	null	O	NNS
rise	null	O	VBN
by	null	O	IN
owe	null	O	VBG
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
43	null	PERCENT	CD
Switzerland	null	LOCATION	NNP
report	null	O	VB
recession	null	O	NN
contraction	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.3	null	PERCENT	CD
Chinese	null	LOCATION	NNP
household	null	O	NNS
Kinh	null	PERSON	NNP
have	null	O	VBD
rate	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
10	null	PERCENT	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
HDFC	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
rise	null	O	VBD
rupee	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
4.19	null	PERCENT	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
asset	null	O	NNS
unsafe	null	O	JJ
consider	null	O	VBN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
87	null	PERCENT	CD
Albania	null	LOCATION	NNP
derive	null	O	VBZ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
97	null	PERCENT	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
facility	null	O	NN
ask	null	O	VBN
say	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
65	null	PERCENT	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
facility	null	O	NN
ask	null	O	VBN
say	null	O	VBD
with	null	O	IN
say	null	O	VBG
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
32	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
prison	null	O	NNS
to	null	O	TO
move	null	O	VB
facility	null	O	NN
ask	null	O	VBN
say	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
65	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
prison	null	O	NNS
to	null	O	TO
move	null	O	VB
facility	null	O	NN
ask	null	O	VBN
say	null	O	VBD
with	null	O	IN
say	null	O	VBG
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
32	null	PERCENT	CD
Americans	null	MISC	NNPS
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
65	null	PERCENT	CD
Americans	null	MISC	NNPS
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
say	null	O	VBD
with	null	O	IN
say	null	O	VBG
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
32	null	PERCENT	CD
USA	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
poll	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
accord	null	O	VBG
say	null	O	VBG
with	null	O	IN
say	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
65	null	PERCENT	CD
USA	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
poll	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
accord	null	O	VBG
say	null	O	VBG
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
32	null	PERCENT	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
safer	null	O	JJR
make	null	O	VBN
believe	null	O	VBP
say	null	O	VBD
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
18	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
boost	null	O	VBN
argument	null	O	NNS
accept	null	O	VBG
make	null	O	VBN
believe	null	O	VBP
say	null	O	VBD
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
18	null	PERCENT	CD
japanese	null	MISC	JJ
price	null	O	NNS
open	null	O	VBD
with	null	O	IN
lose	null	O	VBG
point	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.16	null	PERCENT	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
car	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
sale	null	O	NNS
rise	null	O	VBP
committee	null	O	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
11.9	null	PERCENT	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
car	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
sale	null	O	NNS
rise	null	O	VBP
committee	null	O	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
in	null	O	IN
Paris	null	LOCATION	NNP
rise	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
11.9	null	PERCENT	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
car	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
sale	null	O	NNS
rise	null	O	VBP
committee	null	O	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
in	null	O	IN
Paris	null	LOCATION	NNP
rise	null	O	VBD
compare	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
month	null	DATE	NN
follow	null	O	VBG
slide	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
7.0	null	PERCENT	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
sale	null	O	NNS
rise	null	O	VBD
Paris	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
11.9	null	PERCENT	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
sale	null	O	NNS
rise	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
11.9	null	PERCENT	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
sale	null	O	NNS
rise	null	O	VBD
compare	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
month	null	DATE	NN
follow	null	O	VBG
slide	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
7.0	null	PERCENT	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
manufacturer	null	O	NNS
Paris	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
11.9	null	PERCENT	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
manufacturer	null	O	NNS
Paris	null	LOCATION	NNP
rise	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
11.9	null	PERCENT	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
manufacturer	null	O	NNS
Paris	null	LOCATION	NNP
rise	null	O	VBD
compare	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
month	null	DATE	NN
follow	null	O	VBG
slide	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
7.0	null	PERCENT	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
Citroen	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
report	null	O	VBD
gain	null	O	NN
20.7	null	PERCENT	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
Citroen	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
report	null	O	VBD
suffer	null	O	VBD
decline	null	O	NN
1.7	null	PERCENT	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
38.7	null	PERCENT	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
8.59	null	PERCENT	CD
Italy	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
38.7	null	PERCENT	CD
Italy	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
8.59	null	PERCENT	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VB
shanghaus	null	O	NNS
0.11	null	PERCENT	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VB
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VBD
lead	null	O	VBN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.11	null	PERCENT	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VB
shanghaus	null	O	NNS
0.11	null	PERCENT	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VBD
lead	null	O	VBN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.11	null	PERCENT	CD
Germany	null	LOCATION	NNP
own	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
47.3	null	PERCENT	CD
Germany	null	LOCATION	NNP
force	null	O	VB
own	null	O	VBZ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
90	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
slash	null	O	NNS
say	null	O	VBZ
cut	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
30	null	PERCENT	CD
Philippines	null	LOCATION	NNP
BAGUIO	null	LOCATION	NNP
cut	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
30	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
Inc	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
BAGUIO	null	LOCATION	NNP
cut	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
30	null	PERCENT	CD
Philippines	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
unit	null	O	NN
at	null	O	IN
cut	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
30	null	PERCENT	CD
Philippines	null	LOCATION	NNPS
industry	null	O	NN
account	null	O	VBD
for	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
70	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
automaker	null	O	NN
close	null	O	VB
slash	null	O	NNS
lower	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
sale	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
term	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
help	null	O	VB
restructure	null	O	NN
receive	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
60	null	PERCENT	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
government	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VB
receive	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
12	null	PERCENT	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
as	null	O	IN
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
evaporate	null	O	VBG
by	null	O	IN
hit	null	O	VBN
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
asset	null	O	NNS
unsafe	null	O	JJ
consider	null	O	VBN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
87	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
industry	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
drop	null	O	NN
plummet	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
51	null	PERCENT	CD
Armenia	null	LOCATION	NNP
party	null	O	NN
win	null	O	VBZ
win	null	O	VBD
with	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
46	null	PERCENT	CD
Armenia	null	LOCATION	NNP
party	null	O	NN
win	null	O	VBD
with	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
46	null	PERCENT	CD
armenian	null	ORGANIZATION	JJ
Congress	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
take	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
17	null	PERCENT	CD
armenian	null	ORGANIZATION	JJ
Congress	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
take	null	O	VBD
behind	null	O	IN
Republicans	null	MISC	NNPS
member	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
coalition	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
22	null	PERCENT	CD
Armenia	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
coalition	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
member	null	O	NN
Republicans	null	MISC	NNPS
behind	null	O	IN
take	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
17	null	PERCENT	CD
Armenia	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
coalition	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
22	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
receive	null	O	VB
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
60	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
industry	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
drop	null	O	NN
plummet	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
51	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
automaker	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
rise	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
11	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
sale	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
drop	null	O	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
38	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
industry	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
drop	null	O	NN
plummet	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
51	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Congress	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
look	null	O	VBG
at	null	O	IN
legislation	null	O	NN
cut	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
17	null	PERCENT	CD
indian	null	MISC	JJ
population	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
million	null	NUMBER	CD
of	null	O	IN
city	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
figure	null	O	NN
Indians	null	MISC	NNPS
against	null	O	IN
be	null	O	VBP
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
30	null	PERCENT	CD
german	null	MISC	JJ
Porsche	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
reaffirm	null	O	VBD
finish	null	O	VB
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
10.24	null	PERCENT	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
head	null	O	VBD
spend	null	O	VBG
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
31.1	null	PERCENT	CD
Sweden	null	LOCATION	NNP
record	null	O	VBN
as	null	O	IN
spending	null	O	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
30	null	PERCENT	CD
Belgium	null	LOCATION	NNP
Sweden	null	LOCATION	NNP
record	null	O	VBN
as	null	O	IN
spending	null	O	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
30	null	PERCENT	CD
Romania	null	LOCATION	NNP
at	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
14	null	PERCENT	CD
Romania	null	LOCATION	NNP
Lithuania	null	LOCATION	NNP
at	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
13.2	null	PERCENT	CD
Romania	null	LOCATION	NNP
Estonia	null	LOCATION	NNP
at	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
12.4	null	PERCENT	CD
Lithuania	null	LOCATION	NNP
Romania	null	LOCATION	NNP
at	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
14	null	PERCENT	CD
Lithuania	null	LOCATION	NNP
at	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
13.2	null	PERCENT	CD
Lithuania	null	LOCATION	NNP
Romania	null	LOCATION	NNP
Estonia	null	LOCATION	NNP
at	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
12.4	null	PERCENT	CD
Estonia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Romania	null	LOCATION	NNP
at	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
14	null	PERCENT	CD
Estonia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Romania	null	LOCATION	NNP
Lithuania	null	LOCATION	NNP
at	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
13.2	null	PERCENT	CD
Estonia	null	LOCATION	NNP
at	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
12.4	null	PERCENT	CD
russian	null	MISC	JJ
sector	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
report	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
say	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
11	null	PERCENT	CD
russian	null	MISC	JJ
sector	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
report	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
say	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
reach	null	O	VB
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
20	null	PERCENT	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
level	null	O	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
11	null	PERCENT	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
level	null	O	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
reach	null	O	VB
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
20	null	PERCENT	CD
japanese	null	MISC	JJ
price	null	O	NNS
rise	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.27	null	PERCENT	CD
dutch	null	MISC	JJ
turnout	null	O	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
39.1	null	PERCENT	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	RB
SINGAPORE	null	LOCATION	NNP
0.18	null	PERCENT	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	RB
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VBD
lower	null	O	JJR
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.18	null	PERCENT	CD
SINGAPORE	null	LOCATION	NNP
0.18	null	PERCENT	CD
SINGAPORE	null	LOCATION	NNP
close	null	O	RB
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VBD
lower	null	O	JJR
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.18	null	PERCENT	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	RB
SINGAPORE	null	LOCATION	NNP
0.18	null	PERCENT	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VBD
lower	null	O	JJR
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.18	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
market	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
60	null	PERCENT	CD
Switzerland	null	LOCATION	NNP
enter	null	O	VBZ
with	null	O	IN
drop	null	O	NN
fall	null	O	VBD
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.8	null	PERCENT	CD
Switzerland	null	LOCATION	NNP
GDP	null	O	NNP
fall	null	O	VBD
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.8	null	PERCENT	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
Bank	null	O	NNP
be	null	O	VBZ
expect	null	O	VBN
keep	null	O	VB
at	null	O	IN
record	null	O	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.5	null	PERCENT	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
bank	null	O	NN
leave	null	O	VBD
at	null	O	IN
low	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
3.0	null	PERCENT	CD
spanish	null	MISC	JJ
price	null	O	NNS
fall	null	O	VB
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
30	null	PERCENT	CD
spanish	null	MISC	JJ
price	null	O	NNS
say	null	O	VBD
second	null	ORDINAL	JJ
start	null	O	VBP
price	null	O	NNS
fall	null	O	VB
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
30	null	PERCENT	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
fall	null	O	VB
price	null	O	NNS
start	null	O	VBP
second	null	ORDINAL	JJ
say	null	O	VBD
price	null	O	NNS
fall	null	O	VB
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
30	null	PERCENT	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
fall	null	O	VB
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
30	null	PERCENT	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
second	null	ORDINAL	JJ
say	null	O	VBD
price	null	O	NNS
fall	null	O	VB
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
30	null	PERCENT	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
second	null	ORDINAL	JJ
start	null	O	VBP
price	null	O	NNS
fall	null	O	VB
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
30	null	PERCENT	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	RB
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
0.18	null	PERCENT	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	RB
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VBD
lower	null	O	JJR
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.18	null	PERCENT	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
0.18	null	PERCENT	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
close	null	O	RB
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VBD
lower	null	O	JJR
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.18	null	PERCENT	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	RB
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
0.18	null	PERCENT	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
share	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VBD
lower	null	O	JJR
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.18	null	PERCENT	CD
japanese	null	MISC	JJ
automaker	null	O	NN
overtake	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
spot	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
16.8	null	PERCENT	CD
japanese	null	MISC	JJ
automaker	null	O	NN
overtake	null	O	VB
fall	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
24	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
market	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
16.8	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
market	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
with	null	O	IN
spot	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
overtake	null	O	VB
fall	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
24	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
market	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
share	null	O	NN
boost	null	O	VB
to	null	O	TO
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
20.5	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
market	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
share	null	O	NN
boost	null	O	VB
from	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
19.1	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
market	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
share	null	O	NN
boost	null	O	VB
manage	null	O	VBD
fall	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
30	null	PERCENT	CD
japanese	null	MISC	JJ
Honda	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
take	null	O	VBD
push	null	O	VBD
drop	null	O	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
42	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
prowess	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
symbol	null	O	NN
once	null	DATE	RB
enter	null	O	VBZ
process	null	O	NN
aim	null	O	VBG
for	null	O	IN
so	null	O	RB
bankruptcy	null	O	NN
cut	null	O	VB
reduce	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
50	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
give	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
60	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
give	null	O	VB
provide	null	O	VB
receive	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
12	null	PERCENT	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
government	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VB
give	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
60	null	PERCENT	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
government	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VB
receive	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
12	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
automaker	null	O	NN
close	null	O	VB
slash	null	O	NNS
lower	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
sale	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
term	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
Syria	null	LOCATION	NNP
represent	null	O	VBZ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
23	null	PERCENT	CD
Syria	null	LOCATION	NNP
represent	null	O	VBZ
employ	null	O	VBZ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
30	null	PERCENT	CD
Turkey	null	LOCATION	NNP
through	null	O	IN
run	null	O	VBZ
shrink	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
80	null	PERCENT	CD
Syria	null	LOCATION	NNP
Turkey	null	LOCATION	NNP
through	null	O	IN
run	null	O	VBZ
shrink	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
80	null	PERCENT	CD
Iraq	null	LOCATION	NNP
Turkey	null	LOCATION	NNP
through	null	O	IN
run	null	O	VBZ
shrink	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
80	null	PERCENT	CD
Greenland	null	LOCATION	NNP
island	null	O	NN
cover	null	O	VBN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
80	null	PERCENT	CD
Greenland	null	LOCATION	NNP
island	null	O	NN
contain	null	O	VBZ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
10	null	PERCENT	CD
Greenland	null	LOCATION	NNP
island	null	O	NN
cover	null	O	VBN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
80	null	PERCENT	CD
Greenland	null	LOCATION	NNP
island	null	O	NN
contain	null	O	VBZ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
10	null	PERCENT	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
gas	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
80	null	PERCENT	CD
russian	null	MISC	JJ
system	null	O	NN
over	null	O	IN
monopoly	null	O	NN
have	null	O	VBZ
produce	null	O	VBZ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
80	null	PERCENT	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
4.2	null	PERCENT	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
from	null	O	IN
range	null	O	VBG
to	null	O	TO
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
16.8	null	PERCENT	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
from	null	O	IN
range	null	O	VBG
to	null	O	TO
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
17.4	null	PERCENT	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
from	null	O	IN
range	null	O	VBG
to	null	O	TO
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
18.1	null	PERCENT	CD
Austria	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
4.2	null	PERCENT	CD
Austria	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
from	null	O	IN
range	null	O	VBG
to	null	O	TO
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
16.8	null	PERCENT	CD
Austria	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
from	null	O	IN
range	null	O	VBG
to	null	O	TO
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
17.4	null	PERCENT	CD
Austria	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
from	null	O	IN
range	null	O	VBG
to	null	O	TO
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
18.1	null	PERCENT	CD
Lithuania	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
to	null	O	TO
range	null	O	VBG
from	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
4.2	null	PERCENT	CD
Lithuania	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
16.8	null	PERCENT	CD
Lithuania	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
17.4	null	PERCENT	CD
Lithuania	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
18.1	null	PERCENT	CD
Latvia	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
to	null	O	TO
range	null	O	VBG
from	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
4.2	null	PERCENT	CD
Latvia	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
16.8	null	PERCENT	CD
Latvia	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
17.4	null	PERCENT	CD
Latvia	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
18.1	null	PERCENT	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
to	null	O	TO
range	null	O	VBG
from	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
4.2	null	PERCENT	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
16.8	null	PERCENT	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
17.4	null	PERCENT	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
18.1	null	PERCENT	CD
spanish	null	MISC	JJ
ministry	null	O	NN
report	null	O	VBD
fall	null	O	VBD
remain	null	O	VBG
at	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
17.36	null	PERCENT	CD
Austria	null	LOCATION	NNP
record	null	O	VBD
with	null	O	IN
slip	null	O	VBG
to	null	O	TO
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
6.6	null	PERCENT	CD
Austria	null	LOCATION	NNP
record	null	O	VBD
with	null	O	IN
slip	null	O	VBG
from	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
7.1	null	PERCENT	CD
Azerbaijan	null	LOCATION	NNP
record	null	O	VBD
in	null	O	IN
sector	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
13.7	null	PERCENT	CD
Azerbaijan	null	LOCATION	NNP
economy	null	O	NN
grow	null	O	VBD
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
10.8	null	PERCENT	CD
Azerbaijan	null	LOCATION	NNP
economy	null	O	NN
grow	null	O	VBD
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
drop	null	O	NN
from	null	O	IN
year	null	DATE	NNS
grow	null	O	VBD
at	null	O	IN
average	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
30	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
industry	null	O	NN
performance	null	O	NN
amid	null	O	IN
fall	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
45	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Treasury	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
propose	null	O	VBN
plan	null	O	NN
approve	null	O	VBD
creditor	null	O	NNS
hold	null	O	VBG
about	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
54	null	PERCENT	CD
Afghanistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
make	null	O	VB
short	null	O	JJ
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
10	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
ConocoPhillips	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
own	null	O	VBN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
20	null	PERCENT	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
see	null	O	VBD
admit	null	O	VBN
contract	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
60	null	PERCENT	CD
British	null	MISC	NNP
Barclays	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
Shares	null	O	NNP
tumble	null	O	VBD
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
15	null	PERCENT	CD
Switzerland	null	LOCATION	NNP
BERN	null	LOCATION	NNP
enter	null	O	VBD
in	null	O	IN
quarter	null	DATE	NN
shrink	null	O	VBD
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.8	null	PERCENT	CD
Taiwan	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
turnover	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
fall	null	O	VBD
point	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.07	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
turnover	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
fall	null	O	VBD
point	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.07	null	PERCENT	CD
north	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
50	null	PERCENT	CD
Israel	null	LOCATION	NNP
enjoy	null	O	VBZ
support	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
point	null	O	NNS
have	null	O	VBZ
rating	null	O	NNS
north	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
50	null	PERCENT	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
sale	null	O	NNS
jump	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
75	null	PERCENT	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
sale	null	O	NNS
grow	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
33.8	null	PERCENT	CD
japanese	null	MISC	JJ
price	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VBD
close	null	O	VB
TOKYO	null	LOCATION	NNP
0.27	null	PERCENT	CD
japanese	null	MISC	JJ
price	null	O	NNS
close	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.27	null	PERCENT	CD
chinese	null	LOCATION	JJ
price	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
rise	null	O	NN
relief	null	O	NN
amid	null	O	IN
close	null	O	VBD
close	null	O	VB
TOKYO	null	LOCATION	NNP
0.27	null	PERCENT	CD
chinese	null	LOCATION	JJ
price	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
rise	null	O	NN
relief	null	O	NN
amid	null	O	IN
close	null	O	VBD
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
0.27	null	PERCENT	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
share	null	O	NNS
morning	null	TIME	NN
0.72	null	PERCENT	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
price	null	O	NNS
morning	null	TIME	NN
0.72	null	PERCENT	CD
Germany	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
holiday	null	O	NN
rise	null	O	VBD
point	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
3.20	null	PERCENT	CD
japanese	null	MISC	JJ
price	null	O	NNS
rise	null	O	VBP
show	null	O	VBD
gain	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
1.50	null	PERCENT	CD
japanese	null	MISC	JJ
price	null	O	NNS
rise	null	O	VBP
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
1.63	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
giant	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
respect	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
clear	null	O	VB
filing	null	O	NN
welcome	null	O	VBD
rise	null	O	VBP
show	null	O	VBD
gain	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
1.50	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
giant	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
respect	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
clear	null	O	VB
filing	null	O	NN
welcome	null	O	VBD
rise	null	O	VBP
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
1.63	null	PERCENT	CD
Ukraine	null	LOCATION	NNP
through	null	O	IN
pass	null	O	VBP
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
80	null	PERCENT	CD
Chinese	null	LOCATION	NNP
household	null	O	NNS
Kinh	null	PERSON	NNP
have	null	O	VBD
rate	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
10	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
share	null	O	NN
fall	null	O	VBP
Motors	null	ORGANIZATION	NNPS
CHICAGO	null	LOCATION	NNP
30	null	PERCENT	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
as	null	O	IN
market	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
evaporate	null	O	VBG
by	null	O	IN
hit	null	O	VBN
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
automaker	null	O	NN
close	null	O	VB
slash	null	O	NNS
lower	null	O	VB
by	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
sale	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
term	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
40	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NN
help	null	O	VB
restructure	null	O	NN
receive	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
60	null	PERCENT	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
government	null	O	NNS
provide	null	O	VB
receive	null	O	VB
stake	null	O	NN
12	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
35	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
55	null	PERCENT	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
10	null	PERCENT	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
35	null	PERCENT	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
55	null	PERCENT	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
government	null	O	NNS
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
10	null	PERCENT	CD
Azerbaijan	null	LOCATION	NNP
record	null	O	VBD
in	null	O	IN
sector	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
13.7	null	PERCENT	CD
Azerbaijan	null	LOCATION	NNP
economy	null	O	NN
grow	null	O	VBD
by	null	O	IN
