Germany	null	LOCATION	NNP
partner	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
30	null	DURATION	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
partner	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
30	null	DURATION	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
partner	null	O	NN
partner	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
30	null	DURATION	CD
Germany	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
partner	null	O	NN
partner	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
30	null	DURATION	CD
Vietnam	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Limited	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
company	null	O	NN
keep	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
22	null	DURATION	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
with	null	O	IN
contract	null	O	NNS
keep	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
22	null	DURATION	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
alligator	null	O	NNS
exist	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
million	null	DURATION	CD
200	null	DURATION	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
industry	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
development	null	O	NN
over	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
30	null	DURATION	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
industry	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
achievement	null	O	NNS
over	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
60	null	DURATION	CD
Indian	null	MISC	NNP
Express	null	MISC	NNP
hit	null	O	VBD
flood	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
over	null	O	IN
today	null	DATE	NN
100	null	DATE	CD
chinese	null	LOCATION	JJ
student	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
program	null	O	NN
BEIJING	null	LOCATION	NNP
benefit	null	O	VBN
organizer	null	O	NN
student	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
China	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Foundation	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
surpass	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
U.S.	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NNS
yuan	null	MONEY	NN
surpass	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
France	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Boeing	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
777	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Africa	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
live	null	O	VBD
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
40	null	DURATION	CD
Austria	null	LOCATION	NNP
agency	null	O	NN
tell	null	O	VBD
find	null	O	VBN
Ploechl	null	PERSON	NNP
live	null	O	VBD
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
40	null	DURATION	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
26	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
26	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
26	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
26	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
26	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
26	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
26	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
official	null	O	NNS
process	null	O	NN
able	null	O	JJ
reemerge	null	O	VB
within	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
90	null	DURATION	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Union	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
make	null	O	VBN
representative	null	O	NN
appoint	null	O	VBN
step	null	O	VBD
year	null	DATE	NNS
10	null	DATE	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Nations	null	ORGANIZATION	NNPS
Union	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
make	null	O	VBN
representative	null	O	NN
appoint	null	O	VBN
step	null	O	VBD
year	null	DATE	NNS
10	null	DATE	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
Union	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
make	null	O	VBN
representative	null	O	NN
appoint	null	O	VBN
step	null	O	VBD
year	null	DATE	NNS
10	null	DATE	CD
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
with	null	O	IN
establish	null	O	VB
want	null	O	VBZ
say	null	O	VBN
Funes	null	PERSON	NNP
president	null	O	NN
elect	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
american	null	MISC	JJ
holdout	null	O	NN
as	null	O	IN
status	null	O	NN
end	null	O	VBG
establish	null	O	VB
want	null	O	VBZ
say	null	O	VBN
Funes	null	PERSON	NNP
president	null	O	NN
elect	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
recession	null	O	NN
fight	null	O	VBG
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
30	null	DURATION	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
Hengelo	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
1	null	DATE	CD
ethiopian	null	MISC	JJ
June	null	DATE	NNP
1	null	DATE	CD
kenyan	null	MISC	JJ
Kiprop	null	PERSON	NNP
by	null	O	IN
win	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
3min	null	O	JJ
sec	null	DURATION	NN
34.45	null	DURATION	CD
ethiopian	null	MISC	JJ
Mekonnen	null	PERSON	NNP
of	null	O	IN
ahead	null	O	RB
3min	null	O	JJ
sec	null	DURATION	NN
34.45	null	DURATION	CD
Moroccan	null	MISC	NNP
Moustaoui	null	PERSON	NNP
Mekonnen	null	PERSON	NNP
of	null	O	IN
ahead	null	O	RB
3min	null	O	JJ
sec	null	DURATION	NN
34.45	null	DURATION	CD
iraqi	null	LOCATION	JJ
Jassam	null	PERSON	NNP
hold	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
250	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
army	null	O	NN
by	null	O	IN
hold	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
250	null	DURATION	CD
iraqi	null	LOCATION	JJ
order	null	O	NN
despite	null	O	IN
hold	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
250	null	DURATION	CD
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
Salvador	null	LOCATION	NNP
reestablish	null	O	VBP
tie	null	O	NNS
sign	null	O	VBD
document	null	O	NN
reestablish	null	O	VB
break	null	O	VBN
since	null	O	IN
revolution	null	O	NN
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
50	null	DATE	CD
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
SALVADOR	null	LOCATION	NNP
sign	null	O	VBD
document	null	O	NN
reestablish	null	O	VB
break	null	O	VBN
since	null	O	IN
revolution	null	O	NN
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
50	null	DATE	CD
cuban	null	MISC	JJ
revolution	null	O	NN
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
50	null	DATE	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
Hengelo	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
1	null	DATE	CD
ethiopian	null	MISC	JJ
June	null	DATE	NNP
1	null	DATE	CD
kenyan	null	MISC	JJ
Kiprop	null	PERSON	NNP
by	null	O	IN
win	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
3min	null	O	JJ
sec	null	DURATION	NN
34.45	null	DURATION	CD
ethiopian	null	MISC	JJ
Mekonnen	null	PERSON	NNP
of	null	O	IN
ahead	null	O	RB
3min	null	O	JJ
sec	null	DURATION	NN
34.45	null	DURATION	CD
Moroccan	null	MISC	NNP
Moustaoui	null	PERSON	NNP
Mekonnen	null	PERSON	NNP
of	null	O	IN
ahead	null	O	RB
3min	null	O	JJ
sec	null	DURATION	NN
34.45	null	DURATION	CD
dutch	null	O	JJ
Antilles	null	O	NNPS
of	null	O	IN
Martina	null	PERSON	NNP
gain	null	O	VBD
record	null	O	VBG
seconds	null	NUMBER	NNS
9.97	null	DURATION	CD
dutch	null	O	JJ
Antilles	null	O	NNPS
of	null	O	IN
Martina	null	PERSON	NNP
gain	null	O	VBD
record	null	O	VBG
finish	null	O	VBD
seventh	null	ORDINAL	JJ
sec	null	DURATION	NN
0.30	null	DURATION	CD
american	null	MISC	JJ
finish	null	O	VBD
record	null	O	VBG
seconds	null	NUMBER	NNS
9.97	null	DURATION	CD
american	null	MISC	JJ
finish	null	O	VBD
seventh	null	ORDINAL	JJ
sec	null	DURATION	NN
0.30	null	DURATION	CD
dutch	null	O	JJ
Antilles	null	O	NNPS
deprive	null	O	VBD
see	null	O	VBD
take	null	O	VB
behind	null	O	IN
bolt	null	PERSON	NN
win	null	O	VBD
in	null	O	IN
record	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
seconds	null	NUMBER	NNS
19.30	null	DURATION	CD
jamaican	null	PERSON	JJ
bolt	null	PERSON	NN
win	null	O	VBD
in	null	O	IN
record	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
seconds	null	NUMBER	NNS
19.30	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
giant	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
plan	null	O	NN
reemerge	null	O	VB
within	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
90	null	DURATION	CD
spanish	null	LOCATION	JJ
champion	null	O	NNS
say	null	O	VBD
sideline	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
15	null	DURATION	CD
VENEZUELA	null	LOCATION	NNP
2005	null	DATE	CD
kill	null	O	VBN
run-down	null	O	JJ
PARIS	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
1	null	DATE	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
citizen	null	O	NNS
include	null	O	VBG
kill	null	O	VBN
run-down	null	O	JJ
PARIS	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
1	null	DATE	CD
colombian	null	LOCATION	JJ
Airways	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
belong	null	O	VBG
crash	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
kill	null	O	VBN
run-down	null	O	JJ
PARIS	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
1	null	DATE	CD
north	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
Airways	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
belong	null	O	VBG
crash	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
kill	null	O	VBN
run-down	null	O	JJ
PARIS	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
1	null	DATE	CD
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
Salvador	null	LOCATION	NNP
reestablish	null	O	VBP
tie	null	O	NNS
sign	null	O	VBD
document	null	O	NN
reestablish	null	O	VB
break	null	O	VBN
since	null	O	IN
revolution	null	O	NN
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
50	null	DATE	CD
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
Salvador	null	LOCATION	NNP
SALVADOR	null	LOCATION	NNP
sign	null	O	VBD
document	null	O	NN
reestablish	null	O	VB
break	null	O	VBN
since	null	O	IN
revolution	null	O	NN
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
50	null	DATE	CD
cuban	null	MISC	JJ
revolution	null	O	NN
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
50	null	DATE	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
Open	null	O	NNP
championship	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
year	null	DATE	NN
start	null	O	VBZ
on	null	O	IN
June	null	DATE	NNP
18	null	DATE	CD
GEORGIA	null	LOCATION	NNP
vote	null	O	VB
honor	null	O	VB
memory	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
those	null	O	DT
kill	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
crackdown	null	O	NN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
Niger	null	LOCATION	NNP
president	null	O	NN
confirm	null	O	VBN
go	null	O	VBG
organise	null	O	VB
on	null	O	IN
constitution	null	O	NN
enable	null	O	VBG
stay	null	O	VB
run	null	O	VBZ
on	null	O	IN
December	null	DATE	NNP
22	null	DATE	CD
Iraq	null	LOCATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBZ
dam	null	O	NNS
build	null	O	VBN
over	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
30	null	DURATION	CD
Turkey	null	LOCATION	NNP
build	null	O	VBN
over	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
30	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
giant	null	O	NN
re-emerge	null	O	VB
within	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
90	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
official	null	O	NNS
process	null	O	NN
able	null	O	JJ
reemerge	null	O	VB
within	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
90	null	DURATION	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
Hengelo	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
1	null	DATE	CD
ethiopian	null	MISC	JJ
June	null	DATE	NNP
1	null	DATE	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
Wozniak	null	PERSON	NNP
see	null	O	VB
take	null	O	VBD
minute	null	NUMBER	NNS
53	null	DURATION	CD
polish	null	MISC	JJ
Radwanska	null	PERSON	NNP
against	null	O	IN
triumph	null	O	VBD
take	null	O	VBD
minute	null	NUMBER	NNS
53	null	DURATION	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
office	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBZ
hit	null	O	VBN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
1,000	null	SET	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Waziristan	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
area	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
attack	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
kill	null	O	VBN
hour	null	DATE	NNS
24	null	DATE	CD
Afghanistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
border	null	O	VBZ
Waziristan	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
area	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
attack	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
kill	null	O	VBN
hour	null	DATE	NNS
24	null	DATE	CD
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
Salvador	null	LOCATION	NNP
reestablish	null	O	VBP
tie	null	O	NNS
sign	null	O	VBD
document	null	O	NN
reestablish	null	O	VB
break	null	O	VBN
since	null	O	IN
revolution	null	O	NN
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
50	null	DATE	CD
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
Salvador	null	LOCATION	NNP
Salvador	null	LOCATION	NNP
sign	null	O	VBD
document	null	O	NN
reestablish	null	O	VB
break	null	O	VBN
since	null	O	IN
revolution	null	O	NN
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
50	null	DATE	CD
cuban	null	MISC	JJ
revolution	null	O	NN
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
50	null	DATE	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
take	null	O	VBD
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
65	null	DATE	CD
German	null	MISC	NNP
troops	null	O	NNS
against	null	O	IN
take	null	O	VBD
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
65	null	DATE	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
colonel	null	O	NN
Parish	null	PERSON	NNP
hear	null	O	VB
in	null	O	IN
case	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
Khadr	null	PERSON	NNP
old	null	DURATION	JJ
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
15	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
sergeant	null	O	NN
kill	null	O	VBD
old	null	DURATION	JJ
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
15	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
ask	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
120	null	DURATION	CD
indian	null	MISC	JJ
dive	null	O	NN
plunge	null	O	VBD
slide	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
18	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
ask	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
120	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
lead	null	O	JJ
hold	null	O	VB
in	null	O	IN
case	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
accuse	null	O	VBN
of	null	O	IN
kill	null	O	VBG
old	null	DURATION	JJ
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
15	null	DURATION	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
accuse	null	O	VBN
of	null	O	IN
kill	null	O	VBG
old	null	DURATION	JJ
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
15	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
soldier	null	O	NN
kill	null	O	VBG
old	null	DURATION	JJ
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
15	null	DURATION	CD
Afghanistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
soldier	null	O	NN
kill	null	O	VBG
old	null	DURATION	JJ
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
15	null	DURATION	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
26	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
26	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
26	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
26	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
26	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
26	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
26	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
26	null	NUMBER	CD
France	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
have	null	O	VBN
news	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
hour	null	DURATION	NNS
from	null	O	IN
af	null	O	NN
447	null	NUMBER	CD
brazilian	null	MISC	JJ
Force	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
af	null	O	NN
447	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
on	null	O	IN
era	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
hearing	null	O	NN
hold	null	O	VBD
in	null	O	IN
case	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
accuse	null	O	VBN
of	null	O	IN
kill	null	O	VBG
old	null	DURATION	JJ
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
15	null	DURATION	CD
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
Base	null	O	NNP
on	null	O	IN
era	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
hearing	null	O	NN
hold	null	O	VBD
in	null	O	IN
case	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
accuse	null	O	VBN
of	null	O	IN
kill	null	O	VBG
old	null	DURATION	JJ
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
15	null	DURATION	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
accuse	null	O	VBN
of	null	O	IN
kill	null	O	VBG
old	null	DURATION	JJ
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
15	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
soldier	null	O	NN
kill	null	O	VBG
old	null	DURATION	JJ
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
15	null	DURATION	CD
Afghanistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
soldier	null	O	NN
kill	null	O	VBG
old	null	DURATION	JJ
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
15	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
ask	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
120	null	DURATION	CD
Thailand	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
sell	null	O	VBN
estimate	null	O	VBN
over	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
25	null	DURATION	CD
Laos	null	LOCATION	NNP
revenue	null	O	NNS
estimate	null	O	VBN
over	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
25	null	DURATION	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
staff	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
accord	null	O	VBG
plane	null	O	NN
remain	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
10	null	NUMBER	CD
12	null	DURATION	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
take	null	O	VBD
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
65	null	DATE	CD
German	null	MISC	NNP
troops	null	O	NNS
against	null	O	IN
take	null	O	VBD
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
65	null	DATE	CD
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
with	null	O	IN
relation	null	O	NNS
seek	null	O	VBZ
say	null	O	VBN
Funes	null	PERSON	NNP
president	null	O	NN
elect	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
american	null	MISC	JJ
holdout	null	O	NN
as	null	O	IN
status	null	O	NN
end	null	O	VBG
relation	null	O	NNS
seek	null	O	VBZ
say	null	O	VBN
Funes	null	PERSON	NNP
president	null	O	NN
elect	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
Afghan	null	MISC	NNP
government	null	O	NN
send	null	O	VBD
arrest	null	O	VBN
old	null	DURATION	JJ
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
12	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
embassy	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
letter	null	O	NN
send	null	O	VBD
arrest	null	O	VBN
old	null	DURATION	JJ
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
12	null	DURATION	CD
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
take	null	O	VBN
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
10	null	DURATION	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
26	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
26	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
26	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
26	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
26	null	NUMBER	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
26	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
IND	null	O	NNP
26	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
official	null	O	NNS
process	null	O	NN
able	null	O	JJ
reemerge	null	O	VB
within	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
90	null	DURATION	CD
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
with	null	O	IN
relation	null	O	NNS
restore	null	O	VBG
say	null	O	VBD
Funes	null	PERSON	NNP
leader	null	O	NN
elect	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
with	null	O	IN
relation	null	O	NNS
break	null	O	VBN
since	null	O	IN
revolution	null	O	NN
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
50	null	DATE	CD
cuban	null	MISC	JJ
revolution	null	O	NN
since	null	O	IN
break	null	O	VBN
relation	null	O	NNS
restore	null	O	VBG
say	null	O	VBD
Funes	null	PERSON	NNP
leader	null	O	NN
elect	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
cuban	null	MISC	JJ
revolution	null	O	NN
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
50	null	DATE	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
official	null	O	NNS
process	null	O	NN
able	null	O	JJ
reemerge	null	O	VB
within	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
90	null	DURATION	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
blame	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
attack	null	O	NNS
kill	null	O	VBD
people	null	O	NNS
160	null	NUMBER	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
post	null	O	NNS
Monday	null	DATE	NNP
OTTAWA	null	LOCATION	NNP
fall	null	DATE	NN
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
18	null	DURATION	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
post	null	O	NNS
Monday	null	DATE	NNP
post	null	O	VBD
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
18	null	DURATION	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
Monday	null	DATE	NNP
OTTAWA	null	LOCATION	NNP
fall	null	DATE	NN
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
18	null	DURATION	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
Monday	null	DATE	NNP
post	null	O	VBD
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
18	null	DURATION	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Waziristan	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
area	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
attack	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
kill	null	O	VBN
hour	null	DATE	NNS
24	null	DATE	CD
Afghanistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
border	null	O	VBZ
Waziristan	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
area	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
attack	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
kill	null	O	VBN
hour	null	DATE	NNS
24	null	DATE	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
post	null	O	VBZ
,2	null	NUMBER	CD
show	null	O	VBZ
figure	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
18	null	DURATION	CD
France	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
hit	null	O	NN
send	null	O	VBD
later	null	DATE	RB
minute	null	DATE	NNS
14	null	DATE	CD
France	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
say	null	O	VBD
make	null	O	VBN
flight	null	O	NNS
total	null	O	VBG
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
18,800	null	DURATION	CD
Iraq	null	LOCATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBZ
dam	null	O	NNS
build	null	O	VBN
over	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
30	null	DURATION	CD
Turkey	null	LOCATION	NNP
build	null	O	VBN
over	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
30	null	DURATION	CD
France	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
catastrophe	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
70	null	DURATION	CD
Greece	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
win	null	O	VBD
in	null	O	IN
season	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
seconds	null	NUMBER	NNS
10.06	null	DURATION	CD
France	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Boeing	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
777	null	NUMBER	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
take	null	O	VBD
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
65	null	DATE	CD
German	null	MISC	NNP
troops	null	O	NNS
against	null	O	IN
take	null	O	VBD
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
65	null	DATE	CD
France	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
say	null	O	VBD
make	null	O	VBN
flight	null	O	NNS
total	null	O	VBG
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
18,800	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
official	null	O	NNS
process	null	O	NN
able	null	O	JJ
reemerge	null	O	VB
within	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
90	null	DURATION	CD
libyan	null	MISC	JJ
government	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
critical	null	O	JJ
detain	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
hour	null	DATE	NNS
48	null	DATE	CD
egyptian	null	MISC	JJ
journalist	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
interview	null	O	NN
air	null	O	VBG
for	null	O	IN
detain	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
hour	null	DATE	NNS
48	null	DATE	CD
Egypt	null	LOCATION	NNP
regime	null	O	NN
criticise	null	O	VBG
journalist	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
interview	null	O	NN
air	null	O	VBG
for	null	O	IN
detain	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
hour	null	DATE	NNS
48	null	DATE	CD
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
with	null	O	IN
relation	null	O	NNS
restore	null	O	VBG
say	null	O	VBD
Funes	null	PERSON	NNP
leader	null	O	NN
elect	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
with	null	O	IN
relation	null	O	NNS
break	null	O	VBN
since	null	O	IN
revolution	null	O	NN
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
50	null	DATE	CD
cuban	null	MISC	JJ
revolution	null	O	NN
since	null	O	IN
break	null	O	VBN
relation	null	O	NNS
restore	null	O	VBG
say	null	O	VBD
Funes	null	PERSON	NNP
leader	null	O	NN
elect	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
cuban	null	MISC	JJ
revolution	null	O	NN
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
50	null	DATE	CD
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
with	null	O	IN
relation	null	O	NNS
seek	null	O	VBZ
say	null	O	VBN
Funes	null	PERSON	NNP
president	null	O	NN
elect	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
american	null	MISC	JJ
holdout	null	O	NN
as	null	O	IN
status	null	O	NN
end	null	O	VBG
relation	null	O	NNS
seek	null	O	VBZ
say	null	O	VBN
Funes	null	PERSON	NNP
president	null	O	NN
elect	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
blame	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
attack	null	O	NNS
kill	null	O	VBD
people	null	O	NNS
160	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
for	null	O	IN
call	null	O	VBN
Einhorn	null	PERSON	NNP
work	null	O	VBD
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
29	null	DURATION	CD
North	null	LOCATION	NNP
Korea	null	LOCATION	NNP
accept	null	O	VB
Einhorn	null	PERSON	NNP
work	null	O	VBD
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
29	null	DURATION	CD
Iran	null	LOCATION	NNP
Korea	null	LOCATION	NNP
accept	null	O	VB
Einhorn	null	PERSON	NNP
work	null	O	VBD
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
29	null	DURATION	CD
Rwanda	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
try	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
killing	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
civilian	null	O	NNS
15	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
market	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
share	null	O	NN
fall	null	O	VBD
shrink	null	O	VB
rank	null	O	NN
see	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
year	null	DATE	NNS
30	null	DATE	CD
Niger	null	LOCATION	NNP
president	null	O	NN
confirm	null	O	VBN
go	null	O	VBG
organise	null	O	VB
on	null	O	IN
constitution	null	O	NN
enable	null	O	VBG
stay	null	O	VB
run	null	O	VBZ
on	null	O	IN
December	null	DATE	NNP
22	null	DATE	CD
Afghan	null	MISC	NNP
government	null	O	NN
send	null	O	VBN
arrest	null	O	VBN
old	null	DURATION	JJ
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
12	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
embassy	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
letter	null	O	NN
send	null	O	VBN
arrest	null	O	VBN
old	null	DURATION	JJ
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
12	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
crime	null	O	NN
drop	null	O	VBZ
washington	null	O	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
1	null	DATE	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
in	null	O	IN
crime	null	O	NN
drop	null	O	VBZ
washington	null	O	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
1	null	DATE	CD
indian	null	MISC	JJ
dive	null	O	NN
plunge	null	O	VBD
slide	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
18	null	DURATION	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
Frey	null	PERSON	NNP
with	null	O	IN
blaze	null	O	VBD
finish	null	O	VBN
on	null	O	IN
minute	null	NUMBER	NNS
62	null	DURATION	CD
australian	null	MISC	JJ
Open	null	MISC	NNP
Wimbledon	null	MISC	NNP
win	null	O	VBD
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
12	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
authority	null	O	NNS
clear	null	O	VBD
Uighurs	null	MISC	NNPS
17	null	NUMBER	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
province	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
return	null	O	VBD
torture	null	O	VB
fear	null	O	NNS
to	null	O	TO
due	null	O	JJ
prison	null	O	NN
at	null	O	IN
stick	null	O	VBN
clear	null	O	VBD
Uighurs	null	MISC	NNPS
17	null	NUMBER	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
Frey	null	PERSON	NNP
with	null	O	IN
blaze	null	O	VBD
finish	null	O	VBN
on	null	O	IN
minute	null	NUMBER	NNS
62	null	DURATION	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
be	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
17	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
army	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
chaplain	null	O	NN
Xiong	null	PERSON	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
be	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
17	null	DURATION	CD
romanian	null	MISC	JJ
scamper	null	O	VB
force	null	O	VBG
with	null	O	IN
wrap	null	O	VBN
opening	null	O	NN
set	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
minute	null	NUMBER	NNS
25	null	DURATION	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
beijing	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
date	null	O	NNS
after	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
10	null	DURATION	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
history	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
date	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
list	null	O	NN
date	null	O	NNS
after	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
10	null	DURATION	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
find	null	O	VBZ
after	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
10	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
president	null	O	NN
meet	null	O	VBD
meet	null	O	VBD
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
10	null	DURATION	CD
Israel	null	LOCATION	NNP
freeze	null	O	VBZ
resume	null	O	VB
vow	null	O	VBN
Abbas	null	PERSON	NNP
meet	null	O	VBD
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
10	null	DURATION	CD
Slovakia	null	LOCATION	NNP
mintal	null	PERSON	JJ
score	null	O	VBD
score	null	O	VBD
after	null	O	IN
minute	null	NUMBER	NNS
29	null	DURATION	CD
Slovakia	null	LOCATION	NNP
mintal	null	PERSON	JJ
score	null	O	VBD
on	null	O	IN
minute	null	NUMBER	NNS
37	null	DURATION	CD
Iran	null	LOCATION	NNP
hang	null	O	VBD
man	null	O	NNS
accuse	null	O	VBN
of	null	O	IN
involvement	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
bombing	null	O	NN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
48	null	DURATION	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Africa	null	LOCATION	NNP
add	null	O	VB
title	null	O	NN
set	null	O	VB
in	null	O	IN
win	null	O	VBG
during	null	O	IN
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
12	null	DURATION	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
against	null	O	IN
twenty20	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
both	null	O	DT
win	null	O	VBD
Africa	null	LOCATION	NNP
add	null	O	VB
title	null	O	NN
set	null	O	VB
in	null	O	IN
win	null	O	VBG
during	null	O	IN
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
12	null	DURATION	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
win	null	O	VBG
during	null	O	IN
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
12	null	DURATION	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
win	null	O	VBG
during	null	O	IN
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
12	null	DURATION	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
into	null	O	IN
pour	null	O	VBG
with	null	O	IN
follow	null	O	VBG
sweep	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
haul	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
18	null	DURATION	CD
Egypt	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
live	null	O	VBD
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
14	null	DURATION	CD
Sudan	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
return	null	O	VBG
live	null	O	VBD
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
14	null	DURATION	CD
Jamaica	null	LOCATION	NNP
Bolt	null	PERSON	NNP
win	null	O	VBD
sec	null	DURATION	NN
19.30	null	DURATION	CD
Belgium	null	LOCATION	NNP
third	null	ORDINAL	JJ
with	null	O	IN
finish	null	O	VBN
seconds	null	NUMBER	NNS
18	null	DURATION	CD
Belgium	null	LOCATION	NNP
third	null	ORDINAL	JJ
with	null	O	IN
finish	null	O	VBN
back	null	O	RB
seconds	null	NUMBER	NNS
28	null	DURATION	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
soil	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
foot	null	O	NN
set	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
17	null	DURATION	CD
Iran	null	LOCATION	NNP
hang	null	O	VBD
man	null	O	NNS
accuse	null	O	VBN
of	null	O	IN
involvement	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
bombing	null	O	NN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
48	null	DURATION	CD
Angola	null	LOCATION	NNP
rank	null	O	VBZ
as	null	O	IN
one	null	NUMBER	CD
of	null	O	IN
place	null	O	NNS
set	null	O	VB
with	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
68	null	DURATION	CD
Russian	null	MISC	NNP
concede	null	O	VBN
match	null	O	NNS
advertisement	null	O	NN
capitulate	null	O	VBD
in	null	O	IN
minute	null	NUMBER	NNS
53	null	DURATION	CD
hungarian	null	MISC	JJ
steady	null	O	VBD
be	null	O	VBD
take	null	O	VBG
6-2	null	NUMBER	CD
in	null	O	IN
minute	null	NUMBER	NNS
38	null	DURATION	CD
malawian	null	LOCATION	JJ
hero	null	O	NN
connect	null	O	VBG
with	null	O	IN
cross	null	O	NNS
score	null	NUMBER	VB
on	null	O	IN
minute	null	NUMBER	NNS
64	null	NUMBER	CD
83	null	DURATION	CD
Rwanda	null	LOCATION	NNP
against	null	O	IN
hero	null	O	NN
connect	null	O	VBG
with	null	O	IN
cross	null	O	NNS
score	null	NUMBER	VB
on	null	O	IN
minute	null	NUMBER	NNS
64	null	NUMBER	CD
83	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
president	null	O	NN
meet	null	O	VBD
meet	null	O	VBD
week	null	DATE	NN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
10	null	DURATION	CD
Israel	null	LOCATION	NNP
freeze	null	O	VBZ
relaunch	null	O	VB
vow	null	O	VBN
Abbas	null	PERSON	NNP
meet	null	O	VBD
week	null	DATE	NN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
10	null	DURATION	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Nations	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBZ
hold	null	O	VBN
on	null	O	IN
sentence	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
60	null	DURATION	CD
Myanmar	null	LOCATION	NNP
prison	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
hold	null	O	VBN
on	null	O	IN
sentence	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
60	null	DURATION	CD
hungarian	null	MISC	JJ
steady	null	O	VBD
be	null	O	VBD
take	null	O	VBG
6-2	null	NUMBER	CD
in	null	O	IN
minute	null	NUMBER	NNS
38	null	DURATION	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
soil	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
foot	null	O	NN
set	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
17	null	DURATION	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
military	null	O	JJ
crushed	null	O	JJ
on	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
german	null	MISC	JJ
city	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
huddle	null	O	NN
mean	null	O	VBZ
will	null	O	MD
after	null	O	IN
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
18	null	DURATION	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
soil	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
foot	null	O	NN
set	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
17	null	DURATION	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
official	null	O	NN
Beijing	null	LOCATION	NNP
on	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
people	null	O	NNS
waste	null	O	VBN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
60	null	DURATION	CD
spanish	null	LOCATION	JJ
building	null	O	NNS
on	null	O	IN
symbol	null	O	NNS
adorn	null	O	VB
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
30	null	DURATION	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
building	null	O	NNS
adorn	null	O	VB
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
30	null	DURATION	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
escape	null	O	VB
manage	null	O	VBD
after	null	O	IN
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
10	null	DURATION	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
Earls	null	PERSON	NNP
Munster	null	PERSON	NNP
from	null	O	IN
inherit	null	O	VBG
member	null	O	NN
man	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
12	null	DURATION	CD
Iran	null	LOCATION	NNP
hang	null	O	VBD
man	null	O	NNS
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
48	null	DURATION	CD
romanian	null	MISC	JJ
scamper	null	O	VB
force	null	O	VBG
with	null	O	IN
wrap	null	O	VBN
opening	null	O	NN
set	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
minute	null	NUMBER	NNS
25	null	DURATION	CD
french	null	LOCATION	JJ
region	null	O	NN
wine	null	O	NNS
sell	null	O	VBN
as	null	O	IN
commodity	null	O	NN
prior	null	O	RB
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
12	null	DURATION	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
for	null	O	IN
debut	null	O	VB
player	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
132	null	DURATION	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Wales	null	LOCATION	NNP
for	null	O	IN
knock	null	O	VB
club	null	O	VBG
after	null	O	IN
reputation	null	O	NN
debut	null	O	VB
player	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
132	null	DURATION	CD
Wales	null	LOCATION	NNP
for	null	O	IN
knock	null	O	VB
club	null	O	VBG
after	null	O	IN
reputation	null	O	NN
debut	null	O	VB
player	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
132	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
president	null	O	NN
meet	null	O	VBD
meet	null	O	VBD
week	null	DATE	NN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
10	null	DURATION	CD
Israel	null	LOCATION	NNP
freeze	null	O	VBZ
relaunch	null	O	VB
vow	null	O	VBN
Abbas	null	PERSON	NNP
meet	null	O	VBD
week	null	DATE	NN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
10	null	DURATION	CD
Japan	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Association	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
accord	null	O	VBG
sell	null	O	VBN
compare	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
221,377	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
president	null	O	NN
drop	null	O	VBN
by	null	O	IN
for	null	O	IN
minute	null	NUMBER	NNS
12	null	DURATION	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
Franchitti	null	PERSON	NNP
of	null	O	IN
behind	null	O	IN
settle	null	O	VBN
sec	null	DURATION	NN
2.125	null	DURATION	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
army	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBZ
kill	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
hour	null	DATE	NNS
24	null	DATE	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
army	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBZ
kill	null	O	VBN
say	null	O	VBD
kill	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
24	null	DURATION	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
military	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
kill	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
hour	null	DATE	NNS
24	null	DATE	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
military	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
kill	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
24	null	DURATION	CD
iranian	null	MISC	JJ
city	null	O	NN
erupt	null	O	VBD
go	null	O	VBZ
in	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
10	null	DURATION	CD
Germany	null	LOCATION	NNP
airport	null	O	NN
at	null	O	IN
maintain	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
year	null	DATE	NNS
10	null	DATE	CD
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
with	null	O	IN
relation	null	O	NNS
restore	null	O	VBG
say	null	O	VBD
Funes	null	PERSON	NNP
leader	null	O	NN
elect	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
with	null	O	IN
relation	null	O	NNS
break	null	O	VBN
since	null	O	IN
revolution	null	O	NN
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
50	null	DATE	CD
cuban	null	MISC	JJ
revolution	null	O	NN
since	null	O	IN
break	null	O	VBN
relation	null	O	NNS
restore	null	O	VBG
say	null	O	VBD
Funes	null	PERSON	NNP
leader	null	O	NN
elect	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
cuban	null	MISC	JJ
revolution	null	O	NN
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
50	null	DATE	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Africa	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
lift	null	O	VBD
requirement	null	O	NNS
for	null	O	IN
immigrant	null	O	NNS
enter	null	O	VBG
country	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
period	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
90	null	DURATION	CD
zimbabwean	null	LOCATION	JJ
immigrant	null	O	NNS
enter	null	O	VBG
country	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
period	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
90	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
population	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
percent	null	PERCENT	NN
Muslims	null	MISC	NNPS
old	null	DURATION	JJ
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
18	null	DURATION	CD
argentine	null	MISC	JJ
be	null	O	VBD
play	null	O	VBG
in	null	O	IN
game	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
way	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
claim	null	O	VBG
set	null	O	NN
after	null	O	IN
minute	null	NUMBER	NNS
34	null	DURATION	CD
american	null	LOCATION	JJ
warplane	null	O	NNS
drop	null	O	VBD
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
35	null	DURATION	CD
Vietnam	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
area	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
drop	null	O	VBD
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
35	null	DURATION	CD
Iraq	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
live	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
30	null	DURATION	CD
Iraq	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
12	null	DURATION	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
unemployment	null	O	NN
fall	null	O	VBZ
see	null	O	VBD
time	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
year	null	DURATION	NN
MADRID	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
2	null	DATE	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
MADRID	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
2	null	DATE	CD
argentine	null	MISC	JJ
be	null	O	VBD
play	null	O	VBG
in	null	O	IN
game	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
way	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
claim	null	O	VBG
set	null	O	NN
after	null	O	IN
minute	null	NUMBER	NNS
34	null	DURATION	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
government	null	O	NN
stop	null	O	VBZ
to	null	O	TO
silence	null	O	NN
happen	null	O	VBD
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
20	null	DATE	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
sap	null	O	VBG
drain	null	O	NN
reverse	null	O	VB
eager	null	O	JJ
welcome	null	O	VBN
know	null	O	VBP
swear	null	O	VBN
about	null	O	IN
event	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
20	null	DATE	CD
Israel	null	LOCATION	NNP
Jerusalem	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
return	null	O	VBZ
take	null	O	VBD
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
12	null	DATE	CD
Israel	null	LOCATION	NNP
Authority	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
take	null	O	VBD
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
12	null	DATE	CD
BRAZIL	null	LOCATION	NNP
Graphic	null	O	NNP
by	null	O	IN
mm	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
principle	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
survive	null	O	VBZ
strike	null	O	NN
occurrence	null	O	NN
happen	null	O	VBZ
in	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
1,000	null	DURATION	CD
FRANCE	null	LOCATION	NNP
Graphic	null	O	NNP
by	null	O	IN
mm	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
principle	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
survive	null	O	VBZ
strike	null	O	NN
occurrence	null	O	NN
happen	null	O	VBZ
in	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
1,000	null	DURATION	CD
Germany	null	LOCATION	NNP
footballer	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
Dzeko	null	PERSON	NNP
Wolfsburg	null	LOCATION	NNP
Berlin	null	LOCATION	NNP
2	null	DATE	CD
Germany	null	LOCATION	NNP
footballer	null	O	NN
name	null	O	VBN
footballer	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
Dzeko	null	PERSON	NNP
Wolfsburg	null	LOCATION	NNP
Berlin	null	LOCATION	NNP
2	null	DATE	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
against	null	O	IN
twenty20	null	O	NN
since	null	O	IN
use	null	O	VBN
duo	null	O	NNS
11	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
use	null	O	VBN
duo	null	O	NNS
11	null	NUMBER	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
military	null	O	JJ
crushed	null	O	JJ
on	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
Iraq	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
live	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
30	null	DURATION	CD
Iraq	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
12	null	DURATION	CD
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
readmit	null	O	VBD
after	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
47	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
Obama	null	PERSON	NNP
hold	null	O	VBZ
thlead-wrap	null	O	JJ
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
readmit	null	O	VBD
after	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
47	null	DURATION	CD
British	null	MISC	NNP
Brown	null	PERSON	NNP
lose	null	O	VBZ
within	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
24	null	DURATION	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
on	null	O	IN
call	null	O	VBD
free	null	O	VB
dozen	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
prisoner	null	O	NNS
believe	null	O	VBN
be	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
take	null	O	VBG
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
20	null	DATE	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
market	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
share	null	O	NN
higher	null	O	JJR
sell	null	O	VBD
month	null	DATE	NN
with	null	O	IN
vehicle	null	O	NNS
74,741	null	NUMBER	CD
Mauritania	null	LOCATION	NNP
president	null	O	NN
topple	null	O	VBD
coup	null	O	NN
follow	null	O	VBG
end	null	O	VB
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
10	null	DURATION	CD
Indonesia	null	LOCATION	NNP
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
10	null	DURATION	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
government	null	O	NN
stop	null	O	VBZ
to	null	O	TO
silence	null	O	NN
happen	null	O	VBD
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
20	null	DATE	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
on	null	O	IN
call	null	O	VBD
free	null	O	VB
dozen	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
prisoner	null	O	NNS
believe	null	O	VBN
be	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
take	null	O	VBG
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
20	null	DATE	CD
french	null	LOCATION	JJ
frustration	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
26	null	DURATION	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
military	null	O	JJ
crushed	null	O	JJ
on	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
against	null	O	IN
protest	null	O	NN
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
20	null	DATE	CD
Singapore	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
take	null	O	VBD
hour	null	DURATION	NN
minute	null	NUMBER	NNS
40	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
official	null	O	NNS
process	null	O	NN
able	null	O	JJ
reemerge	null	O	VB
within	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
90	null	DURATION	CD
bosnian	null	MISC	JJ
jail	null	O	VBN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
40	null	DURATION	CD
bosnian	null	MISC	JJ
jail	null	O	VBN
sentence	null	O	VBN
to	null	O	TO
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
40	null	DURATION	CD
bosnian	null	MISC	JJ
gunman	null	O	NN
SARAJEVO	null	LOCATION	NNP
sentence	null	O	VBN
jail	null	O	VBN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
40	null	DURATION	CD
bosnian	null	MISC	JJ
gunman	null	O	NN
SARAJEVO	null	LOCATION	NNP
sentence	null	O	VBN
to	null	O	TO
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
40	null	DURATION	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
pm	null	O	NN
government	null	O	NN
from	null	O	IN
minister	null	O	NN
quit	null	O	VBZ
vid83596	null	O	NN
nsv	null	O	NN
voice	null	O	VBN
report	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
resign	null	O	VBG
make	null	O	VBG
fourth	null	ORDINAL	JJ
go	null	O	VB
in	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
24	null	DURATION	CD
british	null	LOCATION	JJ
Brown	null	PERSON	NNP
cabinet	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
member	null	O	NN
quit	null	O	VBZ
vid83596	null	O	NN
nsv	null	O	NN
voice	null	O	VBN
report	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
resign	null	O	VBG
make	null	O	VBG
fourth	null	ORDINAL	JJ
go	null	O	VB
in	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
24	null	DURATION	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
people	null	O	NNS
have	null	O	VBP
take	null	O	VBD
tell	null	O	VBD
refer	null	O	VBG
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
60	null	DATE	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
Secretary	null	O	NNP
opening	null	O	NN
start	null	O	VBG
after	null	O	IN
9	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
stick	null	O	VBD
demand	null	O	NNS
free	null	O	JJ
return	null	O	VBZ
to	null	O	TO
body	null	O	NN
suspend	null	O	VBN
from	null	O	IN
year	null	DATE	NNS
47	null	DATE	CD
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
free	null	O	JJ
return	null	O	VBZ
to	null	O	TO
body	null	O	NN
suspend	null	O	VBN
from	null	O	IN
year	null	DATE	NNS
47	null	DATE	CD
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
Salvador	null	LOCATION	NNP
reestablish	null	O	VBP
reestablish	null	O	VBD
tie	null	O	NNS
break	null	O	VBN
since	null	O	IN
revolution	null	O	NN
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
50	null	DATE	CD
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
Salvador	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
reestablish	null	O	VBD
tie	null	O	NNS
break	null	O	VBN
since	null	O	IN
revolution	null	O	NN
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
50	null	DATE	CD
cuban	null	MISC	JJ
revolution	null	O	NN
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
50	null	DATE	CD
Sweden	null	LOCATION	NNP
bury	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
100,000	null	DURATION	CD
Sweden	null	LOCATION	NNP
bury	null	O	VB
venture	null	O	VBG
of	null	O	IN
shadow	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
OSKARSHAMN	null	LOCATION	NNP
Sweden	null	LOCATION	NNP
take	null	O	VBZ
seconds	null	NUMBER	NNS
90	null	DURATION	CD
Syria	null	LOCATION	NNP
OSKARSHAMN	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
shadow	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
venture	null	O	VBG
bury	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
100,000	null	DURATION	CD
Syria	null	LOCATION	NNP
OSKARSHAMN	null	LOCATION	NNP
Sweden	null	LOCATION	NNP
take	null	O	VBZ
seconds	null	NUMBER	NNS
90	null	DURATION	CD
Sweden	null	LOCATION	NNP
OSKARSHAMN	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
shadow	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
venture	null	O	VBG
bury	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
100,000	null	DURATION	CD
Sweden	null	LOCATION	NNP
take	null	O	VBZ
seconds	null	NUMBER	NNS
90	null	DURATION	CD
american	null	LOCATION	JJ
warplane	null	O	NNS
drop	null	O	VBD
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
35	null	DURATION	CD
Vietnam	null	LOCATION	NNP
on	null	O	IN
drop	null	O	VBD
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
35	null	DURATION	CD
Sweden	null	LOCATION	NNP
bury	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
100,000	null	DURATION	CD
Sweden	null	LOCATION	NNP
bury	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
Sweden	null	LOCATION	NNP
take	null	O	VBZ
seconds	null	NUMBER	NNS
90	null	DURATION	CD
Sweden	null	LOCATION	NNP
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
100,000	null	DURATION	CD
Sweden	null	LOCATION	NNP
take	null	O	VBZ
seconds	null	NUMBER	NNS
90	null	DURATION	CD
iranian	null	MISC	JJ
Tehran	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
arrest	null	O	VBN
dozen	null	O	NNS
arrest	null	O	VBN
over	null	O	IN
unrest	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
city	null	O	NN
erupt	null	O	VBD
go	null	O	VBZ
in	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
10	null	DURATION	CD
iranian	null	MISC	JJ
city	null	O	NN
erupt	null	O	VBD
go	null	O	VBZ
in	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
10	null	DURATION	CD
Iraq	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
live	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
30	null	DURATION	CD
iraqi	null	MISC	JJ
sympathy	null	O	NN
revulsion	null	O	NN
cause	null	O	VBD
crime	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
shoot	null	O	VBD
take	null	O	VBN
before	null	O	IN
live	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
30	null	DURATION	CD
Iraq	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
operation	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
head	null	O	NN
pull	null	O	VBN
International	null	O	NNP
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
12	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
authority	null	O	NNS
clear	null	O	VBD
Uighurs	null	MISC	NNPS
17	null	NUMBER	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
province	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
return	null	O	VBD
torture	null	O	VB
fear	null	O	NNS
to	null	O	TO
due	null	O	JJ
prison	null	O	NN
at	null	O	IN
stick	null	O	VBN
clear	null	O	VBD
Uighurs	null	MISC	NNPS
17	null	NUMBER	CD
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
with	null	O	IN
relation	null	O	NNS
restore	null	O	VBG
say	null	O	VBD
Funes	null	PERSON	NNP
leader	null	O	NN
elect	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
with	null	O	IN
relation	null	O	NNS
break	null	O	VBN
since	null	O	IN
revolution	null	O	NN
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
50	null	DATE	CD
cuban	null	MISC	JJ
revolution	null	O	NN
since	null	O	IN
break	null	O	VBN
relation	null	O	NNS
restore	null	O	VBG
say	null	O	VBD
Funes	null	PERSON	NNP
leader	null	O	NN
elect	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
cuban	null	MISC	JJ
revolution	null	O	NN
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
50	null	DATE	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
colonel	null	O	NN
Parrish	null	PERSON	NNP
hear	null	O	VB
in	null	O	IN
case	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
Khadr	null	PERSON	NNP
old	null	DURATION	JJ
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
15	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
sergeant	null	O	NN
kill	null	O	VBD
old	null	DURATION	JJ
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
15	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
ask	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
120	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
official	null	O	NNS
process	null	O	NN
able	null	O	JJ
reemerge	null	O	VB
within	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
90	null	DURATION	CD
Aussie	null	MISC	NNP
wait	null	O	VB
hope	null	O	VBG
make	null	O	VB
woman	null	O	NN
reach	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
30	null	DURATION	CD
australian	null	MISC	JJ
woman	null	O	NN
reach	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
30	null	DURATION	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
final	null	O	JJ
reach	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
30	null	DURATION	CD
australian	null	MISC	JJ
woman	null	O	NN
contest	null	O	VBD
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
36	null	DURATION	CD
aussie	null	MISC	JJ
winner	null	O	NN
since	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
36	null	DURATION	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
meeting	null	O	NN
at	null	O	IN
speak	null	O	VBG
face	null	O	VBD
end	null	O	VB
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
47	null	NUMBER	CD
american	null	MISC	JJ
country	null	O	NNS
leftist	null	O	JJ
by	null	O	IN
face	null	O	VBD
end	null	O	VB
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
47	null	NUMBER	CD
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
47	null	NUMBER	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
government	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
advocate	null	O	NN
Zen	null	PERSON	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
want	null	O	VBD
see	null	O	VB
re-examination	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
crackdown	null	O	NN
ago	null	DATE	IN
year	null	DATE	NNS
20	null	DATE	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
for	null	O	IN
call	null	O	VBN
Einhorn	null	PERSON	NNP
work	null	O	VBD
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
29	null	DURATION	CD
North	null	LOCATION	NNP
Korea	null	LOCATION	NNP
accept	null	O	VB
Einhorn	null	PERSON	NNP
work	null	O	VBD
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
29	null	DURATION	CD
Iran	null	LOCATION	NNP
Korea	null	LOCATION	NNP
accept	null	O	VB
Einhorn	null	PERSON	NNP
work	null	O	VBD
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
29	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
colonel	null	O	NN
Parrish	null	PERSON	NNP
hear	null	O	VB
in	null	O	IN
case	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
Khadr	null	PERSON	NNP
old	null	DURATION	JJ
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
15	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
sergeant	null	O	NN
kill	null	O	VBD
old	null	DURATION	JJ
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
15	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
ask	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
120	null	DURATION	CD
iranian	null	MISC	JJ
Tehran	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
arrest	null	O	VBN
dozen	null	O	NNS
arrest	null	O	VBN
over	null	O	IN
unrest	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
city	null	O	NN
erupt	null	O	VBD
go	null	O	VBZ
in	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
10	null	DURATION	CD
iranian	null	MISC	JJ
city	null	O	NN
erupt	null	O	VBD
go	null	O	VBZ
in	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
10	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
personnel	null	O	NNS
cancel	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
24	null	DURATION	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
heap	null	O	NNS
pressure	null	O	NN
let	null	O	VB
heap	null	O	VBD
urge	null	O	VBD
lift	null	O	VB
47	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
on	null	O	IN
pressure	null	O	NN
let	null	O	VB
heap	null	O	VBD
urge	null	O	VBD
lift	null	O	VB
47	null	NUMBER	CD
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
heap	null	O	VBD
urge	null	O	VBD
lift	null	O	VB
47	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Sula	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
back	null	O	RB
heap	null	O	VBD
urge	null	O	VBD
lift	null	O	VB
47	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Sula	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
back	null	O	RB
heap	null	O	VBD
urge	null	O	VBD
lift	null	O	VB
47	null	NUMBER	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
Tuesday	null	DATE	NNP
on	null	O	IN
pressure	null	O	NN
heap	null	O	VBD
urge	null	O	VBD
lift	null	O	VB
47	null	NUMBER	CD
American	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
Organization	null	O	NNP
lift	null	O	VB
47	null	NUMBER	CD
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
lift	null	O	VB
47	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
Police	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
for	null	O	IN
spokeswoman	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
arrest	null	O	VBN
appear	null	O	VB
within	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
48	null	DURATION	CD
japanese	null	MISC	JJ
Honda	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
take	null	O	VBD
push	null	O	VBD
from	null	O	IN
12.0	null	NUMBER	CD
Ireland	null	LOCATION	NNP
for	null	O	IN
half	null	O	NN
into	null	O	IN
minute	null	NUMBER	NNS
13	null	DURATION	CD
spanish	null	MISC	JJ
ministry	null	O	NN
report	null	O	VBD
fall	null	O	VBD
for	null	O	IN
time	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
12	null	DURATION	CD
UNITED	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
state	null	ORGANIZATION	NNS
October	null	DATE	NNP
crash	null	O	NNS
off	null	O	IN
coast	null	O	NN
after	null	O	IN
minute	null	NUMBER	NNS
30	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
coast	null	O	NN
after	null	O	IN
minute	null	NUMBER	NNS
30	null	DURATION	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
sponsor	null	O	VBN
Assembly	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
at	null	O	IN
identity	null	O	NN
orientation	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
statement	null	O	NN
sign	null	O	VBD
country	null	O	NNS
67	null	NUMBER	CD
Netherlands	null	LOCATION	NNP
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
sponsor	null	O	VBN
Assembly	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
at	null	O	IN
identity	null	O	NN
orientation	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
statement	null	O	NN
sign	null	O	VBD
country	null	O	NNS
67	null	NUMBER	CD
Afghanistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
expect	null	O	VBZ
project	null	O	VBN
harvest	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
Afghanistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
32	null	DURATION	CD
Afghanistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
expect	null	O	VBZ
project	null	O	VBN
collect	null	O	VB
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
32	null	DURATION	CD
Afghanistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
32	null	DURATION	CD
Afghanistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
harvest	null	O	NN
project	null	O	VBN
collect	null	O	VB
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
32	null	DURATION	CD
iranian	null	MISC	JJ
Tehran	null	LOCATION	NNP
dozen	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
arrest	null	O	VBN
dozen	null	O	NNS
arrest	null	O	VBN
over	null	O	IN
unrest	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
city	null	O	NN
erupt	null	O	VBD
say	null	O	VBD
go	null	O	VBZ
in	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
10	null	DURATION	CD
iranian	null	MISC	JJ
city	null	O	NN
erupt	null	O	VBD
say	null	O	VBD
go	null	O	VBZ
in	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
10	null	DURATION	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
exhibitor	null	O	NNS
36	null	NUMBER	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
exhibitor	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
participation	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
Taipei	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
time	null	O	NN
since	null	O	IN
launch	null	O	NN
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
29	null	DATE	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
Secretary	null	O	NNP
opening	null	O	NN
start	null	O	VBG
after	null	O	IN
9	null	NUMBER	CD
iranian	null	MISC	JJ
to	null	O	TO
distribute	null	O	VB
above	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
18	null	DURATION	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
government	null	O	NN
stop	null	O	VBZ
to	null	O	TO
silence	null	O	NN
happen	null	O	VBD
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
20	null	DATE	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
sale	null	O	NNS
grow	null	O	VBD
to	null	O	TO
unit	null	O	NNS
670,000	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
market	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
share	null	O	NN
higher	null	O	JJR
sell	null	O	VBD
month	null	DATE	NN
with	null	O	IN
vehicle	null	O	NNS
74,741	null	NUMBER	CD
iranian	null	MISC	JJ
diplomat	null	O	NNS
be	null	O	VBN
time	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
30	null	DURATION	CD
iranian	null	MISC	JJ
to	null	O	TO
distribute	null	O	VB
above	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
18	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
vehicle	null	O	NN
against	null	O	IN
throw	null	O	VBG
of	null	O	IN
accuse	null	O	VBN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
for	null	O	IN
hold	null	O	VBN
think	null	O	VBN
old	null	DURATION	JJ
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
21	null	NUMBER	CD
23	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Treasury	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
obtain	null	O	VBN
aim	null	O	VBZ
emerge	null	O	VB
within	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
90	null	DURATION	CD
Zimbabwe	null	LOCATION	NNP
hearing	null	O	NNS
begin	null	O	VB
in	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
10	null	DURATION	CD
Zimbabwe	null	LOCATION	NNP
hearing	null	O	NNS
begin	null	O	VB
Zimbabwe	null	LOCATION	NNP
start	null	O	VB
in	null	O	IN
time	null	O	NN
10	null	DURATION	CD
Zimbabwe	null	LOCATION	NNP
begin	null	O	VB
in	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
10	null	DURATION	CD
Zimbabwe	null	LOCATION	NNP
start	null	O	VB
in	null	O	IN
time	null	O	NN
10	null	DURATION	CD
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
after	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
47	null	DURATION	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
Sula	null	LOCATION	NNP
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
after	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
47	null	DURATION	CD
American	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
States	null	ORGANIZATION	NNPS
of	null	ORGANIZATION	IN
Organization	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
clear	null	O	VBD
agree	null	O	VBZ
readmit	null	O	VB
Sula	null	LOCATION	NNP
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
after	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
47	null	DURATION	CD
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
rejoin	null	O	VB
clear	null	O	VBD
agree	null	O	VBZ
readmit	null	O	VB
Sula	null	LOCATION	NNP
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
after	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
47	null	DURATION	CD
Kuwait	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
work	null	O	VBZ
husband	null	O	NN
agree	null	O	VBN
rule	null	O	VBN
marry	null	O	VB
later	null	DATE	RB
day	null	DATE	NNS
100	null	DATE	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
official	null	O	NNS
process	null	O	NN
able	null	O	JJ
reemerge	null	O	VB
within	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
90	null	DURATION	CD
Jamaica	null	LOCATION	NNP
triumph	null	O	NN
help	null	O	VBG
by	null	O	IN
take	null	O	VBD
stun	null	O	VBD
by	null	O	IN
set	null	O	VBG
record	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
seconds	null	NUMBER	NNS
9.69	null	DURATION	CD
Jamaica	null	LOCATION	NNP
triumph	null	O	NN
help	null	O	VBG
by	null	O	IN
take	null	O	VBD
stun	null	O	VBD
by	null	O	IN
set	null	O	VBG
record	null	O	NNS
seconds	null	NUMBER	NNS
19.30	null	DURATION	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
blame	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
attack	null	O	NNS
kill	null	O	VBD
people	null	O	NNS
160	null	NUMBER	CD
Iraq	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
live	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
30	null	DURATION	CD
german	null	MISC	JJ
city	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
huddle	null	O	NN
mean	null	O	VBZ
will	null	O	MD
after	null	O	IN
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
18	null	DURATION	CD
Germany	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
2	null	DATE	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
serve	null	O	VBG
speak	null	O	VB
at	null	O	IN
University	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
beacon	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
secularism	null	O	NN
freedom	null	O	NN
lose	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
100	null	DURATION	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
here	null	O	RB
draw	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
have	null	O	VBD
guy	null	O	NNS
19	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
Lewis	null	PERSON	NNP
day	null	DURATION	NNS
into	null	O	IN
sentence	null	O	NN
13	null	DURATION	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
into	null	O	IN
cocaine	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
sentence	null	O	NN
13	null	DURATION	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
begn	null	O	VBD
at	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
24	null	TIME	CD
Bangladesh	null	LOCATION	NNP
against	null	O	IN
proper	null	O	JJ
tournament	null	O	NN
begn	null	O	VBD
at	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
24	null	TIME	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
while	null	O	IN
begn	null	O	VBD
at	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
24	null	TIME	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
while	null	O	IN
begn	null	O	VBD
at	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
24	null	TIME	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
Arles	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
costume	null	O	NNS
by	null	O	IN
inspire	null	O	VBN
design	null	O	NNS
with	null	O	IN
hit	null	O	VBD
ago	null	DATE	IN
year	null	DATE	NNS
20	null	DATE	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
26	null	DURATION	CD
iranian	null	MISC	JJ
diplomat	null	O	NNS
be	null	O	VBN
time	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
30	null	DURATION	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
exhibitor	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
participation	null	O	NN
time	null	O	NN
since	null	O	IN
launch	null	O	NN
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
29	null	DATE	CD
danish	null	MISC	JJ
Politiken	null	O	NNP
tell	null	O	VBD
lose	null	O	VBN
want	null	O	VBP
start	null	O	VB
with	null	O	IN
slate	null	O	NN
after	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
30	null	DURATION	CD
BRAZIL	null	LOCATION	NNP
Graphic	null	O	NNP
by	null	O	IN
available	null	O	JJ
on	null	O	IN
principle	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
survive	null	O	VBZ
strike	null	O	NN
occurrence	null	O	NN
happen	null	O	VBZ
in	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
1,000	null	DURATION	CD
FRANCE	null	LOCATION	NNP
Graphic	null	O	NNP
by	null	O	IN
available	null	O	JJ
on	null	O	IN
principle	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
survive	null	O	VBZ
strike	null	O	NN
occurrence	null	O	NN
happen	null	O	VBZ
in	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
1,000	null	DURATION	CD
UK	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Party	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
head	null	O	NN
Farage	null	PERSON	NNP
admit	null	O	VBD
pocket	null	O	VBD
pound	null	MONEY	NNS
euro	null	MONEY	NNS
over	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
10	null	DURATION	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
on	null	O	IN
call	null	O	VBD
free	null	O	VB
dozen	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
prisoner	null	O	NNS
believe	null	O	VBN
be	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
take	null	O	VBG
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
20	null	DATE	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
president	null	O	NN
drop	null	O	VBN
by	null	O	IN
for	null	O	IN
minute	null	NUMBER	NNS
12	null	DURATION	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
against	null	O	IN
twenty20	null	O	NN
since	null	O	IN
use	null	O	VBN
duo	null	O	NNS
11	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
use	null	O	VBN
duo	null	O	NNS
11	null	NUMBER	CD
american	null	MISC	JJ
secretary	null	O	NN
by	null	O	IN
visit	null	O	NN
here	null	O	RB
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
10	null	DURATION	CD
Philippines	null	LOCATION	NNPS
with	null	O	IN
one	null	NUMBER	CD
into	null	O	IN
evolve	null	O	VB
need	null	O	VBZ
say	null	O	VBD
in	null	O	IN
visit	null	O	NN
here	null	O	RB
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
10	null	DURATION	CD
Iraq	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
live	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
30	null	DURATION	CD
iraqi	null	MISC	JJ
sympathy	null	O	NN
revulsion	null	O	NN
cause	null	O	VBD
crime	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
shoot	null	O	VBD
take	null	O	VBN
before	null	O	IN
live	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
30	null	DURATION	CD
Iraq	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
operation	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
head	null	O	NN
pull	null	O	VBN
International	null	O	NNP
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
12	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
Motors	null	ORGANIZATION	NNPS
emerge	null	O	VB
from	null	O	IN
bankruptcy	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
90	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
Motors	null	ORGANIZATION	NNPS
emerge	null	O	VB
in	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
90	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
official	null	O	NNS
say	null	O	VBD
expect	null	O	VBN
Motors	null	ORGANIZATION	NNPS
emerge	null	O	VB
from	null	O	IN
bankruptcy	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
90	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
official	null	O	NNS
say	null	O	VBD
expect	null	O	VBN
emerge	null	O	VB
in	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
90	null	DURATION	CD
UAE	null	LOCATION	NNP
DUBAI	null	LOCATION	NNP
against	null	O	IN
desert	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
end	null	O	VBZ
Gomez	null	PERSON	NNP
inspire	null	O	VBD
in	null	O	IN
friendly	null	O	JJ
with	null	O	IN
haul	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
14	null	DURATION	CD
Germany	null	LOCATION	NNP
inspire	null	O	VBD
in	null	O	IN
friendly	null	O	JJ
with	null	O	IN
haul	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
14	null	DURATION	CD
United	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Emirates	null	ORGANIZATION	NNPS
over	null	O	IN
victory	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
inspire	null	O	VBD
in	null	O	IN
friendly	null	O	JJ
with	null	O	IN
haul	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
14	null	DURATION	CD
Mauritania	null	LOCATION	NNP
president	null	O	NN
topple	null	O	VBD
coup	null	O	NN
follow	null	O	VBG
end	null	O	VB
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
10	null	DURATION	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
government	null	O	NN
lose	null	O	VBD
minister	null	DATE	NN
within	null	DATE	IN
hour	null	DATE	NNS
24	null	DATE	CD
british	null	LOCATION	JJ
Brown	null	PERSON	NNP
lose	null	O	VBD
minister	null	DATE	NN
within	null	DATE	IN
hour	null	DATE	NNS
24	null	DATE	CD
Macau	null	LOCATION	NNP
Macau	null	LOCATION	NNP
on	null	O	IN
fact	null	O	NNS
list	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
fact	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
Macau	null	LOCATION	NNP
open	null	O	VBD
hand	null	O	VBN
after	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
400	null	DURATION	CD
Macau	null	LOCATION	NNP
on	null	O	IN
fact	null	O	NNS
list	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
fact	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
Macau	null	LOCATION	NNP
open	null	O	VBD
hand	null	O	VBN
after	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
400	null	DURATION	CD
chinese	null	LOCATION	JJ
territory	null	O	NN
about	null	O	IN
fact	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
Macau	null	LOCATION	NNP
open	null	O	VBD
hand	null	O	VBN
after	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
400	null	DURATION	CD
Macau	null	LOCATION	NNP
open	null	O	VBD
hand	null	O	VBN
after	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
400	null	DURATION	CD
Macau	null	LOCATION	NNP
region	null	O	NN
open	null	O	VBD
hand	null	O	VBN
after	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
400	null	DURATION	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
region	null	O	NN
open	null	O	VBD
hand	null	O	VBN
after	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
400	null	DURATION	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
government	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
advocate	null	O	NN
Zen	null	PERSON	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
want	null	O	VBD
see	null	O	VB
re-examination	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
crackdown	null	O	NN
ago	null	DATE	IN
year	null	DATE	NNS
20	null	DATE	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
begn	null	O	VBD
host	null	O	NNS
at	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
24	null	TIME	CD
Bangladesh	null	LOCATION	NNP
against	null	O	IN
tournament	null	O	NN
begn	null	O	VBD
host	null	O	NNS
at	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
24	null	TIME	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
face	null	O	VBP
host	null	O	NNS
at	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
24	null	TIME	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
host	null	O	NNS
at	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
24	null	TIME	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
giant	null	O	NN
washington	null	LOCATION	NN
June	null	DATE	NNP
2	null	DATE	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
in	null	O	IN
save	null	O	VB
move	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
say	null	O	VBD
report	null	O	NN
giant	null	O	NN
washington	null	LOCATION	NN
June	null	DATE	NNP
2	null	DATE	CD
australian	null	ORGANIZATION	JJ
Force	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
join	null	O	VBD
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
91	null	DATE	CD
australian	null	MISC	JJ
military	null	O	NN
serve	null	O	VBD
join	null	O	VBD
railway	null	O	NNS
work	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
45	null	DURATION	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
apply	null	O	VBD
Czechs	null	MISC	NNPS
653	null	NUMBER	CD
canadian	null	MISC	JJ
embassy	null	O	NN
from	null	O	IN
datum	null	O	NNS
to	null	O	TO
accord	null	O	VBG
apply	null	O	VBD
Czechs	null	MISC	NNPS
653	null	NUMBER	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
brand	null	O	NN
empire	null	O	NN
celebrate	null	O	VBZ
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
100	null	DURATION	CD
dutch	null	MISC	JJ
party	null	O	NN
quit	null	O	VBD
after	null	O	IN
year	null	DATE	NNS
14	null	DATE	CD
Turkey	null	LOCATION	NNP
entry	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
support	null	O	NN
over	null	O	IN
quit	null	O	VBD
after	null	O	IN
year	null	DATE	NNS
14	null	DATE	CD
Yemen	null	O	NNP
feel	null	O	VBZ
after	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
unification	null	O	NN
15	null	DURATION	CD
Yemen	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
of	null	O	IN
hotbed	null	O	NN
decade	null	DURATION	NNS
after	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
unification	null	O	NN
15	null	DURATION	CD
Yemen	null	LOCATION	NNP
feel	null	O	VBZ
after	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
unification	null	O	NN
15	null	DURATION	CD
north	null	O	NN
from	null	O	IN
feel	null	O	VBZ
after	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
unification	null	O	NN
15	null	DURATION	CD
french	null	O	JJ
Paris	null	LOCATION	NNP
Belgium	null	LOCATION	NNP
Norman	null	PERSON	NNP
at	null	O	IN
bryan	null	ORGANIZATION	NNS
belie	null	O	VBD
year	null	DATE	NNS
38	null	DATE	CD
Belgium	null	LOCATION	NNP
Norman	null	PERSON	NNP
at	null	O	IN
bryan	null	ORGANIZATION	NNS
belie	null	O	VBD
year	null	DATE	NNS
38	null	DATE	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Africa	null	LOCATION	NNP
Moodie	null	PERSON	NNP
he	null	O	PRP
reach	null	O	VBD
belie	null	O	VBD
year	null	DATE	NNS
38	null	DATE	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
man	null	O	NNS
double	null	O	VBZ
reach	null	O	VBD
belie	null	O	VBD
year	null	DATE	NNS
38	null	DATE	CD
America	null	LOCATION	NNP
twin	null	O	NNS
over	null	O	IN
victory	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
double	null	O	VBZ
reach	null	O	VBD
belie	null	O	VBD
year	null	DATE	NNS
38	null	DATE	CD
Lanka	null	LOCATION	NNP
bus	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
attack	null	O	NN
by	null	O	IN
stun	null	O	VBN
move	null	O	VBN
of	null	O	IN
concern	null	O	NNS
spark	null	O	VBD
by	null	O	IN
attack	null	O	NNS
with	null	O	IN
Oval	null	O	NNP
sell	null	O	VBD
for	null	O	IN
match	null	O	NN
within	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
48	null	DURATION	CD
indian	null	ORGANIZATION	JJ
League	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
move	null	O	VBN
of	null	O	IN
concern	null	O	NNS
spark	null	O	VBD
by	null	O	IN
attack	null	O	NNS
with	null	O	IN
Oval	null	O	NNP
sell	null	O	VBD
for	null	O	IN
match	null	O	NN
within	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
48	null	DURATION	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Africa	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
move	null	O	VBN
of	null	O	IN
concern	null	O	NNS
spark	null	O	VBD
by	null	O	IN
attack	null	O	NNS
with	null	O	IN
Oval	null	O	NNP
sell	null	O	VBD
for	null	O	IN
match	null	O	NN
within	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
48	null	DURATION	CD
India	null	LOCATION	NNP
beat	null	O	VBD
champion	null	O	NNS
defend	null	O	VBG
game	null	O	NNS
go	null	O	VBD
pick	null	O	NN
ensure	null	O	VB
keen	null	O	JJ
sell	null	O	VBD
for	null	O	IN
match	null	O	NN
within	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
48	null	DURATION	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
beat	null	O	VBD
champion	null	O	NNS
defend	null	O	VBG
game	null	O	NNS
go	null	O	VBD
pick	null	O	NN
ensure	null	O	VB
keen	null	O	JJ
sell	null	O	VBD
for	null	O	IN
match	null	O	NN
within	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
48	null	DURATION	CD
german	null	MISC	JJ
politician	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBZ
join	null	O	VB
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
15	null	DURATION	CD
german	null	MISC	JJ
politician	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBZ
join	null	O	VB
June	null	DATE	NNP
politician	null	O	NN
call	null	O	VBN
member	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
part	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
club	null	O	NN
within	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
15	null	DURATION	CD
Israel	null	LOCATION	NNP
join	null	O	VB
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
15	null	DURATION	CD
Israel	null	LOCATION	NNP
join	null	O	VB
June	null	DATE	NNP
politician	null	O	NN
call	null	O	VBN
member	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
part	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
club	null	O	NN
within	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
15	null	DURATION	CD
german	null	MISC	JJ
politician	null	O	NN
June	null	DATE	NNP
join	null	O	VB
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
15	null	DURATION	CD
german	null	MISC	JJ
politician	null	O	NN
call	null	O	VBN
member	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
part	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
club	null	O	NN
within	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
15	null	DURATION	CD
Israel	null	LOCATION	NNP
for	null	O	IN
call	null	O	VBN
politician	null	O	NN
June	null	DATE	NNP
join	null	O	VB
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
15	null	DURATION	CD
Israel	null	LOCATION	NNP
for	null	O	IN
call	null	O	VBN
member	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
part	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
club	null	O	NN
within	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
15	null	DURATION	CD
Chinese	null	MISC	NNPS
unaware	null	O	JJ
enforce	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
chinese	null	LOCATION	JJ
in	null	O	IN
write	null	O	VBN
banner	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
June	null	DATE	NNP
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Treasury	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
obtain	null	O	VBN
aim	null	O	VBZ
emerge	null	O	VB
within	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
90	null	DURATION	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
border	null	O	NN
across	null	O	IN
sanctuary	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
some	null	O	DT
regroup	null	O	VB
launch	null	O	VB
insurgency	null	O	NN
year	null	DATE	NN
with	null	O	IN
civilian	null	O	NNS
2,200	null	NUMBER	CD
Libya	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
vanish	null	O	VBD
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
30	null	DATE	CD
Myanmar	null	LOCATION	NNP
regime	null	O	NN
uproot	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
year	null	DATE	NNS
12	null	DATE	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
of	null	O	IN
thousand	null	O	NNS
watch	null	O	NN
that	null	O	IN
Washington	null	LOCATION	NNP
near	null	O	IN
church	null	O	NN
run	null	O	VBZ
old	null	DURATION	JJ
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
50	null	DURATION	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
pull	null	O	VBN
from	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
Brazil	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
triple	null	O	VBD
card	null	O	NNS
triple	null	O	RB
over	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
PAULO	null	PERSON	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
4	null	DATE	CD
Brazil	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
PAULO	null	PERSON	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
4	null	DATE	CD
Brazil	null	LOCATION	NNP
federation	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
triple	null	O	VBD
card	null	O	NNS
triple	null	O	RB
over	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
PAULO	null	PERSON	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
4	null	DATE	CD
Italy	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
after	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
15	null	DURATION	CD
Italy	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
after	null	O	IN
afp	null	O	NN
police	null	O	NN
near	null	O	IN
turn	null	O	VBZ
recover	null	O	VBN
canvas	null	O	NN
steal	null	O	VBN
year	null	DATE	NNS
15	null	DATE	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
Renoir	null	PERSON	NNP
by	null	O	IN
canvas	null	O	NN
recover	null	O	VBN
turn	null	O	VBZ
near	null	O	IN
police	null	O	NN
afp	null	O	NN
after	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
15	null	DURATION	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
Renoir	null	PERSON	NNP
by	null	O	IN
canvas	null	O	NN
steal	null	O	VBN
year	null	DATE	NNS
15	null	DATE	CD
Italy	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
police	null	O	NN
recover	null	O	VBD
earlier	null	DATE	RBR
year	null	DATE	NNS
33	null	DATE	CD
Afghan	null	MISC	NNP
troops	null	O	NNS
with	null	O	IN
clash	null	O	VBD
fighter	null	O	NNS
confirm	null	O	VBD
say	null	O	VBD
make	null	O	VBN
start	null	O	VBD
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
10	null	DURATION	CD
german	null	MISC	JJ
unification	null	O	NN
to	null	O	TO
way	null	O	NN
pave	null	O	VBG
undergo	null	O	VBN
restoration	null	O	NN
fall	null	O	VBD
in	null	O	IN
revolution	null	O	NN
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
20	null	DATE	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
government	null	O	NN
give	null	O	VBN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
jordanian	null	MISC	JJ
cleric	null	O	NN
release	null	O	VB
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
pm	null	O	NN
government	null	O	NN
from	null	O	IN
minister	null	O	NN
quit	null	O	VBZ
report	null	O	VBD
make	null	O	VBG
fourth	null	ORDINAL	JJ
go	null	O	VB
in	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
24	null	DURATION	CD
british	null	LOCATION	JJ
Brown	null	PERSON	NNP
cabinet	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
member	null	O	NN
June	null	DATE	NNP
LONDON	null	LOCATION	NNP
report	null	O	NNS
resign	null	O	VBD
report	null	O	VBD
make	null	O	VBG
fourth	null	ORDINAL	JJ
go	null	O	VB
in	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
24	null	DURATION	CD
British	null	MISC	NNP
Brown	null	PERSON	NNP
lose	null	O	VBD
within	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
24	null	DURATION	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
happen	null	O	VBG
happen	null	O	VBD
year	null	DATE	NNS
20	null	DATE	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
jail	null	O	VBN
people	null	O	NNS
to	null	O	TO
work	null	O	VBG
Foundation	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
director	null	O	NN
Kamm	null	PERSON	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
happen	null	O	VBD
year	null	DATE	NNS
20	null	DATE	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
student	null	O	NNS
everyone	null	O	NN
supportive	null	O	JJ
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
20	null	DATE	CD
mexican	null	MISC	JJ
Laguna	null	PERSON	NNP
with	null	O	IN
agree	null	O	VBN
finalize	null	O	VBN
with	null	O	IN
23	null	NUMBER	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
travel	null	O	VB
year-old	null	O	JJ
23	null	NUMBER	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
America	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
12	null	DURATION	CD
America	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
12	null	DURATION	CD
Spain	null	LOCATION	NNP
America	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
12	null	DURATION	CD
Chinese	null	MISC	NNPS
unaware	null	O	JJ
enforce	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
Sweden	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
flee	null	O	VBD
jail	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
18	null	DURATION	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
go	null	O	VBG
before	null	O	IN
jail	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
18	null	DURATION	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
match	null	O	NN
before	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
48	null	DURATION	CD
Mauritanian	null	MISC	NNP
PM	null	O	NNP
free	null	O	VBN
after	null	O	IN
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
6	null	DURATION	CD
Mauritania	null	LOCATION	NNP
minister	null	O	NN
free	null	O	VBN
free	null	O	VBN
after	null	O	IN
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
6	null	DURATION	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
pm	null	O	NN
Wednesday	null	DATE	NNP
on	null	O	IN
eve	null	O	NN
indicate	null	O	VBD
election	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
24	null	DURATION	CD
british	null	LOCATION	JJ
Brown	null	PERSON	NNP
government	null	O	NN
Wednesday	null	DATE	NNP
on	null	O	IN
eve	null	O	NN
indicate	null	O	VBD
election	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
24	null	DURATION	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
work	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
18	null	DURATION	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
player	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
attitude	null	O	NN
by	null	O	IN
impress	null	O	VBN
work	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
18	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Treasury	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
obtain	null	O	VBN
aim	null	O	VBZ
emerge	null	O	VB
within	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
90	null	DURATION	CD
Israel	null	LOCATION	NNP
Washington	null	LOCATION	NNP
between	null	O	IN
tension	null	O	NNS
rise	null	O	VBN
to	null	O	TO
level	null	O	NNS
unseen	null	O	JJ
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
Israel	null	LOCATION	NNP
halt	null	O	NN
demand	null	O	VBN
rise	null	O	VBN
to	null	O	TO
level	null	O	NNS
unseen	null	O	JJ
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
british	null	LOCATION	JJ
government	null	O	NN
give	null	O	VBN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
british	null	LOCATION	JJ
prison	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
hold	null	O	VBN
cleric	null	O	NN
release	null	O	VB
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
Israel	null	LOCATION	NNP
halt	null	O	NN
demand	null	O	VBN
rise	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Ponting	null	PERSON	NNP
confirm	null	O	VBD
Thursday	null	DATE	NNP
on	null	O	IN
exit	null	O	NN
come	null	O	VBD
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
48	null	DURATION	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
minister	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
10	null	DURATION	CD
British	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Office	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
say	null	O	VBN
give	null	O	VB
notice	null	O	NN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
48	null	DURATION	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
government	null	O	NN
give	null	O	VBN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
jordanian	null	MISC	JJ
cleric	null	O	NN
release	null	O	VB
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
Myanmar	null	LOCATION	NNP
junta	null	O	NN
keep	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
13	null	NUMBER	CD
of	null	O	IN
year	null	DATE	NNS
19	null	DATE	CD
italian	null	MISC	JJ
newspaper	null	O	NN
tell	null	O	VBD
early	null	O	RB
as	null	O	RB
beatify	null	O	VBN
ROME	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
4	null	DATE	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
pm	null	O	NN
Wednesday	null	DATE	NNP
on	null	O	IN
eve	null	O	NN
indicate	null	O	VBD
election	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
24	null	DURATION	CD
british	null	LOCATION	JJ
Brown	null	PERSON	NNP
government	null	O	NN
Wednesday	null	DATE	NNP
on	null	O	IN
eve	null	O	NN
indicate	null	O	VBD
election	null	O	NNS
in	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
24	null	DURATION	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
people	null	O	NNS
with	null	O	IN
reconnect	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VB
return	null	O	VB
quit	null	O	VBG
say	null	O	VB
come	null	O	VBD
speak	null	O	VBD
minute	null	NUMBER	NNS
90	null	DURATION	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
government	null	O	NN
stop	null	O	VBZ
to	null	O	TO
silence	null	O	NN
happen	null	O	VBD
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
20	null	DATE	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
work	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
18	null	DURATION	CD
Scotland	null	LOCATION	NNP
player	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
attitude	null	O	NN
by	null	O	IN
impress	null	O	VBN
work	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
18	null	DURATION	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
pm	null	O	NN
government	null	O	NN
from	null	O	IN
minister	null	O	NN
quit	null	O	VBZ
say	null	O	VBD
resign	null	O	VBG
make	null	O	VBG
fourth	null	ORDINAL	JJ
go	null	O	VB
in	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
24	null	DURATION	CD
british	null	LOCATION	JJ
Brown	null	PERSON	NNP
cabinet	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
member	null	O	NN
LONDON	null	LOCATION	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
resign	null	O	VBG
make	null	O	VBG
fourth	null	ORDINAL	JJ
go	null	O	VB
in	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
24	null	DURATION	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
brand	null	O	NN
France-cosmetics-luxury-company-Oreal	null	O	NNP
celebrate	null	O	VBZ
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
100	null	DURATION	CD
argentine	null	MISC	JJ
police	null	O	NNS
receive	null	O	VBD
allow	null	O	VBN
take	null	O	VB
with	null	O	IN
delay	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
minute	null	NUMBER	NNS
32	null	DURATION	CD
chinese	null	LOCATION	JJ
activist	null	O	NNS
say	null	O	VBP
decision	null	O	NN
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
20	null	DATE	CD
georgian	null	MISC	JJ
Liberali	null	PERSON	NNP
write	null	O	VBD
show	null	O	VBN
sample	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
launcher	null	O	NNS
use	null	O	VBN
by	null	O	IN
police	null	O	NN
launcher	null	O	NN
303	null	NUMBER	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
membership	null	O	NN
thing	null	O	NN
think	null	O	VBP
people	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
proportion	null	O	NN
show	null	O	VBZ
over	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
25	null	DURATION	CD
dutch	null	MISC	JJ
campaign	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
center	null	O	NN
at	null	O	IN
be	null	O	VBN
sure	null	O	JJ
make	null	O	VBN
45-year-old	null	O	JJ
dye	null	O	VBD
hair	null	O	NN
protection	null	O	NN
hour	null	NUMBER	NN
24	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
force-101	null	O	NN
conduct	null	O	VBN
over	null	O	IN
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
15	null	DURATION	CD
Afghan	null	MISC	NNP
force	null	O	NNS
with	null	O	IN
conduct	null	O	VBN
over	null	O	IN
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
15	null	DURATION	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
enter	null	O	VB
unable	null	O	JJ
unable	null	O	JJ
see	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
Jamaica	null	LOCATION	NNP
record-holder	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
clash	null	O	VB
look	null	O	VBG
Athletics	null	O	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
make	null	O	VBZ
200m	null	O	NN
19.58	null	DURATION	CD
Madagascar	null	LOCATION	NNP
sentence	null	O	NNS
oust	null	O	VBN
to	null	O	TO
antananarivo	null	O	NN
June	null	DATE	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
madagascar	null	LOCATION	NN
court	null	O	NN
sentence	null	O	VBN
oust	null	O	VBN
to	null	O	TO
antananarivo	null	O	NN
June	null	DATE	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
scientist	null	O	NNS
report	null	O	VBN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
million	null	DURATION	CD
14	null	DURATION	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
scientist	null	O	NNS
report	null	O	VBN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
million	null	DURATION	CD
14	null	DURATION	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
flee	null	O	VBG
before	null	O	IN
jail	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
18	null	DURATION	CD
Sweden	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
flee	null	O	VBG
before	null	O	IN
jail	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
18	null	DURATION	CD
UK	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Allen	null	PERSON	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
demonstrate	null	O	VBG
for	null	O	IN
later	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
20	null	DATE	CD
Myanmar	null	LOCATION	NNP
junta	null	O	NN
keep	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
detention	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
13	null	NUMBER	CD
of	null	O	IN
year	null	DATE	NNS
19	null	DATE	CD
Kenya	null	LOCATION	NNP
simplify	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
m	null	O	NN
10,000	null	NUMBER	CD
Taiwan	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
Ying-jeou	null	PERSON	NNP
leader	null	O	NNS
believe	null	O	VBP
one	null	NUMBER	CD
as	null	O	IN
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
20	null	DATE	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
leadership	null	O	NN
one	null	NUMBER	CD
as	null	O	IN
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
20	null	DATE	CD
Venezuela	null	LOCATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
face	null	O	VBN
end	null	O	VB
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
47	null	NUMBER	CD
Bolivia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Venezuela	null	LOCATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
face	null	O	VBN
end	null	O	VB
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
47	null	NUMBER	CD
Nicaragua	null	LOCATION	NNP
Venezuela	null	LOCATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
face	null	O	VBN
end	null	O	VB
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
47	null	NUMBER	CD
american	null	MISC	JJ
country	null	O	NNS
Venezuela	null	LOCATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
face	null	O	VBN
end	null	O	VB
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
47	null	NUMBER	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
like	null	O	IN
country	null	O	NNS
Venezuela	null	LOCATION	NNP
by	null	O	IN
face	null	O	VBN
end	null	O	VB
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
47	null	NUMBER	CD
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
47	null	NUMBER	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
ship	null	O	NN
be	null	O	VBD
carry	null	O	VBG
mini-submarine	null	O	NNS
capable	null	O	JJ
of	null	O	IN
operate	null	O	VBG
at	null	O	IN
depths	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
meter	null	O	NNS
aircraft	null	O	NN
survive	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
30	null	DURATION	CD
Myanmar	null	LOCATION	NNP
junta	null	O	NN
keep	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
13	null	NUMBER	CD
of	null	O	IN
year	null	DATE	NNS
19	null	DATE	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
hangover	null	O	NN
shrug	null	O	VBD
admit	null	O	VBD
come	null	O	VBN
since	null	O	IN
day	null	DURATION	NNS
sideline	null	O	VBD
for	null	O	IN
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
10	null	DURATION	CD
Israel	null	LOCATION	NNP
raise	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
Myanmar	null	LOCATION	NNP
junta	null	O	NN
keep	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
detention	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
13	null	NUMBER	CD
of	null	O	IN
year	null	DATE	NNS
19	null	DATE	CD
chinese	null	LOCATION	JJ
in	null	O	IN
write	null	O	VBN
banner	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
June	null	DATE	NNP
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
pm	null	O	NN
government	null	O	NN
from	null	O	IN
minister	null	O	NN
quit	null	O	VBZ
say	null	O	VBD
resign	null	O	VBG
make	null	O	VBG
fourth	null	ORDINAL	JJ
go	null	O	VB
in	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
24	null	DURATION	CD
british	null	LOCATION	JJ
Brown	null	PERSON	NNP
cabinet	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
member	null	O	NN
June	null	DATE	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
resign	null	O	VBG
make	null	O	VBG
fourth	null	ORDINAL	JJ
go	null	O	VB
in	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
24	null	DURATION	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
ship	null	O	NN
be	null	O	VBD
carry	null	O	VBG
mini-submarine	null	O	NNS
capable	null	O	JJ
of	null	O	IN
operate	null	O	VBG
at	null	O	IN
depths	null	O	NNS
aircraft	null	O	NN
survive	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
30	null	DURATION	CD
France	null	LOCATION	NNP
for	null	O	IN
head	null	O	VBD
with	null	O	IN
dollar	null	MONEY	NNS
50	null	MONEY	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
scientist	null	O	NNS
report	null	O	VBN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
million	null	DURATION	CD
14	null	DURATION	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
scientist	null	O	NNS
report	null	O	VBN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
million	null	DURATION	CD
14	null	DURATION	CD
Chinese	null	MISC	NNPS
unaware	null	O	JJ
enforce	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
Canada	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
family	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
reunite	null	O	VBN
fly	null	O	VB
within	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
30	null	DURATION	CD
Madagascar	null	LOCATION	NNP
sentence	null	O	NNS
oust	null	O	VBN
sentence	null	O	VBN
June	null	DATE	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
madagascar	null	LOCATION	NN
court	null	O	NN
sentence	null	O	VBN
June	null	DATE	NNP
3	null	DATE	CD
French	null	O	NNP
Paris	null	LOCATION	NNP
at	null	O	IN
Bryans	null	ORGANIZATION	NNPS
Norman	null	PERSON	NNP
Belgium	null	LOCATION	NNP
Norman	null	PERSON	NNP
belie	null	O	VBD
year	null	DATE	NNS
38	null	DATE	CD
Belgium	null	LOCATION	NNP
Norman	null	PERSON	NNP
belie	null	O	VBD
year	null	DATE	NNS
38	null	DATE	CD
South	null	LOCATION	NNP
Africa	null	LOCATION	NNP
Moodie	null	PERSON	NNP
he	null	O	PRP
save	null	O	VBD
belie	null	O	VBD
year	null	DATE	NNS
38	null	DATE	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
man	null	O	NNS
double	null	O	VBZ
reach	null	O	VB
save	null	O	VBD
belie	null	O	VBD
year	null	DATE	NNS
38	null	DATE	CD
America	null	LOCATION	NNP
twin	null	O	NNS
over	null	O	IN
victory	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
double	null	O	VBZ
reach	null	O	VB
save	null	O	VBD
belie	null	O	VBD
year	null	DATE	NNS
38	null	DATE	CD
Israel	null	LOCATION	NNP
Washington	null	LOCATION	NNP
between	null	O	IN
tension	null	O	NNS
rise	null	O	VBN
to	null	O	TO
level	null	O	NNS
unseen	null	O	JJ
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
Israel	null	LOCATION	NNP
halt	null	O	NN
demand	null	O	VBN
rise	null	O	VBN
to	null	O	TO
level	null	O	NNS
unseen	null	O	JJ
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
chinese	null	LOCATION	JJ
in	null	O	IN
write	null	O	VBN
banner	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
June	null	DATE	NNP
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
Israel	null	LOCATION	NNP
Washington	null	LOCATION	NNP
between	null	O	IN
tension	null	O	NNS
rise	null	O	VBN
to	null	O	TO
level	null	O	NNS
unseen	null	O	JJ
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
Israel	null	LOCATION	NNP
halt	null	O	NN
demand	null	O	VBN
rise	null	O	VBN
to	null	O	TO
level	null	O	NNS
unseen	null	O	JJ
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
government	null	O	NN
lose	null	O	VBD
minister	null	DATE	NN
within	null	DATE	IN
hour	null	DATE	NNS
24	null	DATE	CD
british	null	LOCATION	JJ
Brown	null	PERSON	NNP
lose	null	O	VBD
minister	null	DATE	NN
within	null	DATE	IN
hour	null	DATE	NNS
24	null	DATE	CD
Afghan	null	MISC	NNP
troops	null	O	NNS
with	null	O	IN
clash	null	O	VBD
fighter	null	O	NNS
confirm	null	O	VBD
say	null	O	VBD
make	null	O	VBN
start	null	O	VBD
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
10	null	DURATION	CD
Jamaica	null	LOCATION	NNP
record-holder	null	O	NN
with	null	O	IN
clash	null	O	VB
look	null	O	VBG
Athletics	null	O	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
make	null	O	VBZ
200m	null	O	NN
19.58	null	DURATION	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
enter	null	O	VB
unable	null	O	JJ
unable	null	O	JJ
see	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
Australia	null	LOCATION	NNP
Ponting	null	PERSON	NNP
add	null	O	VBD
bit	null	O	NN
disappointed	null	O	JJ
with	null	O	IN
event	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
24	null	DURATION	CD
russian	null	MISC	JJ
steady	null	O	VBD
take	null	O	VBD
lead	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
minute	null	NUMBER	NNS
49	null	DURATION	CD
Greece	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
meet	null	O	VBP
in	null	O	IN
season	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
seconds	null	NUMBER	NNS
10.06	null	DURATION	CD
belarusian	null	MISC	JJ
Azarenka	null	PERSON	NNP
take	null	O	VBG
record	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
surface	null	O	NN
match	null	O	NNS
year	null	DATE	NN
to	null	O	TO
win	null	O	NNS
19	null	NUMBER	CD
japanese	null	MISC	JJ
Honda	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
take	null	O	VBD
push	null	O	VBD
from	null	O	IN
12.0	null	NUMBER	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
government	null	O	NN
stop	null	O	VBZ
to	null	O	TO
silence	null	O	NN
happen	null	O	VBD
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
20	null	DATE	CD
Iran	null	LOCATION	NNP
mark	null	O	VBZ
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
brand	null	O	NN
empire	null	O	NN
celebrate	null	O	VBZ
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
100	null	DURATION	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
Renoir	null	PERSON	NNP
by	null	O	IN
canvas	null	O	NN
recover	null	O	VBN
after	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
15	null	DURATION	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
Renoir	null	PERSON	NNP
by	null	O	IN
canvas	null	O	NN
steal	null	O	VBN
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
15	null	DATE	CD
Italy	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
police	null	O	NN
recover	null	O	VBD
earlier	null	DATE	RBR
year	null	DATE	NNS
33	null	DATE	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
enter	null	O	VBG
from	null	O	IN
bar	null	O	VBN
face	null	O	VBZ
with	null	O	IN
hair	null	O	NN
protection	null	O	NN
hour	null	NUMBER	NN
24	null	DURATION	CD
Israel	null	LOCATION	NNP
halt	null	O	NN
demand	null	O	VBN
rise	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
military	null	O	JJ
crushed	null	O	JJ
on	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
crush	null	O	VB
revolt	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
20	null	DATE	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
in	null	O	IN
exile	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
crush	null	O	VB
revolt	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
20	null	DATE	CD
french	null	MISC	JJ
ship	null	O	NN
be	null	O	VBD
carry	null	O	VBG
mini-submarine	null	O	NNS
capable	null	O	JJ
of	null	O	IN
operate	null	O	VBG
at	null	O	IN
depths	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
meter	null	O	NNS
aircraft	null	O	NN
survive	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
30	null	DURATION	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
on	null	O	IN
call	null	O	VBD
free	null	O	VB
dozen	null	O	NNS
of	null	O	IN
prisoner	null	O	NNS
believe	null	O	VBN
be	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
take	null	O	VBG
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
20	null	DATE	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
president	null	O	NN
drop	null	O	VBN
by	null	O	IN
for	null	O	IN
minute	null	NUMBER	NNS
12	null	DURATION	CD
romanian	null	MISC	JJ
community	null	O	NN
post	null	O	VBD
rise	null	O	VBG
by	null	O	IN
people	null	O	NNS
64,770	null	NUMBER	CD
Yemen	null	LOCATION	NNP
decade	null	DURATION	NNS
ADEN	null	LOCATION	NNP
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
15	null	DURATION	CD
Yemen	null	LOCATION	NNP
feel	null	O	VBZ
FOCUS	null	O	NNP
ADEN	null	LOCATION	NNP
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
15	null	DURATION	CD
north	null	O	NN
from	null	O	IN
estrange	null	O	VBN
feel	null	O	VBZ
FOCUS	null	O	NNP
ADEN	null	LOCATION	NNP
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
15	null	DURATION	CD
scottish	null	ORGANIZATION	JJ
League	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
win	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VBG
join	null	O	VBD
for	null	O	IN
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
18	null	DURATION	CD
Scottish	null	MISC	NNP
Cup	null	MISC	NNP
League	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
win	null	O	VB
help	null	O	VBG
join	null	O	VBD
for	null	O	IN
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
18	null	DURATION	CD
british	null	MISC	JJ
government	null	O	NN
lose	null	O	VBD
within	null	O	IN
hour	null	DATE	NNS
24	null	DATE	CD
british	null	LOCATION	JJ
Brown	null	PERSON	NNP
lose	null	O	VBD
within	null	O	IN
hour	null	DATE	NNS
24	null	DATE	CD
Myanmar	null	LOCATION	NNP
junta	null	O	NN
keep	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
detention	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
13	null	NUMBER	CD
of	null	O	IN
year	null	DATE	NNS
19	null	DATE	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
appeal	null	O	NN
reunite	null	O	VB
crush	null	O	VBD
ago	null	DATE	IN
year	null	DATE	NNS
20	null	DATE	CD
Sweden	null	LOCATION	NNP
bury	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
100,000	null	DURATION	CD
Sweden	null	LOCATION	NNP
bury	null	O	VB
build	null	O	VBN
one	null	NUMBER	CD
house	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
100,000	null	DURATION	CD
Sweden	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
build	null	O	VBN
bury	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
100,000	null	DURATION	CD
Sweden	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
build	null	O	VBN
one	null	NUMBER	CD
house	null	O	VB
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
100,000	null	DURATION	CD
Czech	null	LOCATION	NNP
Republic	null	LOCATION	NNP
report	null	O	VBD
ago	null	DATE	RB
day	null	DATE	NNS
10	null	DATE	CD
United	null	LOCATION	NNP
States	null	LOCATION	NNPS
from	null	O	IN
come	null	O	VBN
pilot	null	O	NN
test	null	O	VBD
report	null	O	VBD
ago	null	DATE	RB
day	null	DATE	NNS
10	null	DATE	CD
angolan	null	MISC	JJ
hold	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
8	null	DURATION	CD
angolan	null	MISC	JJ
woman	null	O	NN
LUANDA	null	LOCATION	NNP
rescue	null	O	VBN
report	null	O	NN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
8	null	DURATION	CD
angolan	null	MISC	JJ
media	null	O	NNS
report	null	O	VBD
angolan	null	MISC	JJ
hold	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
8	null	DURATION	CD
Chinese	null	MISC	NNPS
unaware	null	O	JJ
enforce	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
Ramsay	null	PERSON	NNP
delighted	null	O	JJ
leave	null	O	VBD
69	null	NUMBER	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
captain	null	O	NN
Pavin	null	PERSON	NNP
have	null	O	VBD
72	null	NUMBER	CD
Britain	null	LOCATION	NNP
minister	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
10	null	DURATION	CD
indian	null	MISC	JJ
rule	null	O	NN
against	null	O	IN
insurgency	null	O	NN
leave	null	O	VBN
dead	null	O	JJ
over	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
russian	null	MISC	JJ
recovery	null	O	NN
start	null	O	VB
economy	null	O	NN
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
MOSCOW	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
4	null	DATE	CD
Russia	null	LOCATION	NNP
MOSCOW	null	LOCATION	NNP
June	null	DATE	NNP
4	null	DATE	CD
Iraq	null	LOCATION	NNP
resume	null	O	VB
sever	null	O	VBN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
12	null	DURATION	CD
Afghanistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
Iraq	null	LOCATION	NNP
resume	null	O	VB
sever	null	O	VBN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
12	null	DURATION	CD
Iraq	null	LOCATION	NNP
plan	null	O	VBG
resume	null	O	VB
sever	null	O	VBN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
12	null	DURATION	CD
Afghanistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
Iraq	null	LOCATION	NNP
plan	null	O	VBG
resume	null	O	VB
sever	null	O	VBN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
12	null	DURATION	CD
Afghan	null	MISC	NNP
diplomat	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VBD
sever	null	O	VBN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
12	null	DURATION	CD
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
for	null	O	IN
hold	null	O	VBD
say	null	O	VBD
arrest	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
spy	null	O	VBG
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
30	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
WASHINGTON	null	LOCATION	NNP
arrest	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
spy	null	O	VBG
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
30	null	DURATION	CD
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
for	null	O	IN
spy	null	O	VBG
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
30	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
official	null	O	NNS
say	null	O	VBD
arrest	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
spy	null	O	VBG
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
30	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Treasury	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
obtain	null	O	VBN
aim	null	O	VBZ
emerge	null	O	VB
within	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
90	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
Treasury	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
from	null	O	IN
obtain	null	O	VBN
aim	null	O	VBZ
emerge	null	O	VB
within	null	O	IN
day	null	NUMBER	NNS
90	null	DURATION	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
leadership	null	O	NN
one	null	NUMBER	CD
as	null	O	IN
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
20	null	DATE	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
emergence	null	O	NN
about	null	O	IN
talk	null	O	NN
of	null	O	IN
lot	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
emergence	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VB
lot	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
chinese	null	ORGANIZATION	JJ
Party	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
of	null	O	IN
emergence	null	O	NN
say	null	O	VB
lot	null	O	NN
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
China	null	LOCATION	NNP
progress	null	O	VBG
hear	null	O	VBD
for	null	O	IN
year	null	DATE	NNS
20	null	DATE	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
for	null	O	IN
taboo	null	O	JJ
later	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
20	null	DATE	CD
north	null	O	JJ
central	null	O	JJ
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
Derbyshire	null	LOCATION	NNP
rule	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
28	null	DURATION	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
Derbyshire	null	LOCATION	NNP
rule	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
28	null	DURATION	CD
British	null	MISC	NNP
Commissioner	null	O	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
hold	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
9	null	DURATION	CD
Nigeria	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
Commissioner	null	O	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
hold	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
9	null	DURATION	CD
England	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
Derbyshire	null	LOCATION	NNP
control	null	O	VBD
for	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
28	null	DURATION	CD
Syria	null	LOCATION	NNP
pull	null	O	VBZ
after	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
29	null	DURATION	CD
Lebanon	null	LOCATION	NNP
of	null	O	IN
out	null	O	IN
pull	null	O	VBZ
after	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
29	null	DURATION	CD
british	null	LOCATION	JJ
Brown	null	PERSON	NNP
face	null	O	VBD
as	null	O	IN
three	null	NUMBER	CD
quit	null	O	VBN
in	null	O	IN
hour	null	NUMBER	NNS
24	null	DURATION	CD
swedish	null	MISC	JJ
firm	null	O	NN
Sweco	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
talk	null	O	VBD
present	null	O	VBD
ago	null	DATE	RB
year	null	DATE	NNS
10	null	DATE	CD
Iran	null	LOCATION	NNP
Ahmadinejad	null	PERSON	NNP
seek	null	O	VBG
term	null	O	NN
in	null	O	IN
election	null	O	NN
12	null	DATE	CD
Guadeloupe	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
meeting	null	O	NN
at	null	O	IN
sec	null	DURATION	NN
44.50	null	DURATION	CD
indian	null	MISC	JJ
rule	null	O	NN
against	null	O	IN
insurgency	null	O	NN
leave	null	O	VBN
dead	null	O	JJ
over	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
Pakistan	null	LOCATION	NNP
year	null	DURATION	NN
end	null	O	VBZ
June	null	DATE	NNP
30	null	DATE	CD
British	null	MISC	NNP
Commissioner	null	O	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
hold	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
9	null	DURATION	CD
Nigeria	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
Commissioner	null	O	NNP
say	null	O	VBD
hold	null	O	VBN
for	null	O	IN
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
9	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NN
end	null	O	VBZ
in	null	O	IN
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
3	null	DURATION	CD
US	null	LOCATION	NNP
dollar	null	O	NN
stage	null	O	VBD
end	null	O	VBZ
in	null	O	IN
month	null	NUMBER	NNS
3	null	DURATION	CD
Nigeria	null	LOCATION	NNP
to	null	O	TO
defeat	null	O	NN
throughout	null	O	IN
jeer	null	O	VBN
respond	null	O	VBD
with	null	O	IN
display	null	O	NN
against	null	O	IN
side	null	O	NN
reduce	null	O	VBD
for	null	O	IN
minute	null	NUMBER	NNS
50	null	DURATION	CD
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
readmit	null	O	VB
after	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
47	null	DURATION	CD
Honduras	null	LOCATION	NNP
clear	null	O	VBD
agree	null	O	VBZ
readmit	null	O	VB
after	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
47	null	DURATION	CD
American	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
States	null	ORGANIZATION	NNPS
of	null	ORGANIZATION	IN
Organization	null	ORGANIZATION	NNP
clear	null	O	VBD
agree	null	O	VBZ
readmit	null	O	VB
after	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
47	null	DURATION	CD
Cuba	null	LOCATION	NNP
rejoin	null	O	VB
clear	null	O	VBD
agree	null	O	VBZ
readmit	null	O	VB
after	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
47	null	DURATION	CD
chinese	null	MISC	JJ
in	null	O	IN
write	null	O	VBN
banner	null	O	NN
June	null	DATE	NNP
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
20	null	DURATION	CD
japanese	null	MISC	JJ
industry	null	O	NN
about	null	O	IN
think	null	O	VBG
in	null	O	IN
year	null	DATE	NNS
20	null	DATE	CD
Japan	null	LOCATION	NNP
man	null	O	NN
free	null	O	VBN
free	null	O	VBD
jail	null	O	NN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
17	null	DURATION	CD
Japan	null	LOCATION	NNP
man	null	O	NN
free	null	O	VBN
free	null	O	VBD
after	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
17	null	DURATION	CD
Japan	null	LOCATION	NNP
on	null	O	IN
jail	null	O	NN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
17	null	DURATION	CD
Japan	null	LOCATION	NNP
on	null	O	IN
jail	null	O	NN
free	null	O	VBD
after	null	O	IN
year	null	NUMBER	NNS
17	null	DURATION	CD
malaysian	null	LOCATION	JJ
border	null	O	NN
on	null	O	IN
area	null	O	NN
wrack	null	O	VBN
claim	null	O	VBD
life	null	O	NNS
3,700	null	NUMBER	CD
Germany	null	LOCATION	NNP
in	null	O	IN
